Chapter 96: I’m not joking around (1)

“I’m excited.”

“Haha. Thanks to Elder Hwang, I’ll get to see such an interesting event.”

Hwang Mun-Yak smiled at the praise pouring in from the people around him.

“I have to thank you for accepting the invitation. I hope you didn’t have a hard time coming all the way out here.”

“Hahaha. I couldn’t afford to miss this rare opportunity.”

Blessings and cheers came and went. However, Hwang Mun-Yak didn’t ignore that many of the people here were carefully examining the situation and trying to determine who would rise to the occasion at this conference.

There was no way that the people gathered here were simply there for idle entertainment.

Their interest was in the next generation of the two factions. Among them, most were there for the Southern Edge Sect.

The merchants and sects often seemed to be close yet distant at the same time. Considering how quickly a faction can rise or fall, everyone was sensitive to information concerning the strength of a sect. They were all hoping to invest in the next strong sect.

After all, power attracts wealth.

They are trying to estimate the future of the Southern Edge Sect by evaluating the younger generations’ performance here.

“A fight between Mount Hua and the Southern Edge Sect. Isn’t the opponent a bit disappointing, though?”

“You’re right. If they were trying to display their strength, they should have called for a strong sect. Will they really be able to display their best against Mount Hua?”

The public spoke in hushed tones.

‘This would be an objective evaluation.’

Hwang Mun-Yak didn’t believe their assessments were wrong.

Mount Hua now seemed like a joke compared to its past a hundred years ago. There was a time when the Southern Edge Sect could do nothing compared to Mount Hua, which held one of the top positions among the Nine Great Sects. However, Mount Hua lost its place and collapsed, while the Southern Edge Sect grew to attain a position as one of the Ten Great Sects.

But…

Hwang Mun-Yak’s gaze fell upon the disciples of Mount Hua gathered at one side. Hwang Mun-Yak frowned as he struggled to see Chung Myung.

‘I don’t think he’s the type to lose.’

So, is that child hiding some kind of clever trick?

Hwang Mun-Yak smiled.

‘It’s a bit unpleasant to see others rushing into Mount Hua, but Mount Hua’s reputation needs to spread for it to recover. So, this time, I cooperated with the young disciple without another thought.’

Hwang Mun-Yak’s heart swelled with anticipation at what might soon unfold.

Standing in the center, Un Am looked at both sides of the hall, where the disciples of Mount Hua and the Southern Edge Sect stood opposing one another and spoke. It was a bit flustering since an audience had suddenly appeared, but there was no difficulty leading it since the conference had become a tradition.

“First, the representatives of each faction’s disciples will engage each other one-on-one. Ten representatives of the second-class disciples will perform.”

Un Am spoke resolutely.

“Initiate!”

As soon as his words ended, one person from each side stood up.

Jin Geum-Ryong and Baek Cheon.

Each of them was the leader of their sect’s second-class disciples.

“Sahyung!”

“Sahyung! Do your best!”

“You must win!”

At the cheers of his juniors, Baek Cheon took a deep breath. His hardened face could show how nervous he was.

He turned his head, gave a final glance at his juniors, and proceeded to the center of the arena. Across from him, Jin Geum-Ryong strode forward in a relaxed manner.

The two men came face-to-face with one another.

“As expected.”

Along with the Eunha Guild, there was another large figure present. The head of the Daebung Merchant Guild, Wei Zikae, smiled upon seeing Jin Geum-Ryong.

“Jin Geum-Ryong is said to be a remarkably talented disciple that will one day lead the Southern Edge Sect. He has a truly fantastic presence.”

“That’s how a young hero should be.”

Jin Geum-Ryong, donning a white robe and wielding a wooden sword in one hand, captured the crowd’s attention.

“But doesn’t the one across from him also look great?”

“When you say that, well, they seem to look alike. Like black and white, two contrasting sides of a painting.”

Baek Cheon, wearing a black uniform, stood tall against his foe.

“It feels like anticipation is rising in the air, but will Mount Hua’s disciple really be able to match Jin Geum-Ryong?”

“I don’t know. Mount Hua has indeed been weathering the storm for quite a while, but recently it feels like something about the sect has changed. If you think about the sect’s impressive legacy…there may be some unexpected results.”

Although that was said, no one genuinely thought Baek Cheon could defeat Jin Geum-Ryong.

The Mount Hua of today couldn’t be compared to their past glory. Hasn’t the crowd’s lack of faith been proven by how they had already severed their ties with the sect long ago? If they believed there was still any hope left for Mount Hua, they would never have burned their bridges so completely.

What the audience expected was to see how strong the Southern Edge Sect had become.

Sama Seung’s expression stiffened as he overheard the crowd’s idle banter. He understood that they were only speaking empty pleasantries to save Mount Hua’s dignity, but it left him feeling dirty.

‘Show them. Geum-Ryong.’

The reality was that Mount Hua was in no position to even be mentioned alongside the Southern Edge Sect.

Hyun Jong bit his lip and looked at Baek Cheon.

‘Show them everything you’ve got.’

So that there are no regrets.

While everyone had their own expectations and concerns, Jin Geum-Ryong and Baek Cheon faced off against each other.

And Jin Geum-Ryong spoke first.

“You came without running away.”

Baek Cheon answered with a determined face.

“I am the Great Sahyung of Mount Hua’s second-class disciples. There’s no way that I could run.”

“Big words, coming from you.”

Jin Geum-Ryong raised his sword and pointed at Baek Cheon.

“Well, the smallest dogs are known to bark the loudest.”

“Are you going to be bitten by a dog then?”

“I made a mistake. You aren’t even a dog.”

“You…”

“Try it once. As I said yesterday, I will show you. How insignificant you truly are.”

Baek Cheon didn’t bother responding. Instead, he briefly glanced at where Hyun Jong was sitting.

‘Sect leader is watching.’

Now was the time to set aside his personal grudges and selfishness.

‘I am the second-class disciple, Baek Cheon.’

Baek Cheon locked eyes with Jin Geum-Ryong. He, too, raised his wooden sword and squared off with his opponent.

Everyone watched as tension ignited the air.

One was the representative of Mount Hua, and the other was the Southern Edge Sect’s pride.

Normally, it would make sense for these two to face off against each other at the end and close the event. However, according to the conference’s tradition, these two will be the ones to open the event’s proceedings.

In a way, this battle would potentially determine the conference’s outcome entirely on its own. How could the audience not be bursting with anticipation?

The moment someone was about to speak, Baek Cheon moved.

Paaah!

The dull sound of the floor being struck clearly reverberated.

Continuing to sprint forward, Baek Cheon attempted to stab at Jin Geum-Ryong’s neck with efficient moves lacking unnecessary flair.

Swoosh!

Instead of facing the incoming blade directly, Jin Geum-Ryong deftly side-stepped and avoided the strike.

Swish!

Baek Cheon’s sword quickly pursued Jin Geum-Ryong. His wrist seemed to shake slightly, and soon an illusory sword technique was unleashed; it appeared as though dozens of strikes were being unleashed.

Mount Hua’s colorful sword arts enveloped the training hall.

“Oh!”

“Amazing!”

“The children of Mount Hua seem to have great skills.”

It was a splendid technique that made the people watching admire it.

Although the sword technique was displayed through a wooden sword, its sharpness matched that of a real blade. Yet, Jin Geum-Ryong stayed facing it. It was a wonder whether there was any way to deal with this onslaught.

The second and third-class disciples of Mount Hua could not help but clench their fists as they watched.

Jo Gul excitedly exclaimed.

“As expected of Baek Cheon sasuk! Sasuk’s Cheong Yang Fierce Tiger Sword is truly the best!”

Mount Hua’s disciples couldn’t hide their excitement.

They knew.

How much Baek Cheon had trained until his bones gave way. After being humiliated at the last conference, Baek Cheon hadn’t forgotten the disgrace he felt as he fully devoted himself to training.

It was Baek Cheon who volunteered for the closed-door training. The person capable of living the most pleasant life on Mount Hua chose to lock himself away and focus solely on the sword.

How could the disciples not support such a man?

Baek Cheon’s sword shadow splendidly pursued Jin Geum-Ryong as it keenly sliced the air. Each and every movement was sharp enough to wound. It was hard to tell what was real or fake as the illusory blade mixed in complex movements.

Hyun Jong, who carefully observed every detail, clenched his fist.

‘When did that child reach such a level?’

At that level, he wasn’t far behind the Un disciples. He knew Baek Cheon was talented, but this was astonishing!

The eyes of Mount Hua’s martial artists were colored with hope as they proudly watched Baek Cheon’s display.

Perhaps…

It might be different this time.

Even Yoon Jong couldn’t hide his shock and awe.

“Chung Myung! Sasuk is pushing him back!”

“Yes.”

“Maybe we can win!”

“No way.”

“Huh?”

Yoon Jong looked back at Chun Myung. Chung Myung was leaning back on his chair with a sullen face.

“If you want to win, you need to hit your enemy, but he can’t even land a single blow.”

“Still, we can win….”

“Does Sahyung’s face look like someone that’s sure of their victory?”

“Uh?”

Yoon Jong turned his head and looked at Baek Cheon again. Soon, he had no choice but to harden his expression.

Baek Cheon’s face seemed to crumble as he appeared to be struggling.

‘Why!’

Baek Cheon was swinging his sword with all his might.

The first step is intensely taken at the correct angle. Qi is raised and flows through the firm lower body through to the fingertips. Eventually, his sword is brandished with qi and swung with every fiber of his being.

Lightly, and lightly.

Light as a butterfly but sharp as a knife!

However, the light, yet sharp, sword never reached Jin Geum-Ryong’s body.

‘Why won’t it reach!? Why!?’

So far away.

The opponent standing in front of Baek Cheon seemed too far away. It was like standing in front of a cliff that pierced high into the sky.

A cliff he couldn’t dare to climb or cross.

Soaked in fear and perspiration, Baek Cheon screamed, unable to even wipe the sweat on his face.

“AAHHHH!”

One devastating blow.

Baek Cheon’s final strike displayed an illusion of several swords, all piercing at Jin Geum-Ryong.

It was then.

Kang!

Jin Geum-Ryong wielded his sword for the first time and deflected Baek Cheon’s technique.

With the sword stopped, the qi covering the field disappeared. Only then could Baek Cheon clearly see Jin Geum-Ryong’s face.

Unlike Baek Cheon, who was sweating and drenched in sweat, Jin Geum-Ryong had neither shed a single drop of sweat nor had any difficulty breathing. Instead, he simply observed Baek Cheon with a cheeky smile covering his face.

“Have you had your fun?”

“… You.”

“Stupid brat. No matter how hard you struggle to learn Mount Hua’s martial arts, do you really think you could even touch the hair on my head?”

Jin Geum-Ryong’s sword pierced Baek Cheon at an imperceptible speed.

Puak!

Baek Cheon fell to the floor with a gasp, unable to scream, as he was struck in the shoulder.

“Kua…”

Groaning, he forced himself to stand. When he raised his head, he saw Jin Geum-Ryong approaching him with a leisurely smile.

“You’ll soon understand with your body. Just how much of an idiot you are.”

Without mercy, Jin Geum-Ryong’s sword fell on Baek Cheon.

Chapter 97: I’m not joking around (2)

The difference was known from the start.

Jin Geum-Ryong has been recognized for his talent since childhood. Among the people Baek Cheon knew, the one most suited to being called a genius was Jin Geum-Ryong.

He had already experienced defeat.

In the last conference, and even before that, Baek Cheon had never won against Jin Geum-Ryong. He was only ever left with the bitter taste of defeat.

But

‘I thought I could narrow the gap this time.’

Because he worked so hard.

Chung Myung criticized his efforts as misguided, but Baek Cheon endured a bone-cutting ordeal for that training. At least, he was confident that he trained twice as much as Jin Geum-Ryong.

He believed that even if he couldn’t win, he would have at least slightly bridged the divide between them.

But the reality was worse than he’d imagined.

Puck!

“Kuak!”

Jin Geum-Ryong’s sword struck Baek Cheon’s ankle. As he staggered back, he desperately clenched his teeth to sober himself enough to regain balance.

Baek Cheon’s ankle would have been severed if this was a real sword. Thankfully, it wasn’t a real sword but a wooden one.

But conversely, since this wasn’t a real sword, he couldn’t even accept defeat so easily.

‘Why can’t I reach you?’

‘Why!?’

‘I tried so hard!’

Puak!

Jin Geum-Ryong’s sword flew again and hit Baek Cheon’s other thigh.

The impact almost broke the bone. For a moment, Baek Cheon’s distraught mind was lost to pain, but he neither groaned nor screamed. He slapped the floor with his wooden sword and tried to attack again.

“Euuhhhhhh!”

His sword aimed for Jin Geum-Ryong’s head. A simple blow, but it was fast and sharp.

“Slow.”

However, Jin Geum-Ryong took a step back and twisted his body to negate the attack.

Puck!

And Jin Geum-Ryong’s sword struck Baek Cheon’s left shoulder.

His flesh burst from the impact, and blood began to drip from the wound.

“Kuak.”

It would only take one more attack for Jin Geum-Ryong to perfectly finish this match. However, he didn’t end it and stepped back instead.

He looked down at Baek Cheon with an arrogant expression.

“Kuaak.”

Baek Cheon, with one hand, pressed heavily on the ground and tried to raise himself up again.

“…”

Bloodshot eyes.

Despite the pain, he glared at Jin Geum-Ryong with a fierce will.

“Oh?”

Jin Geum-Ryong looked at Baek Cheon, a bit surprised.

“You’re struggling so hard just to stand, but your spirit is still alive.”

Jin Geum-Ryong raised his sword at Baek Cheon.

“But that spirit is all you have. You will remain unable to even touch the hem of my clothes for the rest of your life.”

“… why?”

“You must really lack a brain. I already told you.”

Taking a look around, Jin Geum-Ryong spoke.

“That’s how great the difference between Mount Hua and the Southern Edge Sect is. The martial arts of Mount Hua cannot compare to the martial arts of the Southern Edge Sect. A hundred years may pass! Even if you had a thousand years! Nothing would change!”

An arrogant declaration.

But no one could refute Jin Geum-Ryong. Even the elders of Mount Hua could only listen and bite their lips, but they could not bring themselves to decry his remark.

Hyun Jong shut his eyes tightly.

‘How long must we endure this? How far does he intend to go?’

Who could understand this situation? The elders of the sect were unable to condemn or punish a second-class disciple despite him uttering such humiliating words.

‘My disciples’

‘Forgive me.’

But Jin Geum-Ryong’s arrogance didn’t end there.

He smiled at Baek Cheon.

“If you still want to catch up to me even after this, then you’d better leave Mount Hua. There’s no future here. The only thing left for this ruined sect is ridicule.”

Baek Cheon clenched his teeth.

“I… am a disciple of Mount Hua.”

“Well, that’s fine. Then if that’s the case….”

Jin Geum-Ryong took his sword in hand and rushed at Baek Cheon.

Baek Cheon tried to somehow defend himself, but his arm failed to respond.

Puak!

A vicious sound rang out as Baek Cheon was struck another dozen times before he collapsed.

Thud!

Jin Geum-Ryong glanced at Baek Cheon, who fell unconscious and grinned.

“I need to show you. Ah, my bad. It’s a little too late now.”

With a sly smirk, he retrieved his sword and stepped over the body of Baek Cheon. Steadily walking, he returned to his group.

Defeat.

A complete defeat.

“Sahyung!”

“Sasuk!!”

At that moment, all of Mount Hua’s disciples ran to the center of the hall.

“Sa-Sasuk!”

“D-Don’t mess with me!”

“…”

Baek Sang, who carefully held the unconscious Baek Cheon, was silent for a moment as he bowed his head. Then, he turned his head to glare with a grim expression.

“Isn’t this too much!?”

Jin Geum-Ryong, who was walking back to his sect, turned and looked at Baek Sang.

“What’s too much?”

“This is just a spar! How can you injure your opponent so harshly!?”

“Spar… isn’t that exactly why he ended up like that?”

“… what?”

Jin Geum-Ryong smiled.

“If this had been a battle with real swords, do you think he would simply be unconscious?”

“…”

“It’s because this was a spar that he’s able to stay alive. Am I wrong?”

“How dare you….”

“Don’t get too angry.”

“…”

Jin Geum-Ryong spoke with a grin.

“Even I’m a bit flustered here. I didn’t think he would be so weak. I thought he could at least defend himself. Maybe I expected too much; I apologize.”

Baek Sang bit his lip so hard he nearly drew blood.

A perfect defeat.

And over-the-top mockery afterward.

Baek Sang wanted to drag that guy out and tear him apart if he could.

But there was nothing Baek Sang could do about it.

“Take Sahyung to the treatment hall! Right now!”

“Yes!”

The sajaes holding Baek Cheon quickly carried him away while Baek Sang pulled out his wooden sword.

“Let’s see what this Southern Edge bastard’s sword is worth!”

“There’s no need to refuse. Seo-Han.”

“Yes! Sahyung!”

“Face him!”

“Yes!”

Jong Seo-Han entered the arena with a grin.

Seeing him walk so leisurely, Baek Sang tightly grasped his sword.

Contrary to the oppressive atmosphere forming between the disciples, the audience was enthused and deeply interested.

“So astonishing.”

“Baek Cheon was stronger than I thought, but Jin Geum-Ryong’s achievements exceed my expectations.”

“He is truly a man worthy of the praise he’s received. With such a fine disciple, wouldn’t the Southern Edge Sect be eligible to compete with the top sects?”

“I know. Hahaha.”

Hwang Mun-Yak’s expression went stiff.

‘This is why they are merchants.’

A man was being carried away in a miserable condition, but no one paid any attention to that.

The crowd was only interested in Jin Geum-Ryong, and how they could grasp onto the Southern Edge Sect in order to grow their wealth.

Hwang Mun-Yak isn’t much different from them, but he couldn’t hide his disgust at their actions in such moments.

‘This is a disastrous defeat.’

Baek Cheon and Jin Geum-Ryong.

Even if the representatives of two sects faced off, such a one-sided defeat was normally not possible. Mount Hua’s momentum would halt with such embarrassing results, and morale would sink.

Until the end, Baek Cheon never managed to land a single blow on Jin Geum-Ryong.

If the conference continued like this, Mount Hua would never be able to regain its past glory.

No, most likely, the sect’s downfall would accelerate. Because no one would be willing to acknowledge them.

No matter how heavily Hwang Mun-Yak supported them, reviving the sect would be impossible. This would be a death sentence.

‘Ugh. What the hell are you thinking?’

He thought that Chung Myung would have some plan, so he gathered the most influential people he could. But this was starting to go horribly wrong.

‘Was I overestimating the young disciple?’

Hwang Mun-Yak looked at Chung Myung.

“… is Sasuk fine?”

“There’s no way he’s fine.”

“Is he seriously hurt?”

“Badly.”

“…”

Chung Myung’s dispassionate response evoked a serious and angered reaction from Yoon Jong.

“No matter how bad our relationship is, that man is still our Sasuk! Are you seriously fine with our senior receiving such horrible treatment!?”

“Calm down, Sahyung.”

“You bastard!”

“I told you to calm down.”

Yoon Jong was shaken at how calm Chung Myung was. This was different from Chung Myung’s usual nature.

“You never thought he could win?”

“…”

Yoon Jong bit his lip.

He didn’t expect Sasuk to win. But… just the bare minimum at least. Baek Cheon was someone that carried the expectations of everyone in Mount Hua.

Perhaps the reason Yoon Jong was angry now wasn’t because of Baek Cheon’s injuries but because of his horrible defeat.

‘Is the gap between the Southern Edge Sect and us this big?’

The Ten Great Sects. The Ten Great Sects are incredibly powerful. But the disciples of Mount Hua never cared much about it. Probably because Mount Hua once belonged to that same group.

Although the sect had fallen, Yoon Jong believed that they could one day compete amongst the Ten Great Sects again with enough effort and luck.

However, it seemed like those sects were much stronger than he imagined.

Chung Myung smiled bitterly.

“If everything could be solved by effort alone, then everyone in this world could become a master. What matters isn’t how hard we try; it’s about how you apply your effort.”

“…”

“Watch. Take a good look from now on. All the second-class disciples will lose.”

“All of them?”

“There is not even one here who can defeat them. No, there is one, but I don’t think that person will fight.”

Yoon Jong’s face went stiff.

In the last conference, there were two draws and eight losses.

That itself was a disaster, and this time there won’t even be a draw?

“… if we lose like this…”

It’ll be miserable.

But Chung Myung stared at Yoon Jong with wide eyes.

“Lose? Who’s going to lose?”

“What? You just said….”

“That’s just the second-class disciples!”

“…”

Chung Myung blinked.

“Who’s going to let those Southern Edge bastards return from Mount Hua with a victory? Who will let them!? As long as my two eyes are open, I will never see that happen! Even if my eyes get dirt in them, I refuse to see that sight!”

“…”

“So, relax your body. Maybe we should try and do something flashy.”

“No, the—”

It was then.

“Aacccck!”

Yoon Jong quickly turned his head only for the sight of Baek Sang, lying brutally beaten on the floor, to flood his vision.

Jong Seo-Han kicked the fallen man while he was down.

“Think you can still put up a fight?”

“Uh…”

“It seems you’re all talk.”

Jong Seo-Han looked at Baek Sang and then at the disciples of Mount Hua. Then he made an arrogant gesture as if looking down on them.

Chung Myung’s mouth opened.

“No, but that bastard, what’s with him?”

“Catch him again!”

The third-class disciples rushed in and grabbed Chung Myung, who was ready to charge in.

Seeing that, Jong Seo-Han was dumbfounded and laughed.

“I get to see all kinds of things here. Well, you are just an unknown sect, so it’s understandable.”

“Oh?”

Chung Myung’s eyes widened.

“Let’s see how long you can keep smiling!”

‘You were the one who called for me!’

‘Now it’s too late to regret it!’

Chapter 98: I’m not joking around (3)

“… Sect leader.”

Hyun Jong just closed his eyes without saying anything.

“… Shouldn’t we stop this?”

Hyun Sang spoke with a trembling voice. But Hyun Jong couldn’t answer him.

Stop?

How does one stop this?

They were in the presence of so many influential leaders.

‘We can’t handle the Southern Edge Sect. If we continue, the children will only get injured, so it might be better to end this now.’

Was that what he should say?

That would be a complete disgrace to Mount Hua’s name.

Even if Mount Hua was on the verge of collapse… no, since they were on the verge of collapse, they have something they must absolutely protect. Their name and their pride.

If they were unable to safeguard their pride and the reputation of their name, then Mount Hua would no longer be a top-class sect facing ruination. They would truly become a third-rate sect undeserving of respect.

That would be the moment that Mount Hua truly collapses.

Hyun Jong couldn’t allow that. Not for the sake of his own honor but to protect the possibility that Mount Hua could someday be revived. So, as the sect leader, he could only remain silent in this situation.

However, the circumstances were so bad that even Hyun Sang, who understood Hyun Jong’s plight, couldn’t help but speak out.

Consecutive losses.

Nine times in a row.

They had already achieved the worst outcome of any conference yet. But the biggest issue wasn’t about winning or losing, but the content of the battles.

Nine disciples went forward, and not a single one of them could even touch their opponent. It was like watching a child challenge an adult. No, maybe that would be less tragic than this.

All the important leaders of Shaanxi were watching.

‘How can we handle this disgrace?’

Hyun Jong’s eyes trembled.

It felt like his five viscera were being torn apart inside his body. It wasn’t the humiliation that bothered him; it was the despair his disciples were experiencing.

Unable to gauge the strength of their opponent, they pushed these children into this hopeless battle. Thinking of the emotional impact this would have on the children, who suffered because of the incompetent elders, the sect leader wanted to chop himself to pieces.

“Sect leader…”

Hyun Jong opened his eyes as he let out a sigh.

“… this is saddening.”

“But…”

“Aren’t you upset with me?”

It was then.

“kuak!”

The last of the second-class disciples fell to the floor as his sword fell from his hand.

For a swordsman to lose their sword is a greater disgrace than death. The Southern Edge Sect’s disciple was so skillful that they only aimed for the wrist until they achieved their desired results.

“I don’t understand how a swordsman could let go of his sword. Doesn’t Mount Hua teach you what that means?”

Mockery.

Even with such insulting ridicule, no one could speak out.

Ten consecutive losses.

There was no result more disastrous than this. The faces of Mount Hua’s elders were horribly contorted.

‘Did it have to turn out like this?’

They thought they had finally gotten the opportunity to resurrect Mount Hua. Good things had constantly been happening lately.

But they were too immersed in their dreams; they forgot how cruel reality is. In the end, Mount Hua is a martial sect. Any luxury is meaningless if it isn’t supported by strength.

Everyone there became keenly aware of this harsh fact.

“Well done!”

“Yes, elder!”

Sama Seung patted Ark Ho on the shoulder.

This result was satisfactory.

Not only did everyone win, but every battle was entirely one-sided. The most encouraging aspect was that this was accomplished in full view of Shaanxi’s officials.

‘Now Mount Hua’s fame will fall to the ground and never rise again.’

Hadn’t they dreamed of this situation countless times over the past few generations? Sama Seung felt honored that he would be present to witness the sect’s long-cherished desire be fulfilled.

Perhaps by now, the audience understood the situation.

Unsurprisingly, murmured gossip could be heard.

“This is too one-sided.”

“Still, I had some expectations for Mount Hua… it seems that the past is the past, and the present is the present. Mount Hua can no longer be thought of as it was in the past.”

“Didn’t we already know that?”

“Still, this is too miserable… in fact, I really can’t tell if the Southern Edge Sect is strong or if Mount Hua is just too weak.”

“Isn’t it both?”

“A pity. So unfortunate. It seems like Mount Hua is really finished. All in vain….”

Sama Seung smiled as he heard it.

Public opinion had shifted towards the Southern Edge Sect. However, Sama Seung’s purpose here wasn’t to elevate the name of his sect; his goal was to send Mount Hua plummeting into the abyss.

To do that, even the sprouts needed to be burned to the ground.

“Now, it is time to end this. Did you see what your seniors did?”

“Yes, elder!”

The third-class disciples of the Southern Edge Sect looked determined.

“Do not hesitate.”

Sama Seung’s eyes shone.

“A lion does its best even when hunting a rabbit. Do not show mercy. You need to destroy them so horribly that they never think of learning martial arts again.”

“Yes! I will keep that in mind!”

Sama Seung looked up at the sky with a sly grin.

‘Such a clear day.’

And such a good day too.

“…”

Yoon Jong was at a loss for words.

He couldn’t bear to look at the second-class disciples gathered on the side. Even without seeing their expressions, he could tell how much despair they were drowning in.

And it was the same for the third-class disciples.

‘The difference between our sects is this big?’

The conferences held until now also ended in defeat, but it was never like this. It was never so one-sided. This conference gave off the feeling of a man casually stepping on a gathering of ants.

That was when they realized that Mount Hua had never dealt with the true Southern Edge Sect.

“… is it our turn?”

“…”

The faces of the third-class disciples darkened.

It was true that they trained under Chung Myung, but the gap in abilities that they witnessed completely crushed their confidence.

No, everyone has probably given up…

That wasn’t even the main problem…

Yoon Jong looked at Chung Myung, who was sitting next to him.

And gasp! He held his breath.

Crack!

The sound of teeth gnashing made his heart sink. Chung Myung’s face was boiling red like it would explode.

“…”

Every time one of the seniors was defeated, Chung Myung’s face would turn a slightly deeper shade of red; he now looked like a red plum.

Seeing Chung Myung’s face, Yoon Jong grabbed the hem of his uniform.

‘This bastard is going to lose control soon.’

Three years in the temple, and one becomes good at reciting scripture. Three months next to Chung Myung, and one will become a master of reading the room!

Yoon Jong spoke with a trembling voice.

“Chu—Chung Myung, let’s calm down.”

“… calm down?”

When Yoon Jong heard Chung Myung’s crooked voice, he felt his heart sink… no, he couldn’t give up! This was a conference between two sects! Not just the sect leader, but the people of the Southern Edge Sect and Shaanxi are watching!

If this guy had lost control, something even worse than the second-class disciples losing would happen.

Yoon Jong began to look at Chung Myung as if trying to soothe a rabid dog.

“Ch–Chung Myung. Think carefully. Remember what you said yesterday. In order for a person to accomplish great things, patience is the most important thing!”

“… patience.”

“Right! Patience!”

“… Sahyung.”

“Yes, Chung Myung. I remember those words well….”

“I’ve been thinking.”

“About?”

Chung Myung turned his head slowly, very slowly, to the side and matched Yoon Jong’s gaze.

And

Yoon Jong saw him.

Chung Myung’s eyes were half out of control.

“… I.”

Chung Myung growled like an animal and stood up.

“Don’t have any sense of patience in me!”

That isn’t something to be proud of.

You bastard!

Un Am took a deep breath. His face was pale, no longer able to handle this. He wanted to walk out and leave. But, unless the sect leader instructed him, he couldn’t stop.

“Next… we will hold the exchange of the third-class disciples. Of them—”

It was then.

“Catch him! Don’t ever let go of him!”

“Chung Myung! You’re supposed to go last!”

“People are watching! People are watching! Please! Don’t do this!”

Un Am was bewildered as he looked at the third-class disciples.

It seemed like they were united in trying to block someone as that person continued to push forward with glistening eyes.

‘Chung Myung?’

What’s wrong with that kid?

Un Am had his doubts, but he had to finish his speech. This was his role, and there were many people watching.

“So, the vanguard is—”

“Kuaaaak!”

But Un Am’s words were cut off once again.

As soon as he tried to announce the competitors, Chung Myung escaped from his sahyungs’ clutches and jumped forward.

“Phew.”

Chung Myung stepped into the arena and took a deep breath. Then he looked to the Southern Edge Sect’s side and spoke.

“One of you, quickly get up here!”

“…”

“Anyone works. Come up quick.”

Sama Seung spoke.

“… that crazy bastard!”

He knew that this child was crazy, but this was a whole different level. Not just the Southern Edge Sect, but he even dared to speak such arrogant words in the presence of Shaanxi’s officials!

“Elder, calm down.”

Jin Geum-Ryong quickly stopped Sama Seung from losing his composure.

“We can’t run around and fall into his pace. He’ll be in pain soon enough.”

“Hmmm!”

Seeing that Sama Seung was still greatly displeased, Jin Geum-Ryong coughed and called out.

“Woo-Ryang!”

“Yes, Sasuk!”

Seon Woo-Ryang, the disciple chosen to deal with Chung Myung, resolutely nodded his head.

“The schedule has changed, but it doesn’t make any difference to us. Complete your role.”

“Yes! Sasuk! Don’t worry!”

Seon Woo-Ryang grabbed his wooden sword and quickly arrived in front of Chung Myung.

Then, he aimed his sword at Chung Myung.

“I will crush that arrogant mouth of yours. I’m Southern Edge Sect’s…”

Instantly, Chung Myung disappeared from where he stood and manifested in front of his foe.

“Seon—”

He saw it.

A furious Asura-like visage appeared in front of him. The figure seemed like it was coated in darkness.

Darkness?

In broad daylight…

Ah, it wasn’t dark; something covered his sight. Since it was right in front of him, this…

‘Is a fist?’

At that moment.

Unlike anything the crowd had heard since entering Mount Hua, an explosive sound echoed throughout the hall.

Paaaaakkkkkkkk!

It rotates!

Seon Woo-Ryang’s body spun through the air more than a dozen times before falling to the ground.

“…”

Seon Woo-Ryang’s body, which was plastered to the floor, convulsed pitifully as if he had some medical condition.

Seeing his collapsed enemy, Chung Myung spoke as if dumbfounded.

“I’m not joking around.”

I am going to make you all beg for death.

Chapter 99: I’m not joking around (4)

A roaring sound that nobody could have heard in their lives.

The audience gathered at Mount Hua discovered that the collision between a human’s fist and another’s face could create such a violent sound.

And rotate.

Seon Woo-Ryong, who was hit, rotated in the air and…

Swisssh!

Blood poured from his nose like a waterfall as his body spun through the sky.

‘Maybe I can try for a rainbow?’

A rainbow made from blood.

Was there anything more horrifying than that?

It felt like the line between common sense, and nonsense was breaking apart.

Seon Woo-Ryang, who spun like a bloody windmill, fell to the floor and convulsed. Looking at the young disciple’s state, Chung Myung’s voice rang clearly in their ears.

“I’m not joking around.”

Chung Myung spat on the floor and pulled out the wooden sword around his waist.

“Get up, you son of a bitch. I’m not finished yet. My anger doesn’t die with one hit!”

Chung Myung was roaring like a lion, but it was far from regal…

‘Such dirty and petty words.’

These were Yoon Jong’s honest feelings.

“What…?”

Sama Seung’s beard trembled.

‘W-what is this….’

It happened in front of his eyes, but he couldn’t understand what had happened.

Chung Myung seemed to disappear for a moment and then reappeared in front of his disciple before delivering a blow. The disciple flew into the air, spun around, and then collapsed.

That was what Sama Seung saw.

The problem was that he seemed to disappear.

‘Did I miss that kid’s movement?’

Even though he didn’t care about the third-class disciples’ battles, did it make sense for an elder to miss the movement of such a young disciple?

‘No, no. It can’t be!’

Sama Seung denied what he saw. But this wasn’t his fault. Even if someone other than Sama Seung stood here, they would have reacted the same.

Anyone would surely deny a situation that went so far outside the bounds of common sense.

“You cowardly bastard!”

It was then, an angry voice came from the side of Sama Seung.

“Making a surprise attack when he was speaking! Mount Hua must not have any shame!”

“You wicked bastard!”

“…”

That was how it seemed to the children.

Well, that’s to be expected.

The higher level the opponent, the more significant it is. For the second-class disciples, it wasn’t surprising that they lost sight of Chung Myung’s movements for a few moments.

But for Sama Seung, it was different. He was an elder of the Southern Edge Sect.

Sama Seung calmed his startled heart and concentrated again.

“Seon Woo-Ryang. Get up!”

“Get up! Woo-Ryang!”

The sound of his disciples cheering for Seon Woo-Ryang could be heard. Sama Seung stared at the fallen child with his eyes still wide in shock.

‘I must be mistaken.’

It had to be.

No, it was undoubtedly a mistake.

“Wake up, brat. I didn’t even use qi, don’t be such a crybaby!”

Chung Myung looked at Seon Woo-Ryang with blazing eyes.

The disciples from the Southern Edge sect were cursing him, but Chung Myung made it a point to never listen to barking dogs.

The moment one steps onto the center of the arena, the fight begins. Why should he waste his time on courtesy by letting his opponent say whatever they wanted? If he gets sent to war, is he supposed to shake hands with his enemies, share a few drinks, and then start fighting?

“Kua… akk…”

Seon Woo-Ryang staggered and got up.

Although he was struck suddenly, it was a fist that lacked internal qi. So, he wouldn’t lose consciousness despite the pain.

What if Chung Myung had used internal qi?

Death! There was no need to ask!

Watching him rise, Chung Myung tapped himself on the shoulder with his wooden sword and observed his enemy.

“Get up quickly. Don’t waste my time… are you okay?”

Chung Myung’s voice, which had sounded annoyed and irritated, quickly softened.

“Uhh…”

Drip!

Pour!

This was because Seon Woo-Ryang’s nose was a waterfall of blood gushing nonstop.

So much blood was flowing that the front of Seon Woo-Ryang’s clothes was dripping wet, as a pool of blood collected at his feet. Even Chung Myung flinched at that sight.

Seon Woo-Ryang staggered to stand up and spoke through painful gasps.

“I-I can still fight….”

“But you’ll die?”

No, it seemed like he was really going to die.

Does a broken nose usually bleed that much? It didn’t seem like he had been struck with just a fist. Chung Myung would have to punch someone in the face without qi again to test it and find out.

Seon Woo-Ryang supported himself with trembling legs and covered his nose with both hands.

“The b-blood isn’t stopping….”

“You’re going to die! You brat!”

He would seriously die!

‘No, I’m not afraid of killing people, but it shouldn’t be like this!’

The first murder in Chung Myung’s new life was going to be from excessive blood loss after breaking a child’s nose with a single punch. What bullshit!

Chung Myung, who had such thoughts, looked at Un Am.

“Shouldn’t he get some treatment?”

It would turn into a murder on Mount Hua!

“T-that, well, it’s the rules. Um…”

Un Am was so flustered at this unexpected situation that he couldn’t even speak properly. In this case, there was no ruling on whether one could return to the battle after receiving treatment. In such situations, maybe he had to ask both sides for their understanding? But was the situation right now really calm enough for him to ask both sides?

Pour!

At that moment, Seon Woo-Ryang tore off the hem of his clothes and started to stuff it into his nose.

Stopping the blood?

Smart.

The hem of the shirt was stained in blood instantly, but as he continued to stuff his nose, he somehow managed to stop the blood from flowing further. Seon Woo-Ryang, who managed to control his blood loss, raised his sword at Chung Mung.

‘Ohhh! Is he going to continue?’

He knew that the Southern Edge bastards don’t give up easily. Such a unique bunch, Chung Myung felt oddly proud of their tenacious culture….

“You cowardly bastard!”

“… Huh?”

Chung Myung tilted his head.

“I’m ashamed… cough! Shame on you! What… gurgle…. You did… wrong!”

‘Just focus on one thing at a time. If you’re going to be angry, then be angry; if you’re hurt, go get treatment.’

“I’ll tear you apart and feed you to the dogs!”

Chung Myung frowned.

For now, he was going to erase the compliments he had given them from his memory.

“Is cursing at others the only thing you Southern Edge disciples learn? Maybe you just lack the wisdom to understand.”

- Are you really saying that?

Ah, seriously! Don’t come out whenever you want, Sahyung! What do I do with the current level that Mount Hua is at? I need to raise it!

Chung Myung clenched his sword and shook his head.

“I felt a little sorry for you, but that goodwill is all gone now. Just keep your mouth shut—”

“Even if you kowtow, bang your head on the ground, and beg, it’s too late! You son of a bitch! I’ll crush you so badly that your parents won’t even recognize you.”

“Ah, you’re going to keep talking. Well, whatever.”

The last shred of sympathy that he felt vanished.

Chung Myung raised his sword and aimed it at Seon Woo-Ryang.

“Come.”

“… you fucker!”

“Come, I’ll show you what it’s like to be unable to even touch your enemy.”

“Come, right now!”

It was then!

“Seon Woo-Ryang!”

A sharp voice burst from behind. Seon Woo-Ryang turned his head but flinched when he saw Jin Geum-Ryong’s expression.

“Don’t get excited and remain alert. Don’t underestimate your opponent.”

Seon Woo-Ryang looked back at Chung Myung.

All the second-class disciples had overwhelmed their opponents without being hit even once. But Seon Woo-Ryang was too excited when he acted; he went up and immediately got humiliated.

He grew up hearing lectures about how overexcited people cannot show their true abilities, but he forgot those lessons when he needed them the most.

He took a deep breath and regained control of his mind. He felt uncomfortable that he couldn’t breathe through his nose but was able to re-compose himself.

After getting his breathing under control, his heated gaze seemed to change into a frigid glare as he looked at Chung Myung.

“I will send you to hell!”

“… Yes, I’m sure you will.”

‘Let’s believe that. I don’t really know what I did to his nose either, but he can try whatever he wants.’

“I will show you that the disciples of Mount Hua will never be a match for the Southern Edge Sect. You should be prepared. Do not expect mercy.”

“Sure, sure, anything else? If you are done, then hurry up. Show me that I really can’t touch you.”

“You won’t even be able to touch me!”

“Didn’t I already hit you?”

‘Doesn’t his nose hurt?’

“I’ll kill you! You bastard!”

Seon Woo-Ryang swung his wooden sword and rushed at Chung Myung.

As if he regained his composure, the tip of his sword moved sharply. Surely, Seon Woo-Ryang deserved his title as the strongest third-class disciple in the Southern Edge Sect.

Dealing with him wouldn’t be easy; even Mount Hua’s second-class disciples would suffer at his hands. That’s not to even mention the third-class disciples.

But it was too bad for Seon Woo-Ryang; he had the worst possible opponent.

His enemy was the catastrophe of Mount Hua, Chung Myung.

“No!”

Chung Myung pulled his wooden sword back and ran at full speed at the opponent.

“Huh?”

Chung Myung’s sword, which was pulled back, swung like lightning as it crashed onto Seon Woo-Ryang’s head.

Paaaaakkkkk!

It was unavoidable.

How can anyone avoid an invisible sword?

Seon Woo-Ryang’s mouth fell open as his eyes rolled back.

‘I am dead.’

‘Ehh. He might die.’

‘That child is dead.’

Seon Woo-Ryang’s body crumpled down. However, Chung Myung had no intention of stopping.

“Kids these!”

Paaak!

One more hit to the fallen.

“Days don’t!”

Paaak!

Once more!

“Have manners! No manners!”

Seon Woo-Ryang’s body fell to the floor, and Chung Myung constantly hit him.

“Even I wasn’t like that back in my day!”

If the departed up in heaven had heard that lie, they would have thrown something down to catch this liar.

Sadly, those in the other world couldn’t interfere with those still living.

“You!”

Paaang!

Finally, Chung Myung kicked Seon Woo-Ryang in the crotch and turned away.

Seon Woo-Ryang, who soared in the air once again, fell to the floor.

Thud!

And Chung Myung clicked his tongue.

“If you didn’t curse at me, I would have been gentle with you. But kids these days, no manners!”

Hearing that, all the third-class disciples decided to never swear in front of Chung Myung.

“Ah, right.”

Chung Myung turned back again and approached Seon Woo-Ryang, who was convulsing.

He then grabbed the robe that Seon Woo-Ryang used to cover his nose and pulled it out.

The blood which had stopped began to flow again.

“Ugh, you couldn’t even stop this?”

Chung Myung looked at the Southern Edge Sect’s side.

Neither Sama Seung nor Jin Geum-Ryong nor anyone else could shut their wide-open mouths. They simply stared at Chung Myung with shock and astonishment.

“Surprised.”

He hadn’t even started yet, and they were already this surprised.

Chung Myung glanced at them and returned to his side.

Looking at his back, Sama Seung said,

“What the hell was that….”

But no one there knew that this was just the beginning.

Except for Chung Myung.

Chapter 100: I’m not joking around (5)

“…”

Hyun Young had a blank expression as he tilted his head.

‘How did this just happen?’

He was Mount Hua’s head of finance.

Since he was so quick at calculating and sensitive to profit and losses, he has evaluated potential talents whenever they entered the sect. However, the current condition of the sect made it impossible for him to concentrate on his martial arts.

Thanks to that, he became the weakest of the elders.

Because of this, it was difficult for Hyun Young to understand the scene that just unfolded in front of him.

Chung Myung defeated the disciple of the Southern Edge Sect overwhelmingly.

What was going on?

“No, sect leader….”

Hyun Young, who wanted to listen to the sect leader’s explanation, turned his head and flinched.

Hyun Jong had an expression that Hyun Young hadn’t seen on his face in decades.

His eyes were wide open as if they’d fall out, with his mouth hanging low enough for a bird to fly in. Both Hyun Jong and Hyun Sang were the same.

‘Should I also be surprised?’

He felt a bit upset that he couldn’t understand their reactions…

“Uh…”

“Huh?”

“Hm…”

“Hm?”

Hyun Jong’s eyes trembled as a small voice leaked from his throat as though his soul had been stolen away.

“Th-this… can’t… this can’t… be….”

A series of mesmerized murmurs were uttered over and over. Hyun Young gently pulled on his sleeve.

“Sect leader. People are watching. Get yourself together.”

Hyun Jong quickly shut his mouth. He was so shocked that he couldn’t stop his teeth from clattering.

“No, that child….”

Hyun Jong managed to calm his expression, but he couldn’t repress his surging mind. He raised his trembling hand and pointed to Chung Myung.

“He-He shouldn’t be like that… this… this makes no sense. We should have lost.”

In the end, Hyun Young got annoyed.

“What sort of abuse is that? After that child fought so valiantly, how could the sect leader say such a disgusting thing about their own disciple!?”

“… but this makes no sense. It makes no sense.”

Hyun Sang raised his hand and rubbed his face violently, and with his frozen expression, he asked.

“How long has that child been in our sect?”

“Less than six months.”

“You mean that he beat a disciple of the Southern Edge Sect after six months? And it was completely one-sided as well?”

“…”

Ah…

Thinking like that made no sense.

“Un Geom! Where's Un Geom?”

“I’m here, sect leader.”

Unlike the others, Un Geom seemed relatively calm.

“Before that child entered Mount Hua, did he learn any other martial arts?”

“No. Chung Myung showed no signs of learning anything before joining.”

“Then, in just six months, he grew this much?”

“Yes.”

Hyun Jong looked at Un Geom in disbelief.

“A genius…”

Un Geom spoke as if it wasn’t a huge deal.

“I’m not sure if ‘genius’ suits that child. He’s a child that doesn’t reveal his true self. Even I haven’t been able to fully understand his actions.”

“Huh.”

When Hyun Jong burst out in admiration, Hyun Sang mumbled.

“I thought geniuses and divine dragons only ever fell into other people’s sects, this is… like we were searching for a sack of rice in the warehouse, but a golden calf jumped out instead.”

Hyun Jong was shocked.

“I thought he was just a wealth bringer, but….”

His mumbling represented the feeling of everyone who was watching.

How much has Chung Myung done for Mount Hua already? He didn’t need to have any martial arts talent at all. Chung Myung is only human; it wouldn’t be appropriate to get greedy and try to force unrealistic expectations onto a child that’s done so much for them.

But didn’t this situation show that he had an outstanding talent as well? Enough to take down a disciple from the Southern Edge so easily?

When everyone was shocked, Hyun Young quickly moved.

“Anyway, we got the win. Doesn’t this save our face?”

“…”

“…”

Hyun Jong and Hyun Sang dumbfoundedly turned their heads. Hyun Young grew angry and felt that the elders were acting absurd.

Coughing, he spoke and tried to clear the awkward atmosphere.

“For now, he’s saved our face. For now.”

“Seriously….”

“This is why the finance head should properly learn martial arts. You are the only one who can speak so casually in this absurd situation.”

Hyun Sang joked with Hyun Young, who felt it was an unfair assessment.

Hyun Jong lightly smiled and looked away toward Chung Myung.

‘Saved our face.’

Could it be said so simply?

‘Perhaps…’

The outcome of today’s conference may not matter at all. It was possible that Mount Hua had just acquired a talent that could carry the sect for the next 100 years.

“… Mount Hua’s child seems to have won.”

“Um, looks like it. But…”

“… wasn’t that too one-sided?”

“Oh, this was quite unexpected.”

Hwang Mun-Yak was relaxed as he enjoyed listening to the reactions around him.

‘Of course, he should act out like that!’

Hwang Mun-Yak didn’t know how strong Chung Myung was. He wasn’t even conscious when the Eunha Guild events were settled by that child.

He had been told that a single hit from Lee Song-Baek was enough for Chung Myung to cough up blood, but he didn’t believe it. He couldn’t believe it; that child was too insidious. He must have been playing the victim to capture the culprit.

For Hwang Mun-Yak, Chung Myung was an unknown element. However, the reason he could watch and remain relaxed was that…

‘There’s no way that young brat would underestimate his opponent and entertain a loss.’

It wasn’t like he knew Chung Myung very well, but he was the man whose eye for appraisal built the Eunha Guild up to its current level. In his eyes, Chung Myung stepped ahead with confidence, which meant he was strong enough to ensure victory.

Of course, this was a more radical result than what Hwang Mun-Yak expected.

‘Right. This isn’t a lost cause; that much is clear.’

‘Is this conference a battleground for Chung Myung? Then, the results may be different from what everyone expects.’

“There are talents in Mount Hua too.”

“Considering the age, it’s a great display. No, no, great wouldn’t be enough to suffice.”

“The Southern Edge Sect’s disciples can’t be defeated with luck alone, and that was the best of the third-class disciples. Wasn’t there a big difference between them too?”

“To take the lead so confidently, that child was surely an outstanding talent from the Southern Edge Sect, but it was completely one-sided.”

The conversation between the merchants and officials sounded like a melodious song to Hwang Mun-Yak.

However, Hwang Mun-Yak didn’t miss these voices’ extraordinary heat. It was hard to hear praises for the Southern Edge Sect anymore, but there was also no one there who hadn’t set their sights on Chung Myung.

‘Don’t even dream about it! He is the fish I caught.’

With one hit, Chung Myung managed to get more attention than Jin Geum-Ryong. No, no matter how this conference of sects ended, the name of Chung Myung would now spread throughout Shaanxi.

Hwang Mun-Yak glanced at Chung Myung, who returned to his seat with a smile.

“But they only won once. If all the other disciples lose, then it will just mean that he’s the only outstanding one there.”

“That could be true.”

Hwang Mun-Yak narrowed his eyes and looked at the third-class disciples that welcomed Chung Myung.

‘Now, show me. Chung Myung, show them all!’

Indeed.

Will it end with one outstanding win?

Or will Mount Hua be able to counterattack?

Chung Myung sat down with a smug expression as the sunlight fell on him.

The burning irritation which colored his expression had vanished, and in its place was a relaxed face that seemed to have no concerns.

‘How can he be so happy after beating someone up like that?’

‘Even the devil wouldn’t look so relieved!’

Although the disciples had these thoughts, they felt oddly gratified and burst out.

“Chung Myung! You did well!”

“Shouldn’t you have stepped on him a bit more?”

“He must have lost ten years of his life!”

Seeing the sajaes cheer, Yoon Jong smiled.

‘I guess they are all true masters.’

They would have decried such actions if they had experienced a similar situation before Chung Mung arrived. Such as whether they needed to go so far or how could a disciple of Mount Hua be so vicious; they would have spoken innocent words like that.

But now that they had been tainted in Chung Myung’s color, they cheered as if they were staging a festival.

Even Yoon Jong couldn’t help but smile as he spoke.

“Chung Myung, you did well.”

“Well, I just had a little fun.”

It was a bad thing to say, but at this moment, it seemed justified and made the other disciples feel relieved.

‘I knew he was strong, but….’

They didn’t expect Chung Myung to be able to utterly sweep through a disciple of the Southern Edge Sect.

This would be enough to shake their confidence. Mount Hua’s disciples felt pity for the Southern Edge Sect for the first time.

Mount Hua was always in a position of receiving pity from others and was never able to sympathize with others.

Yoon Jong deeply realized that he could feel pity for all mankind by becoming entangled with Chung Myung.

“Chung Myung, great job!”

“That was amazing, really!”

Even if their relationship with Chung Myung was rather strained, the second-class disciples still flocked towards him and cheered.

It wasn’t the third-class disciples or the elders, but the second-class disciples who were the happiest with Chung Myung’s results. He had helped them repay the disgrace they suffered.

The defeat was one thing, but the ridicule and insults that the Southern Edge Sect had directed towards them were unacceptable. Chung Myung beating his opponent was like a refreshing bucket of cold water pouring down on a blazing summer day. Despite their previous grievances, Chung Myung even began to look a bit cute to these seniors.

Personal feelings shouldn’t be included, but they were still happy that Chung Myung had managed to regain a bit of Mount Hua’s honor after being damaged in the matches so far.

‘So cheeky.’

‘If he has such skills, he can act however cheeky he wants!’

‘Maybe he’s a good child after all.’

Chung Myung shrugged his shoulders as he received everyone’s praises and looked at Yoon Jong.

“Sahyung!”

It was a firm voice. Yoon Jong, who guessed its meaning, nodded with a firm expression.

‘It’s my turn.’

Chung Myung accomplished his role… no, he overdid it. Now, Yoon Jong and the others should carry the flame.

Determined…

“What are you looking at so stupidly? Get out there.”

“…”

No, does this bastard have to send someone off like that?

“… Yes.”

Still, there was something Yoon Jong needed to ask.

“Do you have any advice? Some tips or knowledge about their martial arts?”

“Would you be able to use it even if you knew?”

“…”

“Just get out there. If you can see their face, you can slap it.”

“… I know.”

With bewildered eyes, Yoon Jong walked to the center of the arena. Looking at the eyes around him, his expression changed.

‘The atmosphere definitely changed.’

Mount Hua didn’t have any presence before. But thanks to Chung Myung, the mood changed.

There were expectations that the third-class disciples might be different.

It was Yoon Jong’s job to turn the audience’s expectations into a reality.

“Phew.”

He didn’t want to be nervous, but he couldn’t help it. Maybe it was because he didn’t expect so many eyes on him or because of Chung Myung’s performance.

But if Yoon Jong loses…

It was then.

“Sayung.”

Chung Myung called him from behind, and Yoon Jong looked back with a stiff face.

‘Right, any bastard with a conscience would offer some kind of encouragement.’

“If you lose, I’m going to kill you.”

“…”

‘Ah, I forgot for a moment that he’s Chung Myung.’

‘It was my fault. My fault.’

Taking a deep breath, Yoon Jong’s stiff face hardened again. He drew his sword, took his stance, and boldly stared at the disciples of the Southern Edge Sect.

Aiming his sword, he spoke.

“Yoon Jong, third-class disciple of Mount Hua, asks for an opponent from the Southern Edge Sect!”

The winds of change began to blow towards Mount Hua.

Chapter 101: I will make sure you never forget this day! (1)

“He’s…!”

“How dare he speak like that!”

The reaction was intense.

Jin Geum-Ryong clenched his teeth. While he was still reeling from the shocking defeat, Yoon Jong took the initiative to demand the next battle. Such a cheeky request made Jin Geum-Ryong’s blood boil.

On the other hand, Yoon Jong recoiled when he saw the fiery reaction on the Southern Edge’s side.

‘Did I overdo it?’

Although it was an event where they had to fight, it was natural that they’d react poorly after such apparent provocation.

However, this was something Yoon Jong had to do.

He had to continue carrying the momentum started by Chung Myung.

Jin Geum-Ryong shouted with an angry voice.

“Gong-Jin! Gong-Jin!”

“Yes, Sasuk!”

“Go! Smash that cocky bastard and hurry back!”

“Yes!”

Jin Geum-Ryong’s face was distorted.

He was a perfectionist. He desired a complete and total victory over Mount Hua, but now that perfect flow had been broken.

It was a crack that would be impossible to fill.

‘Chung Myung!’

His eyes turned to Chung Myung in the distance.

‘This idiot!’

Jin Geum-Ryong didn’t expect Seon Woo-Ryong to suffer such a devastating defeat. Was their disciple weaker than expected? Or was Chung Myung that much stronger than anticipated?

‘The latter.’

It was impossible for Jin Geum-Ryong to misinterpret Seon Woo-Ryang’s capabilities. He was undoubtedly the most powerful among the third-class disciples.

For him to be defeated by Chung Myung meant that he was much stronger than the Southern Edge Sect’s third-class disciples.

‘It’s possible. But the other disciples aren’t that strong.’

It was an unexpected blow, but he wasn’t disgraced yet. If the remaining disciples could claim victory and retake the momentum, the conference would end with Chung Myung being the only remarkable thing about Mount Hua.

Gong-Jin, one of the strongest of the third-class disciples, took to the stage and drew his wooden sword.

With that, Yoon Jong took a deep breath.

‘Is he my opponent again?’

This was actually sooner than Yoon Jong expected.

Yoon Jong battled Gong-Jin in the last conference as well. Back then, he was pushed back and crushed without even being able to counterattack.

Now, two years later...

‘Honestly, I had no chance to win.’

If it hadn’t been for Chung Myung’s arrival.

Before Chung Myung joined the sect, Yoon Jong never properly trained. To be precise, he trained out of obligation; he never trained with the desire to improve himself and grow powerful.

Because it all felt meaningless.

A lethargic air permeated Mount Hua and corrupted the disciples; the impact of their previous defeat at the Southern Edge Sect’s hands was just that great. Baek Cheon was the only one who challenged that wall of despair.

But then, one day, Chung Myung appeared as if he was a star that had dropped from the sky. Thanks to him, Yoon Jong was able to spend the past few months doing his best.

Could the gap have narrowed with just a couple months of training? Yoon Jong couldn’t be sure, but…

‘I won’t lose so easily.’

He is the great sahyung of the third-class disciples.

Even if Chung Myung was truly the one in charge of the third-class disciples, Yoon Jong still had his pride as the great sahyung. He refused to give an unseemly performance here.

Gong-Jin fiercely glared at Yoon Jong.

“No need for words. I’ll make you painfully aware of how deeply I care about victory.”

“I have no intention of saying anything either.”

“Words are useless!”

Gong-Jin yelled and rushed at Yoon Jong, who stood there grasping his sword.

‘His sword is swift and straight.’

A sword that can be seen clearly, a traditional sword that follows a predictable path.

Yet, the former Yoon Jong couldn’t stop it. That was the difference between Yoon Jong and Gong-Jin. A vast difference where clumsy tricks could not affect the technique’s flow.

But this time!

Kang!

Gong-Jin’s outstretched sword was blocked by Yoon Jong’s blade.

“Huh?”

Quickly responding to the unexpected collision, Gong-Jin retrieved his sword and stabbed it again.

“It looks like you haven’t been just playing around. But you still don’t have a chance.”

“Kuak!”

Yoon Jong continued to defend against Gong-Jin’s consecutive assaults.

It was fast.

And heavy.

Gong-Jin’s sword was faster and more intense than in the past. Yoon Jong could fully realize just how much he had struggled to improve. It was at least twice as strong as the last time they fought.

But…

‘Why?’

Kang! Kang! Kang!

Yoon Jong’s sword moved concisely to block the opponent.

Two years ago, he couldn’t even see this sword properly. That same frightening sword was even faster now, so why could he see it now?

It was a complete mystery.

‘Why can I see it so clearly?’

It wasn’t slow.

The strikes were fast. Fast enough to loudly cry out as they sliced through the air. Yet, Yoon Jong’s eyes could perfectly discern the sword’s path. It was nothing like the past, where he couldn’t react at all…

Kang!

Yoon Jong’s sword traveled in a simple fashion to efficiently deflect Gong-Jin’s strikes. Meanwhile, Gong-Jin was unable to overcome the recoil and struggled to correct his posture as he was pushed back.

“… you!”

Yoon Jong looked at him with a puzzled face.

“… is this all you have?”

“You…”

“Ah-No. Don’t get angry. I’m not trying to provoke you or anything; I am sincerely asking. You aren’t trying to disgrace me by only using half your strength or anything, right? I need to be sure.”

“You bastard! I’ll kill you!”

Gong-Jin was boiling red with fury; Yoon Jong’s innocent questions seemed like mockery to his ears. Seeing his reaction, Yoon Jong became more flustered at the situation rather than afraid.

‘Chung Myung. What the hell did that bastard do to us?’

Every movement of his rushing opponent could be seen and felt. Yoon Jong could tell by the simple movements of Gong-Jin’s shoulders which direction the strikes would come from.

It was not predicting the sword’s path; he could see it with his eyes and understand.

Swish!

Although the wooden sword was swung violently, Yoon Jong perfectly avoided it by taking a simple step back. The blade struck the empty air and fell in front of Yoon Jong.

Gong-Jin’s posture tilted as he put too much power into the sword. A small gap that the old Yoon Jong would have never been able to see had opened up in front of him, and he could see it as clear as day.

Puak!

Yoon Jong’s feet moved before his mind could fully process his own actions, kicking Gong-Jin in the side. When he saw that Gong-Jin had been thrown back by his kick, Yoon Jong unwittingly looked back.

Chung Myung!

Chung Myung was looking at him with downcast eyes.

As if he was bored and simply wanted this to end quickly.

‘That crazy bastard.’

It was no wonder that Chung Myung was behaving strangely.

It was as if he had already foreseen the results of this conference.

“Ahhhh!”

Gong-Jin had lost all reason at that time as his mind drowned in anger. He ran towards Yoon Jong once again. Seeing his foe’s charge, Yoon Jong spread his legs slightly and raised his sword.

From the top.

The basic posture of swordsmanship and the basic stance for the Equilibrium of Six Sword.

It was the same stance that Yoon Jong endlessly drilled into his body for 10 days straight.

Gong-Jin’s sword stretched out, and his movement began to change compared to the swordsmanship he’d displayed so far. If it was the old Yoon Jong, he would have felt flustered and been embarrassed by this sudden difference.

But now, Yoon Jong’s eyes could clearly see and understand everything.

All the changes and swordsmanship eventually come through the fingertips. He fixed his lower body like a mountain and didn’t miss a single movement…

Swoosh!

He saw it!

The moment when the sword and body connected. Yoon Jong didn’t miss that slight gap, and his body began to move automatically once he confirmed it.

Kwaaak!

The sword cut through the air. A blade that slashed with no hesitation.

An unshaken heart, a disciplined body, and a clear purpose.

This sword connected these three cornerstones and pierced through Gong-Jin’s sword path before striking him on the shoulder.

Frightened, Gong-Jin suddenly turned his sword to block the attack.

Kwang!

And the sword soared into the sky.

Gong-Jin’s sword spun violently as it flew through the sky and landed in the distance.

Thud!

The subtle sound of the sword hitting the ground rang quietly through the training hall, which was stunned into silence.

“…”

Everyone was quiet.

Some jumped up and stared incredulously.

Gong-Jin.

The Southern Edge Sect’s third-class disciple had collapsed to the ground unconscious. In front of him, Yoon Jong firmly stood tall, like a massive mountain.

A perfect victory without any declaration needed.

Yoon Jong, who looked at Gong-Jin, retrieved his sword and put it near his waist.

“I learned a lot.”

And turned around to return to his sect.

Shortly after, a thunderous roar erupted.

“Woaaahhh!”

“We won! We won! Yoon Jong Sahyung won!”

“Hahahaa! Insane, this makes no sense.”

Not just the children. Even the elders and the Un disciples were in an uproar.

“Uhahahaha! Yoon Jong! Yoon Jongggg!”

“Act appropriately, Sahyung!”

Hyun Young deftly grabbed Hyun Sang, who was about to rush over to Yoon Jong.

“Damn it! I am going to lose it! uhahahaha! We won! We won!”

“Sahyung! Be dignified! Control yourself!”

“Do I look like I can do that now!”

Even Hyun Young couldn’t hide his smile as he held onto Hyun Sang.

‘So good.’

Hyun Sang was always harsh on himself. Just like how the finance division was stressed because of Mount Hua’s condition, Hyun Sang was troubled at the decline of their martial arts. As head of martial arts, he needed to lead the development of the sect’s martial prowess. Yet he was resentful because there was nothing he could do to raise the level the disciples were stuck at.

He never showed it, but it was clear how frustrating it was.

But the third-class disciples, who they expected nothing from, were trampling all over the Southern Edge bastards!

‘Sect leader?’

Hyun Young looked at Hyun Jong.

He was smiling happily. Kind and comfy, just looking at him made one’s heart warm…

“Ahhhhhhh! Don’t follow the light! Come back, Sect Leader!”

Hyun Young threw away Hyun Sang, ran to Hyun Jong, and shook him by the shoulders.

“Get yourself together! Sect leader! Not now! Don’t let your soul escape!”

“E-everything has been accomplished….”

“No! We still have a long way to go! Call the practitioner! Medical practitioner!”

While that was happening, Yoon Jong returned to his group and shyly smiled at the sahyungs.

But he also…

Felt like flying.

But while everyone was dancing joyously, Jo Gul couldn’t smile. It was his turn next.

“Sahyung! Great Sahyung! How did you do that? What did you—”

“Gul.”

“Yes! Sahyung!”

“Just go.”

“… Huh?“

Yoon Jong smiled. Now he understood why Chung Myung didn’t say anything and just told him to leave.

“You won’t lose even if you want to. Just go; you will see soon enough.”

“…”

Jo Gul tilted his head.

But Yoon Jong didn’t speak anymore. With a stiff expression, Jo Gull headed to the center.

Without even looking at Jo Gul, Yoon Jong went to Chung Myung and sat next to him, then firmly asked.

“What did you do to us?”

Chun Myung lightly smiled while looking at Yoon Jong.

“What?”

“To us!”

“Ah, that?”

Chung Myung smiled and spoke.

“Nothing much. I just made you win.”

‘That is what I’m asking! How did you do that!?’

That goblin bastard!

Chapter 102: I will make sure you never forget this day! (2)

“Look there.”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung pointed to the central area and spoke.

While Jo Gul was taking his place, the disciples of the Southern Edge Sect came and retrieved the fallen Gong-Jin.

“What do you think of the Southern Edge sect?”

“What do you mean?”

“Are they strong? Weak?”

“Obviously, they’re strong.”

Chung Myung stared wide-eyed at Yoon Jong and asked.

“Then Sahyung defeated such a strong foe?”

“D-Don’t say that. It just happened; what do I know?”

Chung Myung shook his head and giggled.

“Strong. Right, strong. He’s strong for his age, but he’s weak too.”

“… what does that mean?”

“Because he learned so much more than what he should have been taught at that age.”

“Isn’t it good to learn a lot and get used to it?”

“Sahyung.”

Chung Myung reached out and drew the shape of a tower.

“Martial arts are like a tower. How tall you can build a tower depends on how strong the bottom floor and the foundation are.”

“… right.”

“But those people started building the second floor before the first was finished, then they added a third on top of the incomplete second as well. They’re adding weight to the first floor and building taller without strengthening the foundation first.”

“…”

“What do you think will happen if those kids collide with someone who perfectly developed their tower’s ground floor?”

“They’ll collapse.”

“That’s right.”

Chung Myung said,

“All I did was clear away the wood on the first floor Sahyung’s were building and reforged the foundation. It’s difficult to build, but it won’t crumble easily once built.”

“… I don’t understand. Did that training have such meaning?”

“What are the basics of martial arts?”

“Uh?”

Chung Myung’s face grew serious.

“There is one fundamental basic: to use the body to strike down the opponent perfectly. The stem forms from that one root, and then the branches proliferate. I just had Sahyungs focus on developing the roots.”

“Hmm.”

“See.”

Chung Myung pointed to Jo Gul. Jo Gul was facing off against the Southern Edge disciple that just came out.

“An unshakeable lower body, clean swordsmanship, and the eyesight to carefully observe everything happening. And above all….”

Jo Gul’s sword pushes the opponent’s sword and delivers a blow.

“Concentration capable of bringing out all of the body’s power at once.”

Puak!

Chung Myung smiled.

The disciple of the Southern Edge Sect collapsed, and Jo Gul looked at his opponent with a puzzled expression. He turned his head, unable to believe what he had done.

“For now, that is all you need. With that one alone, you can defeat all the kids your age.”

Of course, that isn’t all.

They also took the pill that Chung Myung gave them. By following through with Chung Myung’s training regime, the disciples managed to create bodies that were second to none.

If they didn’t lag behind in physical strength and internal qi, their battles were bound to be decided by their swordsmanship. And anyone who faced them without a solid foundation was destined to fall before them.

Jo Gul returned and looked at Chung Myung with blank eyes. Following his lead, another disciple from Mount Hua went forward.

Totally confident.

He was full of desire to fight and bring honor to their sect.

“I still don’t understand. If it’s that easy… then why don’t the other sects train like that?”

“Easy?”

Chung Myung shook his head.

“Was the training until now easy?”

“N-No. I didn’t mean that, but conceptually….”

“Sahyung.”

“Yes?”

“Sahyung must have studied, right? To be in good form, take rest, take care of one’s parents sincerely, and not deceive the weak or be greedy for riches. Above all, be polite to others, respect those below you, live life without losing yourself, keep your friends close, and be loyal to the nation. Can you do all of that?”

“No.”

“Why? Isn’t that how you become a true man?”

“That…”

Yoon Jong stayed silent. He knew what Chung Myung was talking about.

Everyone knows what it means to be an exceptional man. However, only two or three people in the nation can follow every tenet throughout their entire lives. Such a small number within this vast nation.

In other words, despite knowing what it takes, ordinary people cannot do it.

“Constant water dripping down can pierce a rock. Always devote yourself and work hard. Nothing is more important than effort. The ancestors endlessly emphasize hard work and dedication. Do you know the reason?”

“Well…”

“Because people can’t do that.”

Chung Myung had a bitter smile.

In fact, Chung Myung was the same in the past. He always craved stronger swordsmanship and fame, even though his Sahyung constantly nagged him about concentrating on his basics.

Even in Chung Myung’s final moments, he sought higher ground and never looked down.

Only after death did he realize.

“Train to the point of death, push past your limits and devote yourself to it again and again. It might sound like nonsense….”

Chung Myung pointed to the central area.

Gasp!

Mount Hua’s disciple was causing the Southern Edge Sect’s disciple to falter and retreat. It was an impressive sight; Mount Hua’s disciple wasn’t giving his foe any chance to attack or recover.

“But, that’s what happens.”

“…”

“Although we know what it takes, people can’t push themselves that hard. Who would choose to do so? After three days, they’d lie down and say they can’t do it, run away, or make some excuse.”

Yoon Jong nodded.

Didn’t they also try to escape? It was Chung Myung who grabbed them by the collar and forced them to continue.

“You…”

“Sahyungs did it.”

Chung Myung said firmly.

“This...”

“…”

“After you endured that, the match was already won. There is nothing more to see. Those who only look up without seeing what’s beneath their feet will lose their footing and collapse. If a bird without wings believes that it can fly, it’ll only realize the truth after the jump.”

Chung Myung clicked his tongue when he saw the disciple of the Southern Edge Sect being carried away.

“Their feet betrayed them, and now they’ll fall.”

Yoon Jong’s eyes trembled.

He thought that the training was being overdone. It wasn’t just once or twice that he wanted to curse Chung Myung for his vicious methods.

But he endured. He persevered until the end, hoping that he would grow stronger in some way, but all that training was done with a far-off future in mind?

‘Where the hell did this guy learn all this?’

Yoon Jong couldn’t understand Chung Myung at all, but he was certain of one thing.

Paaak!

Another Southern Edge disciple fell to the ground.

Yoon Jong knew.

His sajaes weren’t too different. At least, aside from Yoon Jong and Jo Gul, the ten disciples representing Mount Hua were all roughly equal in their abilities.

There was such a large difference between the previous disciple and his opponent. So the result of the next battle would be the same.

That meant…

‘We’re going to win?’

Mount Hua’s third-class disciples against the Southern Edge Sect?

Yoon Jong could feel it.

They were really winning against those bastards.

“W-we are winning?”

No one responded to Yoon Jong’s words. They couldn’t deny what was happening before them, but it wasn’t easy to believe either. It was because they never thought this could happen.

But there was no need for them to believe it.

No matter what Yoon Jong or anyone else thought, the result of the conference was real.

One person.

And another

“Achhh!”

A shrill scream signaled the end.

In an instant, ten disciples fell.

“Aaaakkkk! We won!”

“All ten! We won them all! Damn it!”

“Chung Myung! We did it! We did it!”

The third-class disciples clenched their fists and cheered. Some even wept. Even the second-class disciples were running to embrace them.

It was like a festival.

Ten wins in a row.

All of Mount Hua’s third-class disciples were victorious.

Ten consecutive victories followed after ten straight losses.

It was evident which side would have better momentum and which side had a greater sense of victory.

The disciples from Mount Hua defeated the third-class disciples of the Southern Edge Sect.

“Chung Myung!”

Yoon Jong grabbed his hand with a thrilled expression.

“We won! We won! Thank you! Thanks to you—”

Right when Yoon Jong was about to speak words of admiration that he’d kept hidden in his heart, Chung Myung spoke.

“Win?”

An icy air instantly froze the heated atmosphere as Chung Myung’s words escaped.

Everyone’s eyes focused on Chung Myung, who tilted his head to the side.

‘What’s wrong with him now?’

‘Here we go again. This time my heart will stop!’

Seeing their anxious gazes, he said.

“Like this?”

“… again, what more now?”

“We already lost ten times. After winning ten times, doesn’t that make this a draw?”

Right.

“But that…”

“Sahyung doesn’t seem to know.”

“Uh?”

“There’s no such thing as a draw in my vocabulary!”

Chung Myung’s eyes shone again!

‘Ah- please!’

‘The atmosphere is so good, Chung Myung, please!’

“Drawww! A draw with the Southern Edge Sect? I can’t carry that embarrassment all my life!”

He would be cursed to death even after death.

His Sahyung would softly smile down at him and stab away with sharp dagger-like retorts and insults. And what about the other Sahyungs? They would drag him around everywhere and speak about how he came to a draw with the Southern Edge Sect.

‘I’m not going to let that happen.’

Flames ignited in Chung Myung’s eyes.

If he was happy with a draw, he wouldn’t have even bothered starting this battle.

He still hadn’t paid them back for snatching away the Plum Blossom Sword technique. Now he was supposed to send them home with a draw after they insulted Mount Hua and the sect leader the entire time they were there?

That isn’t Chung Myung’s style.

Chung Myung began to laugh.

“This is the beginning. Ahh, just the beginning. Now! They won’t be able to walk themselves home. Hehehe.”

The third-class disciples slowly retreated, seeing Chung Myung’s eyes gleaming in madness.

‘He’s completely lost it.’

‘Was he stabbed to death by the Southern Edge Sect in a previous life? Why does he always go insane when the Southern Edge Sect comes into the picture?’

‘Isn’t this enough? What more are you going to do?’

It was then.

Chung Myung got up from the seat, and Yoon Jong jumped to his feet as well.

“Hey! Hey! Stop him—”

“Sahyung!”

When Yoon Jong tried to shout and stop his antics, Chung Myung spoke in a cold voice that was unlike his usual self.

“Huh?”

Pressured by force exuding from Chung Myung, Yoon Jong listened in bewilderment.

“From now on, don’t miss a single move of what I do. This applies to everyone. Understood?”

Chung Myung headed off to the central area as the Sahyungs simply nodded in response.

Everyone merely stared at his back as if possessed.

It was the back of the man that would lead Mount Hua, a sight they would see countless times from now on.

Chapter 103: I will make sure you never forget this day! (3)

“Kuak… Kuak…”

“Sect leader! Sect Leader, get yourself together! Where are the doctors!? Are they still away?”

“Doctor? Get out of the way!”

Hyun Sang pushed Hyun Young aside, put his hand on Hyun Jong’s back, and quickly began to channel his qi into the man.

‘No, his dantian is shaking in happiness?’

Hyun Sang was surprised; he had never heard of such an absurd thing. However, this bizarre event was happening right in front of him.

Hyun Jong took deep breaths as he received the elder’s qi infusion.

“I-I’ve calmed down.”

“Are you alright? Sect leader?”

“Am I fine?”

Hyun Jong stared absentmindedly at Hyun Sang; the elder couldn’t think of a time when he’d seen the sect leader look so dumbfounded before.

“You’re asking if I’m alright now?”

“… I made a mistake, Sahyung.”

“W-what are… uh, oh my….”

Hyun Jong took one deep breath after another. He wasn’t able to calm down.

Why?

Hyun Sang could understand. Even his hands were still trembling. How could the Sect Leader remain calm and not be thrilled right now?

“Un Geom!”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“D-did you teach the children that?”

Un Geom smiled slightly.

“I wish I could answer yes, I would be able to stand tall with my shoulders straight, but unfortunately, I did not. The third-class disciples conducted this training by themselves.”

“By themselves?”

Hyun Jong looked back at Un Geom incredulously, unable to understand.

“Sajae, explain it to me.”

Un Am urged Un Geom to be more detailed. Despite his usual calmness, he couldn’t stifle his excitement at this moment.

“Maybe Chung Myung…”

“Chung Myung?”

Now it wasn’t so shocking.

Whenever something happened, his name would come up. Even now, his heart somehow predicted this name would pop up.

“That child, what the hell has that child been doing?”

“Wasn’t the Sect Leader the one who gave him permission to enter the sect? You don’t know anything about him?”

“How could I know? He just showed up one day. I felt that it was meant to be, so I accepted him.”

That simple connection was creating unbelievable results.

Ever since Mount Hua was destroyed by the Demonic Sect and the ancestors were annihilated, Mount Hua was unable to defeat the Southern Edge Sect.

Actually, it wasn’t correct to say that they had won. Objectively speaking, Mount Hua no longer had the strength to even compete with the Southern Edge Sect. That’s why despite all of their previous provocations, Mount Hua was forced to remain silent and endure their lashings.

However, the third-class disciples overcame this disparity in strength, and it wasn’t just a victory but a clean sweep.

‘Oh, my ancestors.’

Hyun Jong’s eyes turned red.

The day had finally arrived.

Hyun Jong firmly believed that this day would come, but he thought that it would be impossible to see in his lifetime. He truly felt satisfied after witnessing this scene that he’d always dreamt of; he couldn’t bring himself to wish for anything more.

“Sect leader! We did it! The children did it!”

“Yes, I know. Right. Quite terrific.”

Hyun Jong wasn’t even able to speak coherently; he just continued to agree over and over.

‘Now that I’ve lived to see this, I can greet the ancestors with pride….’

‘What?’

‘Why is that child coming out again?’

Hyun Jong blinked several times to double-check. However, the scene in front of him didn’t change. With a wooden sword at his waist, Chung Myung walked toward the central arena once more.

He looked at Hyun Jong.

“I think he’s looking this way?”

“W-what is he going to do now?”

Now the expectations were greater than the concerns. Hyun Jong clenched his fist and continued to observe.

At that moment, Chung Myung smiled wickedly.

“…”

Could a Taoist make such an expression?

What the hell was he trying to do?

At that moment, Hyun Jong doubted whether this child had fallen from his path as a Taoist.

“You…. You! You pathetic bastards!”

Sama Seung was beside himself with anger. He bit his lip so severely that it tore, and blood flowed to the side.

Ten consecutive losses.

There was no defeat more disastrous. At first, they had secured ten straight wins, but no one would remember that. Losing to Mount Hua, and in such an overwhelming fashion, had paralyzed the elder’s mind.

Even if Mount Hua was unable to stand against their sect, nobody could laugh off such a disgraceful event as losing ten matches after dominating the previous ten. It wasn’t technically a loss, but it almost felt worse.

“Didn’t you all say that you were going to victoriously return as proud disciples of the Southern Edge Sect!? What the hell is this loss to Mount Hua!? You pathetic bastards!”

As if spewing fire, he kept coughing out his anger.

“You idiots are destroying the honor of the sect! You lost to Mount Hua in front of so many people!? To Mount Hua!? Ackk! You assholes!”

The third-class disciples couldn’t even look at Sama Seung or the second-class disciples who were glaring at them.

While Sama Seung was overwrought with anger, Jin Geum-Ryong glared at the young disciples as if he wanted to kill them.

It was done.

His hope for a clean victory had collapsed horribly.

A draw.

A draw with Mount Hua. Something they never dreamed of. But wasn’t that what happened?

“Damn it…”

Jin Geum-Ryong couldn’t hold back from cursing despite his elder being there. As he turned his bloodshot gaze filled with rage toward Mount Hua’s disciples, he was shocked at what he saw.

“That brat!”

Hearing his words, Sama Seung turned and watched as Chung Myung walked out.

‘That bastard!’

‘Even if I tore him apart, it wouldn’t be enough to calm down.’

As Sama Seung thought about it more deeply, wasn’t that child the one who started everything?

“Why is he coming out again?”

Everyone present shifted their focus to Chung Myung.

“Oh, my God. For such results….”

“It seems like Mount Hua has sharpened their swords. Unimaginable.”

“Ten wins, the third-class disciples from the Southern Edge Sect couldn’t defeat even one of Mount Hua’s disciples?”

And there was another thing no one spoke about.

The third-class disciples from Mount Hua defeated their opponents even more overwhelmingly than how Southern Edge’s second-class disciples secured their victories.

What’s more, it was pitiful to reflect on how the Southern Edge Sect’s disciples behaved while winning. At the time, it seemed natural for the strong to stand above their opponents. However, seeing Mount Hua’s third-class disciples handle their victories with grace made the Southern Edge’s previous ridicule and provocation seem ugly and resentful.

“Aren’t they superior in manners as well as their skill?”

“Truly, Mount Hua is a sect that deserves to be called prestigious. I am shocked by their composure.”

It’s going up.

Rising up and up.

Mount Hua’s name was rising up. At this moment, it had reached the sky.

Meanwhile, Elder Hwang struggled to suppress a joyous scream from his heart.

After this event, the audience would re-assess their initial thoughts about Mount Hua. It was apparent that some were already calculating how much to invest.

But the value will be difficult to determine. For them, these results were completely unexpected.

The more Hwang Mun-Yak thought about it, the more he realized just how wonderful it was for him to meet Chung Myung and invest in Mount Hua.

“Now then…”

It was then.

“Wait.”

Someone shouted when Elder Hwang was about to end the proceedings.

“Huh?”

Turning his head, he looked at the center and saw Chung Myung smiling.

“Isn’t he that boy from earlier?”

“He called himself Chung Myung. He spearheaded this victory.”

Hwang Mun-Yak met Chung Myung’s eyes while listening to the crowd gossip around him.

“What is it, young disciple?”

Chung Myung smiled and continued.

“I have a question I would like to ask. Since all of you saw everything that happened here, I think you can make an appropriate judgment.”

“What is it?”

“Who won?”

“Huh?”

Who won?

Well…

Hwang Mun-Yak’s expression hardened.

‘Young disciple doesn’t want to end this with a draw.’

He didn’t know what he planned, but he had to respond to it. Hwang Mun-Yak slowly turned his head and looked at everyone as he asked.

“What do you think? Come to think of it, we have yet to decide the winner or loser.”

The people of Shaanxi, who gathered there, fell into thought and began to speak one after another.

“A draw seems appropriate, but if we had to determine a winner, wouldn’t it be the Southern Edge Sect that won thanks to the older students?”

“What nonsense. What’s the purpose of this conference? Isn’t it for the future of the sects? Then shouldn’t we prioritize the third-class disciples? It’s a victory for Mount Hua, where the younger generation prevailed.”

“Huh, what are you saying? Potential is just potential. It’s always possible that the third-class disciples will fail to surpass Southern Edge’s second-class disciples.

“Then, you have to look at the situation of the Southern Edge Sect’s third-class disciples. They are all younger than the third-class disciples from Mount Hua! There’s a big difference in their ages!”

“The oldest of Mount Hua’s second-class disciples are even younger than the youngest of the Southern Edge Sect’s disciples!”

“No—this man!”

There was no conclusion.

Everyone had their own reasons, and they had their own preference for who won.

Hwang Mun-Yak, who listened from the side, then spoke.

“Young disciple. It is difficult to draw a conclusion.”

“Right?”

Chung Myung snapped.

“But if this ends, it would be uncomfortable for the audience here. Besides that, I’m sure the Southern Edge Sect would feel gloomy if we didn’t settle this with certainty.

“… what do you mean?”

“Simple.”

Chung Myung pointed to the Southern Edge sect.

“The ten people that won over there.”

“…”

The Southern Edge Sect listened to Chung Myung.

“Against the only ten that won from Mount Hua.”

“W-why us?”

Yoon Jong stuttered.

Chung Myung looked at both sides and spoke.

“The only solution is to remove the losers and put the winners back into the match. Would that give a clear answer?”

‘Is he crazy?’

‘What’s he planning? They are second-class disciples, and we are just third-class disciples!’

‘No. There’s no way he would jump into a losing fight. He must be up to something!’

Without disappointing the expectations of his sahyungs, Chung Myung put in a condition.

“Instead!”

‘Yes!’

Just as the third-class disciples felt relieved, a sound like thunder fell.

“Let’s set aside the boring one-on-one matches! One fighter will remain until the end. A fight where whoever wins continues battling until he loses. The winner will fight the next person in line. The last one standing wins. What do you think?

Chung Myung looked at the Southern Edge Sect with a unique smile.

“Of course, it’s understandable if they’re scared.”

It was an unavoidable attack.

Chapter 104: I will make sure you never forget this day! (4)

Jin Geum-Ryong was dumbfounded as he looked at Chung Myung.

‘What the hell is he up to now?’

Another fight?

Between the third and second-class disciples? Based on the winning streaks?

Was that how he intended to win?

“This…”

Jin Geum-Ryong sharpened his teeth.

There is a limit to how much the Southern Edge Sect can be ridiculed. As head of the second-class disciples, Jin Geum-Ryong refused to let this transgression go.

Even if Mount Hua’s third-class disciples were able to dominate their opponents, wasn’t that still just a battle between the same classes?

This classing isn’t something that can be overcome with talent and effort. If the difference between classes could be overcome so easily, the hierarchy of the sect’s disciples would collapse. That’s why many sects keep a large age gap between classes when accepting new disciples.

No matter how strong the third-class disciples of Mount Hua were, there was a fundamental difference between that and challenging the second-class disciples. Jin Geum-Ryong had never heard of a younger generation challenging the seniors of a sect before.

Just being offered such a proposal was shameful.

“That bastard…!”

As soon as Jin Geum-Ryong called out, Sama Seung grabbed his shoulder.

“E-elder.”

“Calm down.”

“But…”

Sama Seung’s face distorted.

“Our name has already been dragged through the mud. If we reject this offer to save face, others will only say that we ran away in fear.”

Jin Geum-Ryong bit his lip.

He couldn’t deny it. That damn bastard wouldn’t think twice about spreading that rumor. If the battle had been proposed politely or gently, there would have been a justified way to reject it. However, there was no way out when the child so brazenly provoked their sect.

It was a disgraceful proposal to accept, yet humiliating to reject.

Sama Seung raised his head and looked at Chung Myung.

“Chung Myung, was it?”

“Yes. You didn’t seem to remember very well before, but now you seem to get it.”

“I heard your suggestion, but I don’t think you’re in a position to make this offer on behalf of Mount Hua, are you?”

“Then ask the sect leader yourself. Well, it isn’t that hard.”

“You…”

That brat really could twist someone’s stomach with words alone.

“I’m pointing out your attitude. There’s an order to everything. Is this how they teach you in Mount Hua?

It was a cheap but effective attack. Once in a bad mood, attack using age and manners. Hasn’t this method been tried and true since the ancient past?

“I don’t know how Mount Hua teaches because I only joined recently. So, I haven’t had the time to learn properly. Since I grew up as an orphan, I have my shortcomings, so I hope you understand.”

“Uh…”

‘Suddenly mentioning his parents?’

‘Then what am I supposed to say?’

Chung Myung stared at Hwang Mun-Yak, while Sama Seung tried to find some other way to push him down.

“How about it?”

“I-it seems fine, but…?”

“There are only people from Mount Hua and the Southern Edge sect here. We need an objective judgment.”

‘Someone to take our side.’

With the officials of Shaanxi present, Southern Edge must strive for victory at all costs. They can’t afford to step down, or else they’d be disgraced as cowards who are afraid of losing to their opponents.

Hwang Mun-Yak coughed and asked while looking at the crowd.

“What do you think?”

“Umm. Regardless of what is fair or not, we would love to see more spars!”

“Actually, I want to see how well the third-class disciples can hold their ground against the second-class disciples. It’s very exciting.”

Hwang Mun-Yak nodded his head.

Of course, the audience would agree. This would take the fighting to the next level. By asking a third-class disciple to face a second-class, one could see how strong the disciples really are.

“I’m looking forward to it, young disciple.”

Chung Myung nodded his head.

“So, the audience has given permission. Sect leader! How about you!?”

Hyun Jong looked at Chung Myung with a puzzled expression.

“What is he doing?”

Hyun Jong asked Un Geom for help.

“Allow him, Sect leader.”

“Allow? You think I should allow this nonsense?”

“He’s a smart child.”

“…”

Un Geom spoke firmly.

“Maybe this sounds exaggerated, but I’ve never felt that child to be foolish or immature. In fact, there are times when it seemed like he was teasing me or trying to pull one over my head. Didn’t Sect Leader also admit that this boy has a certain depth to him?

“Sure, but…”

Clearly, that was the case with Chung Myung.

He was like an old man wearing the mask of a child.

“There is no way such a child could act ignorant suddenly. I’m sure that he has an answer ready, so please allow it. Above all else….”

Un Geom smiled and spoke.

“What’s wrong with losing now? We have nothing to lose anyway.”

Hyun Jong looked at Un Geom, confidence gleaming within his eyes.

Hyun Jong looked at the remaining elders and confirmed their thoughts through their eyes before nodding in consent.

‘If it’s as Un Geom said, then everything that’s happened was due to that child’s plan.’

There was nothing left to do but to trust that everything would work out.

Hyun Jong wondered if he was expecting too much from a child, but Mount Hua truly had nothing to lose.

Even if they lost horribly, they wouldn’t forget the victories they had already earned.

Hyun Jong, who made up his mind, spoke in a loud voice.

“Mount Hua agrees.”

Immediately, cheers erupted from the onlookers.

“Oh! Then the Southern Edge can’t back down!”

“Such spectacular events today! I need to talk about what I saw. I didn’t expect such a lively show!”

“Mount Hua is Mount Hua, after all. No wonder it’s called the most prestigious sect! There may be ups and downs, but there’s no downfall.”

Hwang Mun-Yak smiled bitterly as he heard the change in the crowd’s attitude.

‘Bat-like bastards!’

But this was the nature of a merchant and the general reaction of most people. Isn’t it human nature to want to befriend powerful and promising figures?

In other words, Mount Hua was starting to look like a place worthy of risk and trade.

‘Then… how will the Southern Edge Sect react?’

Personally, Hwang Mun-Yak would never accept this offer. Because there were no benefits to be won but much to lose. But what if he was in Sama Seung’s position?

‘I would accept.’

Unlike merchants, a martial arts sect cannot simply withdraw.

This was because of their self-esteem and pride.

It was impossible to retract their tail and cower away after receiving such an advantageous offer from a sect that’s weaker than themselves. So, naturally…

“We agree as well!”

That’s right!

They would obviously come out.

Hwang Mun-Yak looked at them with excitement.

Yoon Jong sprinted up with a terrified face and grabbed Chung Myung before dragging him along.

“What’s wrong with you?”

When Chung Myung protested, Yoon Jong pulled him to the corner and softly asked.

“Brat! What are you up to?”

“What?”

“How can we defeat the second-class disciples? They’re the second-class disciples of the Southern Edge sect! Jin Geum-Ryong! The best in Shaanxi!”

“Oh? Really?”

“N-No way, do you really think we can beat them? Are you saying we got that much stronger?”

“Sahyung.”

“Uh?”

“Don’t you think people should have a conscience?”

“…”

“I rescued a drowning man, and now he wants to fight someone that’s armed with a club in hand. What? You think you could win?”

“A-No… I was just asking.”

Yoon Jong was excited and hopeful, just a little bit.

“Don’t even dream about it. You won’t win.”

Especially over Jin Geum-Ryong.

If it was any of the other disciples, maybe it was worth a try? Well… that wouldn’t be easy either. But if Jin Geum-Ryong steps forward, none of the third-class disciples would be able to do anything.

What Chung Myung taught would work on those of the same age, but the difference was too great when fighting someone older and more experienced.

“T-then what are you going to do?”

Chung Myung chuckled.

“The plan is simple….”

“Wheel Warfare…”

Sama Seung said firmly.

“It’s obvious what they’re planning. They want to whittle down our strength by cycling through their disciples in order to score at least one victory against us. After battling nine times in a row, their last competitor will be able to secure an easy victory over our exhausted disciple.”

Sama Seung immediately recognized what was happening.

The victor continues to fight.

In other words, those who don’t lose can’t step down. If they continue to win consecutively, they will drain all of their stamina.

“Maybe he assumed that Jin Geum-Ryong would lead the charge.”

Jin Geum-Ryong takes the lead. After nine of the third-class disciples came out, he would be exhausted and out of stamina. Finally, Chung Myung would come and defeat the tired Jin Geum-Ryong.

Nine defeats and only one victory.

But this one win would be worth more than all nine defeats. The fact that Jin Geum-Ryong of the Southern Edge Sect was defeated by Mount Hua’s third-class disciples would spread.

Sama Seung ground his teeth.

“Such a sneaky bastard.”

Shaking his head, he looked at Jin Geum-Ryong.

“You know what you have to do.”

Jin Geum-Ryong.

“Without losing. Over ten. Over twenty! I will deal with as many as you like.”

“No.”

“… Uh?”

Sama Seung shook his head.

“There’s no need for you to jump into their trap.”

Jin Geum-Ryong showed a look of disgust.

“But…”

“What pride is there in willingly jumping into your enemy’s trap? People will only discuss how those third-class disciples toyed around with you.”

Jin geum-Ryong bit his lip.

That made sense. This match was strange from the start and could be interpreted that way.

“You will go last.”

“… Yes, I understand.”

“The first…”

Sama Seung turned his head.

“You go, Yu Baek.”

“Yes, elder! I will not disappoint you.”

“It’s alright even if we don’t win every match. Defeat as many as you can until you run out of stamina; once you feel exhausted, simply surrender and return. Never fall under their swords. Do you understand?

“Yes!”

Sama Seung gnashed his teeth.

It was best if Yu Baek defeated everyone. If he’s unable to, at the very least, they should finish by only sending out two people.

‘Then Jong Seo-Han? Since Geum-Ryong can’t go out, he’s the next best. Lee Song-Baek has been strong lately as well….’

“Ugh?”

At that moment, he heard a bizarre whistling sound and looked at the stage.

“… w-what?”

And Sama Seung saw it.

Chung Myung, who had been dragged away by someone to talk to, walked out on stage with a wooden sword draped over his shoulder.

“Plan, what plan? Hurry and come get beaten. I am the plan!”

Chung Myung smiled as he lowered his head.

“I will make this a day you can never forget, Southern Edge Sect.”

It was a calm but bold declaration.

Chapter 105: I will make sure you never forget this day! (5)

Everyone’s eyes were focused on Chung Myung.

The fact that Chung Myung took the lead was something no one predicted.

Anybody with some knowledge of martial arts… no, even a person with no understanding of martial arts could tell that Chung Myung was the most exceptional among Mount Hua’s third-class disciples.

Usually, the strongest fighter would wait until the final moments to have a favorable chance at victory, especially in events like this where the winner continues until they lose.

‘What the hell is he thinking?’

‘Does he want to fight against the Southern Edge Sect’s disciples head-on?’

Those who predicted some kind of trick out of Chung Myung were confused and struggled to comprehend his actions.

Hyun Jong and Un Geom were the same, as were Hwang Mun-Yak and Yoon Jong.

“S-sahyung. Shouldn’t we stop him now? I will take the lead. Then—”

“You know there’s nothing we can do, right?”

When the third-class disciples approached him and asked, Yoon Jong, frowned.

“How can we stop him when he’s the one throwing himself out there?”

Everyone’s concerned gazes focused on Chung Myung’s back. But Chung Myung simply kept his sights on the Southern Edge Sect.

‘Do kids today know the legend of the strongest swordsman that single-handedly defeated a gang of people when he was just fifteen?’

Maybe the story was still told. Well, this person was from an era even before Chung Myung, but he’d heard this story over and over again.

‘It’s said that Buddha was just eighteen when he gained insight.’

That was also a story that resonated throughout the world.

Other than that, there were no other examples.

The masters of those generations, who made names for themselves since childhood, must have also been told similar legends.

Why? Because without such stories, there would be no conversation.

The world they lived in praised the strong. In order to prove one’s strength and display their skills, a worthy opponent must be overcome.

Martial sects were the same.

No matter how strong Mount Hua becomes, no one would appreciate the change if they could not prove it. Whether they grew twice as strong or ten times, no one would ever know that change came to Mount Hua.

Change must be seen with the eyes and experienced with the body. Every powerful person needed to recognize the change Mount Hua was undergoing. That was the quickest way to rebuild Mount Hua’s reputation.

And today.

Chung Myung intended to create a legend that would spread the name of Mount Hua.

‘There are two ways to make a name for a sect.’

One is to build achievements that no one can ignore.

And the other is to prove the sect’s strength.

The strongest sect? That’s good.

The best swordsman in the world? That’s good too.

However, the best way is to have rising stars among the disciples.

People treat others the most favorably when they have higher expectations of them. The strongest sect may be seen as an enemy, while the strongest swordsman would be seen as competition. Rather than those options, having powerful disciples with potential that live up to the expectations of others is the most comfortable way.

There is a reason that young geniuses are evaluated as rising dragons and tigers. This was an eternal law of sects that has been passed down from generation to generation.

Mount Hua’s third-class disciples defeated the Southern Edge Sect’s third-class disciples?

That would be a fun story.

The third-class disciples defeated Southern Edge Sect’s second-class disciples?

That’s a remarkable event.

But!

A single third-class disciple from Mount Hua swept through Southern Edge Sect’s second-class disciples one after another?

This news would turn the world upside down.

And it would become a shame that the Southern Edge Sect would be unable to wash away for generations.

Chung Myung smiled.

‘Why did you have to touch Mount Hua?’

‘If you wanted to touch it, you should have done it when I wasn’t alive.’

“Well, shouldn’t I collect some interest while I’m at it?”

As Chung Myung raised his sword, Yu Baek approached and stood across from him as he spoke.

“Your confidence is clearly second to none in this world, but I’ll let you know that self-confidence without skill is a shortcut to a disgraceful defeat.”

“Phew.”

Chung Myung just lifted the sword without answering.

Normally, he would have said something back, but now he wasn’t in the mood.

Instead, he looked back at the third-class disciples of Mount Hua.

“Sahyung.”

“…C-concentrate on the match!”

“Remember my words. Do not miss a thing.”

“Huh?”

Perhaps this was a rare chance to see an interesting performance from a real match.

Chung Myung looked at Yu Baek and said

“Mount Hua’s third-class disciple, Chung Myung, asks for a match.”

Yu Baek, who was about to say something, flinched and then accepted.

“The Southern Edge Sect’s second-class disciple, Yu Baek, accepts Mount Hua’s offer.”

The third-class disciples who were watching felt their bodies tense up.

‘There’s something different about him right now.’

This wasn’t the usual Chung Myung that they knew.

The usual Chung Myung would have provoked the enemy in front of him the moment he stood against him. However, his iconic playfulness was nowhere to be found.

A frigid feeling came from his back that left them feeling cold.

Like…

A swordsman heading into the battlefield.

Yoon Jong couldn’t take his eyes off Chung Myung as if he was possessed; he felt that something extraordinary was about to happen.

And at that moment

Chung Myung’s sword moved slowly.

The sword that began moving from above slowly descended until it was brought back to its original form.

Yoon Jong couldn’t breathe as he saw this scene.

The Initial form.

Chung Myung was now displaying the initial form of the Equilibrium of Six Sword.

The initial form was a greeting and courtesy to inform the opponent that he was ready to begin. But now, Yoon Jong felt as if he was being sucked into that otherwise simple movement.

It was an absolutely perfect sword, with perfect speed and perfect form.

‘How could so much be shown with just that one move?’

Yoon Jong noticed.

This wasn’t something that was being shown to the opponent. It was meant for Mount Hua’s disciples. From now on, he would be using the Equilibrium of Six Sword, so he was asking them to pay attention.

“Don’t miss it.”

Yoon Jong shouted unconsciously.

“Don’t miss a single one of Chung Myung’s moves! Never! Don’t even blink; just watch him!”

No one replied. They all just nodded. They were all trying their best to capture Chung Myung’s movements.

“I’ll fix that troublemaking head of yours!”

Perhaps Yu Baek couldn’t understand how fearsome Chung Myung was, or maybe it was because of his opponent’s pressure, but Yu Baek burst into a scream as he rushed at Chung Myung.

Chung Myung’s eyes just looked at him coldly.

Equilibrium of Six.

This sword technique was the basis for all of Mount Hua’s swordsmanship.

Four cardinal directions brought together on earth and beneath heaven combine into six. It represents everything within the world as well as unity.

That was the essence of this simple and basic swordsmanship.

Stab! Cut! Slash! Block!

Nothing more than basic swordsmanship.

But in the end, every sword technique in the world begins with these movements. No sword can escape this rule.

The opponent’s sword danced gracefully in the sky.

“That!”

Hyun Jong’s eyes went wide as he noticed something strange.

That swordsmanship was reminiscent of a flower in full bloom. Doesn’t it seem familiar to something he’d heard about?

Did the Southern Edge Sect have such sword arts?

Aside from the beautiful appearance, the sharpness of the swordsmanship was apparent. Dozens of sword-like forms swept in for Chung Myung with bizarre petal-like movements.

However, Chung Myung’s eyes began to ice over and emit a deathly chill as he saw this technique.

Chung Myung merely took a single step forward, aiming for the top. At the same time, he thrust his sword ahead.

“Kuak!”

The change that was forming in the air disappeared like a ghost.

‘H-How?’

Chung Myung’s sword, which precisely struck and interrupted the flowing swordplay, hit Yu Baek’s wrist. Yu Baek retreated as he felt the heavy pain assail his senses.

But it was an obvious mistake.

Chung Myung took another step and swung his sword down.

Kak!

Chung Myung’s wooden sword, loaded with qi, collided with Yu Baek’s simple sword and echoed loudly with a dull sound. Somehow, he had managed to raise his sword in time to block. However, the weight of Chung Myung’s blow came crashing down upon his body.

“Kuak!”

Yu Baek eventually pushed the sword of Chung Myung away and stepped back.

However, with a cold and expressionless face, Chung Myung stepped closer and swung his sword.

There was no flashy movement. It wasn’t some sharp sword or weighted move.

It was a simple sword movement.

Stab! Cut! Slash! Block.

Yet, the child’s sword couldn’t be blocked. If it was blocked, the blade would fly again, and if it was pushed away, it would strike the chin.

‘W-what is this?’

Yu Baek blocked and blocked again, but each time Chung Myung’s sword was blocked, he would be pushed back several steps.

‘J-just once!’

He only needed one opportunity. Then, by inserting his sword into that gap, he could display his sect’s swordsmanship.

If he could unfold the Southern Edge Sect’s newest sword art, then this cheeky bastard could be defeated.

But…

“Ack!”

Unfortunately for him, Chung Myung’s sword struck before he could fully display the technique earlier.

His wrist seemed to have been broken as he screamed in agony. But with his pride on the line, he didn’t withdraw.

‘O-once!’

Just break through the child’s sword once…

But the sword of Chung Myung kept coming.

And the cost of not receiving Chung Myung’s sword properly was great. Chung Myung’s sword fell at a slow pace, it wasn’t quick, yet it destroyed Yu Baek’s flow.

‘W-what the hell is this?’

Realizing that he was being driven into a corner, Yu Baek looked at Chung Myung’s sword as if his soul had been drained from his body.

Stab.

Swing.

Yet, he couldn’t find a single gap between those movements.

Perfect. It was absolutely perfect.

Kang!

In the end, Yu Baek was unable to keep up with the change in movements, and his sword was deflected away. As his sword rose into the sky, Yu Baek stared at Chung Myung’s sword as it keenly slashed for his head.

“This must be a dream….”

Pang!

Chung Myung’s sword stopped right in front of his head. He didn’t hit, but that was enough. Unable to handle this strike, Yu Baek stumbled back.

“S-Sajae!”

“Sahyung!”

That was the end.

Staring at the Southern Edge disciples that gathered, Chung Myung simply continued to gaze at them from afar.

Those who received that look felt a chill run down their spine and took a step back.

Chung Myung spoke with the softest voice.

“Next.”

“…”

That was the moment when the Southern Edge Sect disciples desperately realized that something was wrong.

Chapter 106: Mount Hua will not disappear (1)

The world seemed to freeze as a chilling silence descended on Mount Hua.

No one could open their mouths, and no one thought to move.

Those who knew martial arts couldn’t speak because they understood just how incredible the spectacle before their eyes was. Even those who didn’t know martial arts recognized that something extraordinary had happened just now.

Sama Seung looked at Chung Myung with trembling eyes.

‘With just basic swordsmanship….’

He overpowered Yu Baek?

Without being hit a single time?

Those consecutive movements smoothly flowed together like water. Yu Baek, who was caught within, couldn’t counter.

‘Would it have been possible for me to do the same?’

Sama Seung couldn’t immediately answer the question that popped into his head.

Subduing Yu Baek in an instant was something Sama Seung could do. However, only using a basic sword technique to subdue an opponent without giving them a chance to counterattack was different.

Even if someone twice as strong as Sama Seung came, it couldn’t be guaranteed that he would perform at the level of Chung Myung.

It was a matter of how perfectly the basics were mastered and performed.

To put it crudely, a vast and robust root.

Not some colorful branches and stems. A firm root that supported everything but stayed invisible.

‘W-what the hell did he do?’

There was a deeper meaning to the fact that the roots were so massive.

That the child will grow into a giant tree; he will become a great tree that can cover all of Mount Hua!

At that moment, a cold voice penetrated Sama Seung’s mind.

“Next.”

Sama Seung’s eyes trembled as he looked at Chung Myung.

The cold eyes made one sink into the abyss, with his sword pointed to the Southern Edge Sect.

‘He must be stopped.’

This fight was fine. But if Chung Myung grows in the future, everyone will be covered under this child’s shadow one day.

Right.

It would be just like when the ‘Plum Blossom Sword Saint’ roamed about in the past.

“E-elder…”

“Ah…”

Only then did Sama Seung come to his senses, and after looking at his disciples, he clenched his teeth and thought.

‘Who should I send?’

It was then.

Jong Seo-Han growled and glared at Chung Myung.

“Elder! I will go! I will take him down and teach Mount Hua a lesson.”

“…”

One could only see as much as they knew. Chung Myung’s strength was unknown to the Southern Edge Sect disciples; Jong Seo-Han didn’t understand what he was facing.

‘What should I do?’

Sama Seung was a bit worried.

“Seo-Han.”

“Yes! Elder.”

“Don’t lose easily. Tire him out.”

“… what?”

“Do what you are told!”

Jong Seo-Han looked at the elder with a puzzled expression and nodded.

“I will do as the elder commands.”

“… go.”

“Yes!”

Jong Seo-Han grabbed his wooden sword and moved.

Jin Geum-Ryong, who was silent till them, spoke.

“Elder…”

“It might be difficult to say, but….”

Sama Seung turned his gaze to Jin Geum-Ryong. Seeing his face, Jin Geum-Ryong flinched and stepped away without realizing it.

It was cold.

A face that was so cold he could feel his bones chilling.

Sama Seung turned away his glare.

Jong Seo-Han took a deep breath.

‘I’m not being careless. I don’t underestimate my opponent, and I’m not overconfident.’

If he could do his best, the child would lose. If he was careless like Yu Baek, then horrible things could happen.

“I commend you for defeating Yu Baek. But I am—”

The words found themselves trapped within his throat.

His mouth which unable to speak and couldn’t move.

Silence.

Chung Myung, who was standing in front of him, seemed to slowly be melding into his surroundings. Jong Seo-Han began to feel an oppressive sinking feeling.

‘… this?’

He didn’t realize it while standing in the crowd.

However, Chung Myung’s aura was something he’d never faced before. Not even Jin Geum-Ryong or their teacher could give him this feeling.

He gulped at the thought as his muscles tensed.

His instincts were screaming that it was dangerous just by looking at Chung Myung in front of him.

Chung Myung’s half-hearted eyes calmly observed him.

At that moment, without realizing it, Jong Seo-Han took his stance. All the thoughts inside his head disappeared. It felt like only he and Chung Myung existed in this world.

At that moment.

Shhh!

Chung Myung took a slow step.

Although everyone could clearly see that it was a slow step, Chung Myung’s body reached Jong Seo-Han instantly.

He firmly exerted force on the ground through his legs.

The force of the recoil traveled through the waist, and the waist moved to give power to the upper body. As if absorbing that force, the sword swung ferociously.

Bang!

Nothing fancy.

Power, speed, accuracy. Just the basics.

The sword’s power that faithfully adhered to the basics ascended beyond the basics.

Jong Seo-Han’s legs trembled.

As Chung Myung advanced one step ahead, Jong Seo-Han’s posture crumpled, and he lost balance as his body twisted with a muffled sound.

‘Ah–no!’

And that was it.

Jong Seo-Han’s eyes saw the wooden sword falling toward his head.

‘Ah…’

There was fear and shock in his eyes.

‘Unbelievable…’

Kwang!

Jong Seo-Han fell to the floor, blood dripping.

This sword.

Just this sword.

The second greatest of Southern Edge’s second-class disciples, Jong Seo-Han, was defeated with a single strike to the head. Everyone witnessing this stood aghast in shock.

Receiving these shocked gazes, Chung Myung softly spoke.

“Next.”

He just silently looked at the Southern Edge Sect.

Now, the Southern Edge Sect seemed to finally understand. Their faces went stiff as if they had seen a ghost.

‘Not yet.’

It was too early to be surprised. Because Chung Myung still had more to show.

He had no intention of being content with just this.

Considering what the Southern Edge sect did to Mount Hua, such a defeat was nothing but a light punishment.

Today, here, Chung Myung would leave an indelible mark on the Southern Edge Sect.

As long as Mount Hua survives in this world and as long as the Southern Edge Sect exists. This day will remain a stigma in their sect’s history.

‘You did something you shouldn’t have done.’

Mount Hua gave everything to save the world. Despite Chung Myung’s dissuasion, his Sahyungs all gave up their lives for the sake of the world.

And what was the cost?

‘Shit.’

The anger that had been suppressed turned into a cold flame that burned in Chung Myung’s chest.

‘In the world we protected, the Southern Edge Sect was there.’

Instead of repaying the favor, the Southern Edge Sect stole the Plum Blossom Sword technique and despised Mount Hua. Now, they were even trying to destroy it.

‘Well, everyone endured it till now.’

Chung Myung kept control of himself. Several times a day, he felt his broken heart ache. Finally, he didn’t need to hold back the anger he’d been suppressing anymore.

“Next!”

When Chung Myung sharply shouted, the disciples of the Southern Edge Sect shuddered. A few came forward and carried Jong Seo-Han away.

One of them remained with a stiff face and stood facing Chung Myung with a sword.

‘I’ve already shown off the Equilibrium of Six, then let’s move on to the next technique.’

Chung Myung retook his stance.

A groan that seemed to breathe in sounded from behind him.

“F-Falling Flower Sword!”

After taking the basic form, Chung Myung raised his sword and aimed it at the foe in front of him.

And sprinted ahead.

‘It’s different!’

Jo Gul clenched his fist.

Chung Myung’s movements changed completely. They weren’t serious and concise like what had been previously shown. These were sharp movements, like wind blowing through a canyon.

Just by changing the sword technique, his entire bearing changed. How could one man have such perfect execution?

Flowers blooming on an old tree along the cliff seem to be swept away by this violent wind.

Swish!

A completely incomparable speed to Chung Myung’s previous technique was displayed.

Such a formidable attack went flying towards the disciple from the Southern Edge Sect.

“Kuak!”

Kang!

The moment it seemed to be blocked, the sword was recovered faster than it stabbed and then continued the assault again and again.

‘What!’

Kwakwang!

The sword that was blocked quickly retreated back.

Usually, when dealing with a swift sword, a martial artist would strike after defending before their opponent has time to recover their stance and withdraw their sword. That was the trick. However, the Southern Edge Sect’s disciple had no way to counterattack despite knowing that.

The moment he tried to attack, Chung Myung’s retrieved sword would stab again.

“Ack!”

Faster.

Puak!

Even faster!

Pak!

Sometimes the sword would just brush past the shoulder. But even so, that light contact felt like it had enough destructive force to crush the bones.

“Accckkkk!”

The Southern Edge Sect’s disciple couldn’t find a proper way to deal with the attack and recklessly decided to swing his sword.

No, he tried to.

Puak!

Chung Myung’s sword struck his throat before he could even place strength in his hand.

“Grrr!”

The disciple collapsed on the spot.

Thud!

Chung Myung looked at the fallen disciple and said,

“Next.”

Yoon Jong seemed deflated as he gasped.

‘T-that is the Falling Flower Sword.’

Different.

It was different from what he or Jo Gul did.

If the Equilibrium of Six was loyal to the basics, then this sword technique centered on pleasure and was the core of Mount Hua’s swordsmanship.

Chung Myung was now showing them.

This is the true Falling Flower Sword. This is Mount Hua’s sword.

“… Falling Flower Sword.”

The sword they learned.

To be honest, Yoon Jong never thought that Mount Hua’s sword technique could be as good as the Southern Edge Sect’s.

Even though swordsmanship wasn’t everything, Mount Hua’s martial arts tended to fall a bit short if it was evaluated calmly.

So far, Yoon Jong… no, that was what all the third-class disciples thought.

But instead of using a hundred words, Chung Myung showed them through a single battle.

It’s been said that Mount Hua’s martial arts used to be superior to the Southern Edge Sect. That may be the reason that Chung Myung was fighting them with those techniques.

“… what have I even been looking at till now?”

The children that had envied the abilities of others without properly understanding their own techniques felt ashamed of themselves.

“Sahyung. The Falling Flower Sword…”

“Right.”

Yoon Jong knew what Jo Gul was trying to say.

Yoon Jong nodded his head and spoke.

“Don’t take your eyes off him. That is Mount Hua’s Sword. The sword of Mount Hua that we need to learn and pass on.”

Yoon Jong realized one thing.

Perhaps after today, the disciples of Mount Hua will no longer be the same. Once they have witnessed this absurd sight, they can never turn back.

The image of Chung Myung’s back, wielding his sword, was burned into their eyes.

That bastard who always ran his arrogant mouth, at this moment, was silently leading them with his back.

‘Show us more.’

What Mount Hua’s sword meant.

How strong Mount Hua’s sword can be.

The world was getting quieter and quieter.

In the eyes of Yoon Jong, the figure of Chung Myung grew larger. It appeared as if Chung Myung was the only one standing in the whole world.

Chapter 107: Mount Hua will not disappear (2)

Thud!

Another one fell.

The blood drained from the faces of the Southern Edge Sect’s disciples as they stood in shock.

Six.

Six had fallen.

A total of six!

Six second-class disciples from the Southern Edge Sect had been defeated by a single third-class disciple. It was an utterly one-sided defeat as well.

But it wasn’t the current losses that left them terrified.

What truly scared them was the creeping realization that they may not be able to secure even a single victory in this match.

‘Will we be completely annihilated? By just one third-class disciple?’

Their fingers turned numb, and a cold sweat ran down their spine. Their eyes clouded over in despair, and their legs lost strength.

Was there anyone here that didn’t understand how disgraceful this was?

This event was one in a thousand; if such news leaked, it would travel the world before the disciples could even return home.

For Mount Hua, this would be a glorious achievement.

And for the Southern Edge sect, this would be a humiliation that would last for generations!

That historically absurd disgrace was occurring right here and now on Mount Hua. Realizing that, the Southern Edge Sect disciples felt a sense of fear that went beyond this moment’s pressure.

“Next!”

In their ears echoed the most terrifyingly heartless voice.

No one stepped forward. They weren’t stupid. If it happened once or twice, it could be considered luck. But winning six times in a row was no coincidence.

It was unbelievable, but Mount Hua’s third-class disciple, Chung Myung, was stronger than them.

Overwhelmingly.

They were no longer afraid of stepping forward and losing. However, the burden of being one of the disciples that contributed to this catastrophic defeat was terrifying beyond measure.

“S-Someone go.”

“I-I can’t….”

“-Sahyung. Shouldn’t Sahyung go?”

“What am I supposed to do? I…”

It was at that moment.

“Pathetic.”

Jin Geum-Ryong spoke in a cold voice.

“The disciples of the Great Southern Edge Sect are afraid of a child that’s ten years younger than them? You all seem to have forgotten about shame.”

Everyone was unable to respond and merely bowed their heads.

Jin Geum-Ryon took a step forward.

“I will go.”

“S-Sahyung!”

“I cannot watch that arrogant bastard any longer. So, watch me as I regain the sect’s honor! Although, I don’t know if there is any honor left to reclaim.”

Jin Geum-Ryong’s face twisted like a ravenous demon, but someone spoke just as he was about to walk out.

“Stop.”

“…”

Jin Geum-Ryong turned to see that Sama Seung was looking at him with a stiff face as he called on someone else.

“Man Jeok.”

“… Yes, elder.”

“You go.”

“… I, I…”

Sama Seung cut the disciple’s words off as if to pre-empt and nip any excuses in the bud.

“Go out there and drag him down by the ankles. Do you understand what I mean?”

“… Yes.”

Jin Geum-Ryong tried to disagree, but Sama Seung stopped him.

“Come here.”

“But the fight is—”

“That’s enough. Come here!”

Sama Seung led Jin Geum-Ryong to the back. After reaching an isolated place where no one could hear them, Sama Seung spoke in a low voice.

“Do you think the other kids can win?”

Jin Geum-Ryong couldn’t answer.

It was a question with an obvious answer. However, the reason he couldn’t respond wasn’t that he felt sorry for his juniors. It was because he couldn’t understand the reality of what was happening.

Nothing was lacking about the second-class disciples’ skills, yet they lacked confidence despite their efforts.

They no longer had any chance against Chung Myung with such a mindset.

Sama Seung spoke bluntly to the confused Jin Geum-Ryong.

“Your thoughts aren’t wrong.”

“… Yes?”

“That’s a monster. No, I would call him a monster cub. But if you leave him alone, he will become a real monster one day.”

“… Elder?”

“And that monster will block the Southern Edge Sect’s path again. Do you understand what I mean?”

Jin Geum-Ryong’s eyes went wide.

‘Is that possible?’

Jin Geum-Ryong had to admit that Chung Myung is incredibly strong for his age. But could he really become a hindrance to their sect?

Jin Geum-Ryong bit his lip in frustration.

Saying that Chung Myung would block the sect’s path was the same as saying that Jin Geum-Ryong would be unable to handle him. Whether it’s true or not, at least Sama Seung thought so.

His blood boiled inside.

‘Does that mean I can barely handle that child?’

This was an insult he’d never heard before.

Jin Geum-Ryong’s expression revealed the anger that he couldn’t hide.

Sama Seung looked deeply into his eyes and spoke.

“Geum-Ryong, you are a genius.”

“…”

“But how many people do you think get called geniuses? It’s not something I want to say, but there are at least ten men of your caliber in your generation alone. Maybe it’s even more than that.”

Jin Geum-Ryong tightly clenched his teeth.

Sama Seung coldly asked.

“Do you believe that you can be the strongest in the world in the future?”

Jin Geum-Ryong may be the most confident person in the world, but even he didn’t dare to lightly answer that question.

The title of ‘strongest in the world’ held too much weight.

When Jin Geum-Ryong hesitated to answer, Sama Seung narrowed his eyes.

“Master. Genius. This title may be enough to carry on the spirit of the Southern Edge Sect and lead our sect into a golden era. However!”

Sama Seung finally arrived at the main point he really wanted to say.

“Being the best in the world is impossible.”

“…”

“Those who compete for the position of strongest in the world are monsters, not geniuses. Only those who casually ignore common sense, crush down the laws with their power, and defy all reason with their talents can stand on that stage. Right…”

Sama Seung’s head slowly turned towards the center.

“Monsters like him.”

Jin Geum-Ryong’s shoulders trembled.

“Elder, I…!”

Jin Geum-Ryong was about to cry out and protest when he was suppressed by the elder’s cold voice.

“But.”

It became difficult to breathe.

“He may be a monster, but he is still just a cub. Even a dog can bite a tiger to death if it’s just a baby.”

Jin Geum-Ryong understood the meaning behind Sama Seung’s words and stared at him in shock. As if to affirm Jin Geum-Ryong’s startling thoughts, a quiet and eerie voice penetrated his ears.

“Kill him.”

“E-Elder.”

Sama Seung whispered with a ghastly visage.

“It’s still possible. He is a monster, but he can be dealt with now. You must kill him. If you don’t kill him now, we will never get another chance in this lifetime.”

“…”

“Don’t forget. People with talent don’t become the best. Among those called geniuses and prodigies, only one person can truly stand at the peak. Do it now! If you can’t kill him, at least cut off his arm!”

Jin Geum-Ryong unknowingly stepped back.

‘He’s lost his mind.’

It wasn’t because of what was said, but a certain sense of madness was glowing in his eyes. Whatever it was, it didn’t seem normal.

“Elder, think rationally….”

“Rational?”

Sama Seung burst into laughter before grinding his teeth.

“Are you going to live in his shadow for the rest of your life?”

Jin Geum-Ryong shut his mouth.

Under the shadow? …Of that child?

Jin Geum-Ryong clenched his fist. His nails digging into the palm of his hand nearly punctured the flesh.

It was such a humiliating thought that he couldn’t bear it.

“The choice is yours.”

Sama Seung said while growling.

“You don’t need to take all the responsibility for this. You just made a mistake. Mistakes are common in spars like this. Don’t you think so?”

Jin Geum-Ryong looked at Sama Seung with fire raging within his eyes and spoke.

“First of all, let me be clear. I am not someone who can be overshadowed by a child like him.”

Despite those bold words, Sama Seung waited for Jin Geum-Ryong to continue.

“But.”

He continued with a cold face.

“If that child’s existence will become an obstacle for the Southern Edge Sect, then there’s no reason to follow the rules.”

A sinister smile blossomed on Sama Seung’s lips.

“That’s right.”

Thud!

Another disciple fell.

With this, eight have fallen to Chung Myung.

Chung Myung lowered his sword and looked at the Southern Edge Sect.

There were only two left, and he arrogantly stared at his remaining foes.

‘Not yet.’

It is too early for despair. There was something else Chung Myung had prepared.

“It doesn’t look like I’m getting to ten wins so easily.”

Of course, Jin Geum-Ryong would appear in the end, but it’s difficult for them to find someone to fill the final role. Who was going to come forward when they were all terrified?

‘It’s unfortunate. Do I need to be content with my current win record?’

It was then.

Step.

A man steadily walked out without saying a word. Chung Myung seemed shocked upon seeing who it was that approached the stage.

“Why?”

The person approaching smiled modestly.

“I know it’s too early for me to compete with you. But… our sect is suffering a great humiliation, so I can’t just sit on the sidelines and watch from behind.”

“Hmm.”

Chung Myung nodded his head.

This guy was surely worth it.

Lee Song-Baek.

Lee Song-Baek, who he had already met at the Eunha Guild, came to face Chung Myung.

“The Southern Edge Sect’s Lee Song Baek, a second-class disciple, asks disciple Chung Myung for a match.”

“Mount Hua’s third-class disciple Chung Myung accepts.”

The two stood facing one another with swords drawn.

‘What do I do?’

Chung Myung looked at Lee Song-Baek. Even though he was from the Southern Edge Sect, Chung Myung didn’t hate him. But…

Chung Myung lowered his sword after much consideration and gently closed his eyes.

‘It wouldn’t hurt to show him.’

If he could accept and overcome it, then it would be medicinal. If he cannot overcome this, it will become poison. It would all depend on Lee Song-Baek.

“Taaaah!”

Lee Song-Baek screamed as he charged.

Chung Myung’s sword also began to move slowly.

Lee Song-Baek was someone that would grow by using the old methods of the Southern Edge Sect. The current Chung Myung could show him where to begin, but…

A little should be enough for Lee Song-Baek.

The tip of Chung Myung’s sword was aimed precisely at Lee Song-Baek.

And at that moment.

Lee Song-Baek, who was running towards Chung Myung, opened his eyes wide.

‘The s-sword!’

Chung Myung’s entire body was covered by the sword. No, the sword that stabbed toward Lee Song-Baek grew so large that it obscured his view of Chung Myung.

‘N-No, that’s not it either!’

Not visible.

Not being able to feel it.

The only thing he could see and feel was the sword aimed at him.

‘Is that True Unity with the Sword?’

A huge shock swept through Lee Song-Baek’s body before he could fully comprehend what was happening.

Thud!

As blood dripped down, Lee Song-Baek stepped back and subtly smiled.

‘I saw…’

Thud!

Lee Song-Baek fell to the floor.

Nine consecutive losses.

Now there was only one left.

Chung Myung turned to look at the Southern Edge Sect’s disciples. No, his gaze was aimed at just one person.

“Come out.”

Jin Geum-Ryong.

It’s finally time to pay for your sins, Southern Edge Sect.

Chapter 108: Mount Hua will not disappear (3)

The sound of wind escaped from Hyun Jong’s mouth. Still, he didn’t risk turning his eyes away from the center for even a moment.

Hyun Jong’s gaze moved from Lee Song-Baek to Chung Myung.

Another win.

After winning nine times, Chung Myung was waiting for his final opponent.

The elders and disciples that gathered together were watching in suffocating silence. No one wanted to disturb this atmosphere by speaking first.

Doubts about Chung Myung?

Doubts about the situation?

Those were probably valid concerns to consider. But they could find out later.

What was important now was that Chung Myung was on the verge of achieving a full victory over the Southern Edge Sect.

‘Has this ever happened in the history of Mount Hua?’

Mount Hua and the Southern Edge sect have always been wary of each other. Looking at it objectively, Mount Hua often stood ahead of the Southern Edge Sect throughout history.

Of course, the tide had turned in recent generations. But looking at both sect’s histories, it was undeniable.

Yet, as far as Hyun Jong knew, there was never a situation in Mount Hua’s history where they crushed the Southern Edge Sect so one-sidedly.

Of course, there were legends that the Southern Edge Sect couldn’t even step outside during the Plum Blossom Sword Saint’s era, but that was a different matter. There had never been an ‘official’ incident like this.

At Mount Hua’s darkest hour, an unprecedented event was unraveling before their eyes in this time of hardship. They were unable to focus on anything else.

Hyun Jong looked at Chung Myung, who was staring at the other sect.

Confident.

Hyun Jong was more impressed by that dignified attitude than the victories he achieved.

Just when was it?

‘When was the last time that a member of Mount Hua could proudly stand against the Southern Edge Sect?’

Was it ever possible for them to stand tall?

‘Oh, my ancestors.’

Hyun Jong’s eyes kept watering. As Mount Hua’s sect leader, he knew that he needed to remain calm and shouldn’t show such emotions; however, the passion rising from his heart was overwhelming.

“Sect leader…”

“Don’t say anything….”

Hyun Jong shook his head at Hyun Sang’s call.

“For now, let’s wait and see. What more he can show to us.”

Everyone held their breath and focused on Chung Myung’s every move.

‘Maybe today…’

A hopeful light that had never been seen before emerged in Hyun Jong’s eyes.

‘Maybe the fate of Mount Hua will change.’

Strange.

The gazes that pierced him.

The feeling of his toes touching the floor.

The wooden sword in his hand.

All of that was different from usual.

Jin Geum-Ryong stepped on stage feeling a burden that was unfamiliar to him.

‘Strange.’

Jin Geum-Ryong felt it.

This wasn’t the sort of gaze that normally poured onto him. Jin Geum-Ryong had already received looks of anticipation and excitement.

Right.

He was a valiant martial artist that carried the future of the sect. Those who saw him always looked at him with pride and expectation. This was the first time he’d received such looks of anxiety and concern.

‘Why?’

‘Why are they looking at me like that?’

Jin Geum-Ryong raised his head and saw the figure of Chung Myung looking back at him.

‘Right. Because of him.’

It was incomprehensible. But something was raging inside him.

Jin Geum-Ryong worked hard all his life to get to where he stood now.

He strove to have his potential recognized and consistently lived up to the extraordinary expectations of those around him. Naturally, he began to be praised for his efforts. He was a man that might someday become the sect leader of the Southern Edge Sect.

It was the recognition and expectation he earned throughout his life.

But in less than an hour, it all turned into concern and worry.

‘Am I that unreliable?’

To the extent that they were worried he couldn’t handle a single child from a fallen sect?

A wave of cold and heavy anger swept through Jin Geum-Ryong’s body. He stared intently into Chung Myung’s eyes.

‘I didn’t like him from the start.’

That arrogant face, the pretentious attitude, and the sharpness of his gaze.

Above all else, Jin Geum-Ryong despised how arrogantly he behaved. Even when Chung Myung was face to face with Jin Geum-Ryong, it felt as though he was looking down on the Southern Edge Sect.

Jin Geum-Ryong took a deep breath and began to speak with an emotionless voice.

“Should I give you a compliment?”

“I don’t need that.”

Chung Myung shrugged his shoulders.

“It’s not like I did anything great.”

“…”

Jin Geum-Ryong looked at the child with cold eyes.

“You dare ignore the Southern Edge sect?”

“Ignore.”

Chung Myung chuckled.

“It isn’t a matter of ignoring you. There’s no reason to be proud of bullying the weak.”

Annoying.

Every single word.

“You…”

Jin Geum-Ryong stopped himself as he was about to speak before sighing and shaking his head.

“No. You don’t need to be humble. Your skills are enough; any humility from you will upset me.”

“Hmm?”

“I admit it. Your strength has earned you the right to be arrogant. Just the fact that you defeated nine of us is shocking. You will be recognized as a once-in-a-lifetime genius.”

Chung Myung narrowed his eyes.

Shhh!

Jin Geum-Ryong drew his wooden sword and aimed it at Chung Myung.

“Do you know what your misfortune is?”

“Well?”

“You were born during the same time as me.”

Chung Myung had a subtle smile while Jin Geum-Ryong stared at him and continued.

“As a result of that misfortune, you will always stare at my back. Unable to overcome the difference between us, you’ll chase after my shadow for the rest of your life.”

Chung Myung grinned widely.

“It’s good to be so confident.”

“I’m not done yet.”

Jin Geum-Ryong spoke coldly.

“If you hadn’t chosen Mount Hua, you might have been able to overcome your misfortune. If you chose the Southern Edge Sect instead of Mount Hua, you might have had the opportunity to surpass me.”

“Really? You think so?”

“I do.”

Jin Geum-Ryong cleared his breath and continued.

“Mount Hua is still tied down by the past. Its disciples desperately struggle to recover their lost martial arts and recreate their former glory. But not the Southern Edge Sect. Without lingering on ancient history, we invent a new system and achieve a better future.”

Jin Geum-Ryong spoke as if making a declaration.

“That’s why Mount Hua will never be able to catch up with the Southern Edge Sect.”

“Kua.”

Chung Myung exclaimed in admiration.

He wanted to clap too. If someone other than the Southern Edge Sect said it, he might have slapped his Sahyungs on the back of their heads.

‘Look at them and learn something, you bastards!’

Chung Myung may have shouted that.

Unfortunately, the future that Jin Geum-Ryong was talking about was achieved by stealing Mount Hua’s martial arts.

‘What should I do?’

Two things were necessary to bring the truth to light. The first was acknowledging the truth, and the second was having the power to carry through with that announcement.

When the Southern Edge Sect began to study the martial arts they stole from Mount Hua, Chung Myung was so furious that he was worried he would go insane.

But does anger change anything?

Realistically there was no way Mount Hua could punish the Southern Edge Sect.

If the issue was brought to the public, there would only be an outcry of voices demanding that they prove the Southern Edge Sect was actually learning the Plum Blossom Sword technique. Even if Mount Hua restored and displayed the true technique, the Southern Edge Sect would claim that they had been the ones that had their techniques copied and stolen.

The weak Mount Hua had no choice but to suffer.

Why?

They simply didn’t have enough power.

Martial arts are a sensitive subject. Those who leak their sect’s techniques would pay with their lives, and those who steal them from others should be prepared for an all-out war.

But Mount Hua cannot punish the Southern Edge Sect. The moment they raise the issue, the Southern Edge Sect will wage war on Mount Hua, and no one in the world could help them then.

No one would risk their lives to defend a collapsing sect.

So, Chung Myung stayed patient.

Until this moment!

He suppressed his boiling anger and endured his urge to charge into the Southern Edge Sect and slaughter them all.

For this moment alone.

A gruesome smile spread across his face.

“The future of the Southern Edge Sect. That is a good thing to say.”

Chung Myung smiled at Jin Geum-Ryong.

Right. Chung Myung also thought about the Southern Edge Sect’s future a lot.

What to do with their future?

Chung Myung left one seed in the Southern Edge Sect a little while ago. It was unknown if the seed would grow or not, but it served its purpose.

So, he would no longer act as a third-class disciple from Mount Hua from this moment on.

He would be acting as Chung Myung, the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, to those filthy people who ripped them off after they showed grace.

“That future…”

Chung Myung raised his sword.

“I’ll present it to you as a gift.”

“Right. It’ll be a gift that you will never forget for the rest of your life, so you’d better keep your eyes open.”

Jin Geum-Ryong looked at him, unable to understand. But Chung Myung smiled.

‘The perfect gift.’

Like a curse.

Restoring Mount Hua and destroying the current Southern Edge Sect wouldn’t be enough to relieve Chung Myung’s anger.

He was about to cut off the Southern Edge Sect’s future forever.

‘You covet the sword of Mount Hua?’

Chung Myung smiled and laughed like a wolf facing his prey.

“Then receive it properly.”

‘I will show it to you, so don’t forget it.’

Chung Myung tightly grasped his sword.

“Get away!”

“Sasuk!”

“Baek Cheon Sahyung!”

Mount Hua’s disciples couldn’t breathe as they looked at the center of the arena but were startled when a voice came from behind.

Baek Cheon staggered his way inside.

“S-Sahyung! Are you alright?”

Listening to the questions pouring in, Baek Cheon simply waved his hand and walked ahead.

Seeing this, Baek Sang shouted.

“Ch-Chair! Get a chair!”

“Yes, Sasuk!”

One of the third-class disciples hurriedly brought a chair for Baek Cheon. However, Baek Cheon only stared at Chung Myung and Jin Geum-Ryong without even looking at the chair.

‘I need to see this.’

As soon as he opened his eyes, he heard that Chung Myung had nine straight wins.

It was impossible for him to remain lying down after hearing that. Even if his body was shattered, he needed to be there to cheer for Chung Myung.

Jin Geum-Ryong.

And Chung Myung.

Two people that held a special meaning to him were facing one another.

‘Win. Chung Myung!’

Baek Cheon’s earnest eyes shone with a desperate light.

Swish!

Swish!

Both Chung Myung and Jin Geum-Ryong’s swords began to move with a low sound.

Whatever the outcome may be, the results of this battle would ring throughout the land and echo across the world.

Mount Hua’s disciples opened their eyes wide. They refused to miss even a single moment of this historic battle.

Chapter 109: Mount Hua will not disappear (4)

“Elder, will Sahyung win?”

Seeing the elder tightly biting his lips, the disciple asked cautiously. Sama Seung parted his lips to answer as a stream of blood trickled down his chin.

“Will he win?”

It was an absurd question.

“He has to win, no matter what.”

If that monster’s wings aren’t broken today, then he would continue to soar further into the sky.

Once that monster ascends, no one will ever be able to catch up. From that moment on, that monster would become a dragon.

This might be the last chance.

It might be the worst-case scenario, but Sama Seung hadn’t given up hope.

‘It’ll be possible for Jin Geum-Ryong.’

Although he was also a second-class disciple, Sama Seung had faith in him. Jin Geum-Ryong’s abilities stood far above the others. Although Sama Seung had spoken harshly to him, he firmly believed that Jin Geum-Ryong could stand among the best in the world with enough luck.

In other words?

If Jin Geum-Ryong cannot defeat that child, then no one in this world within that age range will be able to stop Chung Myung. In other words, if Chung Myung defeats Jin Geum-Ryong today, then Chung Myung will naturally take his place as the strongest in his generation.

That outcome was unacceptable.

‘We should have stopped him sooner.’

Even if they had been criticized, Mount Hua should have been exterminated before it came to this. This was the result of them not destroying Mount Hua properly.

‘Damn those Mount Hua bastards!’

Sama Seung glared at them.

He could not allow history to remember this day as the Southern Edge Sect’s disgrace.

Never!

At that moment, Jin Geum-Ryong’s sword began to bloom like a fantasy. Sama Seung clenched his fists as he watched the Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword technique unfold perfectly.

‘This sword will take your breath away!’

Chung Myung looked at the sword.

‘Similar.’

The movement was copied really well.

The splendor.

The beauty of a single flower, as if it was alive and breathing. And a keen, fatal blow hidden behind the beauty.

Truly, the Twenty-Four Movement Plum Blossom Sword technique.

It is different from what Lee Song-Baek performed. If Lee Song-Baek’s sword was merely an imitation of Mount Hua’s technique, then Jin Geum-Ryong’s sword had an elegance that even Chung Myung might admire.

Anyone bearing witness to such a fantastic sword would end up praising it.

But

The person in front of Jin Geum-Ryong was Chung Myung.

And he avoided the sword.

Swish!

Jin Geum-Ryong’s sword cut the hem of Chung Myung’s robe.

Swish!

The tip of his hair was also cut.

Swish!

Soon, it brushed past Chung Myung’s cheek. A red line appeared, and a drop of blood trickled down.

Chung Myung easily stepped back and raised a finger to wipe away the flowing blood before licking his finger. Bittersweet.

“You won’t be able to defeat me by running away like that.”

Hearing Jin Geum-Ryong’s provocation, Chung Myung simply looked back at him in silence.

Jin Geum-Ryong’s eyes revealed a sense of peace, and he appeared relaxed.

“Once upon a time, Mount Hua made a name for itself with a sword resembling a flower, right?”

“…”

“But that’s a story of the past. Now even those legends will be buried beneath the Southern Edge Sect’s new sword. The world will remember the tales of my sect and forget the sword of Mount Hua.”

Chung Myung quietly listened without responding.

“The ancestors of my sect created this technique to show the world that the Southern Edge Sect’s swordsmanship will always be superior to Mount Hua’s. I honestly believe that it was a meaningless act. What’s the point in proving our superiority over a dying sect? However!”

Jin Geum-Ryong spoke in a cold voice.

“There is meaning in this sword technique being the one that severs the last breath from Mount Hua. Come! I will end this dying legacy!”

Arrogant words, but it was a poignant talk.

However, Chung Myung’s reaction to this was different from what Jin Geum-Ryong expected.

“Pffft.”

“…?”

Chung Myung covered his mouth and then began to lose himself in laughter.

“… what are you doing?”

Chung Myung, who struggled to hold back his laughter, shook his hand with his head down.

“No. No. I am trying, but I just can’t hold it back anymore.”

Chung Myung smiled, revealed his teeth, and raised his sword at Jin Geum-Ryong.

“I enjoyed the show. That act… well, it is more like a clown.”

“Clown?”

“Right. I enjoyed that clumsy impersonation. Even I can do it if it’s only at that level.”

Jin Geum-Ryong’s face was distorted. He gnashed his teeth, and his forehead crumpled.

“How dare you… compare my sword to a mimicry?”

“Ah, don’t get me wrong. It isn’t like I am looking down on you. Rather, it’s the sword technique or… perhaps, it’s the Southern Edge Sect, who invented the technique, that I’m looking down on?”

Jin Geum-Ryong glared at Chung Myung. Yet, Chung Myung didn’t back down.

“You don’t need to glare at me like that. I am going to give you a gift. I’ll fill the void in that sword technique.’

“… it would be better for you to think about how you can escape with your body intact.”

“I don’t think that’s something that a person who could barely touch their opponent should say.”

Jin Geum-Ryong flinched.

The Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword technique. The opponent shouldn’t be able to distinguish between genuine strikes and illusory falsehoods. So, wouldn’t it be impossible for Chung Myung to avoid it?

Jin Geum-Ryong’s knuckles turned white as he clenched his sword.

Chung Myung wouldn’t be able to survive once this technique was displayed, and Mount Hua wouldn’t dare to ask Jin Geum-Ryong to pay for his actions either. If they pressed charges, they would have to deal with the entire Southern Edge Sect.

In the end, the strong dominate the weak.

The weak may complain about injustice, but they can never punish the strong. An absolute law that can never be changed.

“You…”

However, Chung Myung brutally interrupted Jin Geum-Ryong.

“I will ask you one thing.”

It was an unfamiliar tone.

“Just what is that sword?”

“… what do you mean?”

“No, don’t bother. That’s enough.”

Chung Myung shook his head.

It meant that he meant nothing.

Chung Myung suppressed his true intention and spoke with a smirk in a voice loud enough for everyone to hear.

“That’s a pretty good imitation, but it won’t be enough. Mount Hua’s sword is faster, sharper, and more dazzling.”

Everyone certainly heard that declaration.

With this…

The Southern Edge Sect would be unable to escape from the curse.

“Even now, you’ve got a big mouth.”

“If you find a way to kill my mouth, let me know. Anyway, you’re the one that’s been doing all the talking for a while.”

“You…”

Jin Geum-Ryong moved his sword, deciding not to exchange words anymore. He was going to fight it out and not talk.

One win.

Just one win.

His sword was splendid and swiftly traversed through the air. The qi emanating from the sword began to form vivid flower patterns.

One win.

And another win in a different aspect.

Soon, the flowers created by Jin Geum-Ryong began to cover the area.

As beautiful as can be, yet equally as dangerous.

‘You will die by this sword!’

Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword technique.

Jin Geum-Ryong displayed the perfect version of this technique, the Snow Flower Full Heaven.

The flower that dyed the world in white began to wrap around Chung Myung as if wanting to tear his body to shreds.

“C-Chung Myung!”

Screams erupted from all around.

The disciples of Mount Hua, who were silently watching as if possessed, jumped up from their seats at once.

They knew.

How dangerous that sword could be.

They didn’t have to be there to know. Just looking at it from afar was enough to make goosebumps rise and their hearts skip a beat.

Chung Myung, whose strength always instilled confidence and faith in them, suddenly seemed to have fallen into a dangerous situation where his survival was uncertain.

Yoon Jong clasped his hands in front of his chest without realizing it.

‘Heavenly God!’

Jin Geum-Ryong’s sword was so fierce that they worried for the safety of the monster-like Chung Myung. It seemed like no one could survive in that storm of snow flowers.

Even Baek Cheon was screaming for Chung Myung.

But just one.

Yu Yiseol, bit her lip as she looked at the scene without much agitation. However, a single question crossed her mind.

‘That’s…?’

A sight she had seen before. Perhaps it was something familiar too? Something she’d seen recently, but…

‘Different.’

Something felt different.

This sword wasn’t too different from what she knew. However, it didn’t give that same feeling of her soul being sucked in, like Chung Myung’s sword.

What was different?

Yu Yiseol turned her sights on Chung Myung.

He would be the one to tell them what was different.

Chung Myung had a subtle expression as he looked at the waves of flowers around.

‘This is another kind of experience.’

It was different from when he was with his Sahyungs. It was rare to feel true killing intent from his Sahyungs.

‘This must be how those demonic bastards felt when they faced the Twenty-Four Movement Plum Blossom Sword technique.’

Maybe a little different.

Chung Myung felt no threat, no pressure at all, from this technique.

Why?

‘This is just a shell.’

Exactly, the shell of a failed sword.

A technique begins with an idea, then a vision for how it would be displayed. Once the vision is formed, it must be granted substance. A sword that’s given substance can be taught and learned. A sword that goes further than that can finally be called one with the Tao.

But this sword was empty.

The idea and vision form the shell of the sword, but there was no substance or deeper meaning. It could never be a true sword technique.

This sword was nothing but a copy of Mount Hua’s sword. A shell with no opportunity for growth.

This all happened because of a long-time misunderstanding.

‘The Plum Blossom Sword technique makes flowers bloom?’

That is wrong in two ways.

One.

Chung Myung began to move his sword slowly. The disciples of Mount Hua recognized it right away.

‘The Seven Sages Sword?’

The disciples all knew that this technique was recently brought back to the sect. But it seemed like a weak choice against the Southern Edge Sect’s technique.

At that time, Chung Myung mumbled to himself.

“It isn’t the Plum Blossom Sword technique that makes the flowers bloom.”

Flowers don’t just bloom in dense forests.

Even a single plum tree on a cliff can make flowers bloom.

Whether it was the Plum Blossom or the Seven Sages Sword technique, it wasn’t the technique that made the flowers bloom but the disciple who held the sword.

That…

Made a faint flower bloom at the tip of Chung Myung’s sword.

A single red flower bloomed amidst the myriad flowers that colored the world white.

It looked like a single Plum Blossom on a snowy mountain.

Snow Plum blossoms bloom alone in the winter when the flowers turn dry and give off a stronger fragrance than others.

Chung Myung’s single plum blossom gradually multiplied and soon covered the white world with red plum blossoms, like snow plums blossoming on a snow-capped Mount Hua.

Everyone witnessing this event was mesmerized.

It was too beautiful to be swordsmanship and too majestic to be a man-made scene.

‘This is fantasy.’

Time stopped.

In that frozen time, only the plum blossoms that bloomed at that moment continued to release a scent so strong that they captivated the audience’s senses.

Chapter 110: Mount Hua will not disappear (5)

‘This…’

Jin Geum-Ryong saw the tinge of red blooming within the white world he’d created.

A feeble light.

Like a drop of blood that fell on a pure white snowfield, it was nothing more than a tiny dot that seemed fragile yet radiantly shone red.

The red dot soon vividly took on the form of a plum blossom.

One blossom, then another. In an instant, plum blossoms began to blend into Jin Geum-Ryong’s technique.

And burned it away.

Just as snow melts in the blazing spring sun, the remnants of Jin Geum-Ryong’s technique melted away wherever the red plum blossoms bloomed.

‘Plum blossoms?’

It was said that Mount Hua could no longer make plum blossoms bloom. That was why everyone assumed that Mount Hua would be unable to revive again.

The plum blossom is the symbol of Mount Hua, no matter what anyone says. If Mount Hua cannot make the plum blossoms bloom, they could never recapture their former glory.

But at this moment, the plum blossoms that had vanished from Mount Hua’s history had begun to bloom again.

Even more vividly and colorful.

“Eik!”

Jin Geum-Ryong couldn’t believe it.

He didn’t doubt that Chung Myung’s sword could give rise to the plum blossoms.

That wasn’t what Jin Geum-Ryong failed to understand.

He couldn’t believe that the snow flowers he desperately bloomed were melting into Mount Hua’s plum blossoms.

‘Why?’

The Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword technique.

This technique contained the last hundred years of the Southern Edge Sect’s efforts. Wasn’t this sword art supposed to culminate the essence of all Southern Edge’s techniques and show their dedication to development?

Even if the legendary plum blossom sword was reproduced, the sword of the Southern Edge sect must be more advanced.

It was impossible that their technique would lose to a relic of the older generations!

But

‘Why is this happening?’

Melting away.

Tearing it apart.

The moment the pure white flowers Jin Geum-Ryong created touched Chung Myung’s red plum blossoms, they collapsed as if they had never existed at all.

‘Why?’

Jin Geum-Ryong’s eyes began to tremble.

He couldn’t display a sword any more perfect than this. It was a sword that unfolded perfectly, to the point that perfection itself seemed inadequate to describe it. So, why couldn’t that shabby plum blossom be defeated?

Crushed.

Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword.

It was broken.

The sword of the Southern Edge Sect.

Collapsing.

Their pride.

“Uh…”

Everything Jin Geum-Ryong had built up till now was scattered by the red plum blossoms.

“WHYYYYYYYY!”

Jin Geum-Ryong screamed.

Chung Myung swung his sword with a half-hearted look in his eyes.

A stream of red plum blossoms trailed from the tip of his sword. The flowers following Jin Geum-Ryong’s sword collapsed without any effort.

‘A shell.’

Just a shell. No, an imitation of a shell.

Everyone misunderstands Mount Hua’s sword. Even the disciples of Mount Hua misunderstand it.

The Plum Blossom Sword technique, no, the sword of Mount Hua, is a sword that faithfully reproduces the color and beauty of the plum blossoms.

People misunderstand and assume that Mount Hua’s sword is judged by how beautiful and sophisticated the plum blossoms are.

But is that all?

Mount Hua is a Taoist sect.

All of Mount Hua’s sword techniques walk the path of Tao.

The Wudang sect considered Taiji as their source.

The Diancang sect considered the sun as their source.

The Kongtong sect considers the five elements as their source.

Every Taoist sect in the world resembles a form of nature, and their ultimate goal is to realize the Tao in their body.

But Mount Hua is different.

Mount Hua only pursues plum blossoms with their sword.

When the sword of the Wudang sect reaches its peak, they feel like they have attained their source. QinCheng’s sword becomes a blazing sun. The Kongtong sect harnesses the power of the five elements in their sword.

However, Mount Hua has Plum Blossoms and Plum Blossoms alone.

This made Mount Hua different from others. It is a sect that feverishly pursues glorious and beautiful techniques.

But was that all?

Did Mount Hua’s Sword only pursue the image of the Plum Blossom?

‘Of course not.’

Everyone misunderstood.

Chung Myung finally understood. After swinging the sword again and again, making plum blossoms bloom and spending his entire life with Mount Hua’s sword. He managed to climb to a height that no one else had ever reached.

What Mount Hua strove to reproduce wasn’t the plum blossom.

Mount Hua didn’t imitate the plum blossom. Mount Hua’s sword makes plum blossoms bloom.

‘It isn’t the plum blossom.’

It was the ‘blooming.’

“Blooming.”

The conception of life.

The fruit of patience finally blooms after persevering through a long winter.

Since the plum blossoms are in full bloom on Mount Hua, they were chosen to represent the ability. But their sword can give birth to new life, so what does it matter which flower they choose to produce?

The essence of Mount Hua’s sword is ‘blooming.’

Those who become blinded by the splendor of the plum blossoms and sharpen their swords in pursuit of that image will never reach the sect’s true essence.

If one can understand that Mount Hua wasn’t pursuing the plum blossoms, but ‘blooming’… right, once they reach the level of Chung Myung, there was no need to distinguish between techniques.

Even if it was a flower that wasn’t the Plum Blossom. Even if it wasn’t the Twenty-Four Movement Plum Blossom Sword technique.

Whether it was the Twelve Movement Snow Flower Sword or the Falling Flower Sword, they could make the plum blossoms bloom.

That was the true meaning of Mount Hua’s sword.

Those who live under the name of Mount Hua need to bear this in their hearts.

Those that fail to understand this and simply pursue the dazzling sword they see would lose their light and forever wander, unable to reach the peak.

Right.

Like Jin Geum-Ryong.

And just like his ancestors who created that sword technique.

Jin Geum-Ryong stared, mesmerized, by Chung Myung.

‘Look clearly.’

How your sword collapses.

Human memory works mysteriously.

The image of the Southern Edge Sect’s technique being broken by Chung Myung’s more splendid and vivid sword in this conference would be engraved into their memories forever.

Every time they swing their swords, they will remember this sight. Whenever they train, they will try to imitate what they have seen.

In the end, the strength they believed in and depended upon will not help them escape from this curse.

Flashier and even more extraordinary.

But there is nothing at the end. All that exists for them is emptiness.

The more they pursue splendor, the more the Southern Edge Sect would lose their sword and fall deeper into the mire.

Even if those they trusted betray you.

Even if they lost the sword techniques that were the center of their sect.

Even if an enemy pushes into the heart of their sect.

Mount Hua will never disappear.

As long as the spirit of Mount Hua remains what they seek. Then, just as plum blossoms endure the harsh winter and bloom again, Mount Hua will once again make its name in the world.

But what if the Southern Edge Sect lost their techniques? What if they lose the spirit they once pursued? What if they were betrayed by their own ideas?

Even if they haven’t suffered a decline, the sect would soon collapse.

Now Chung Myung’s sword will serve as poison for these men and become a curse that will bind their futures.

‘Look!’

Clearly!

What you tried to steal, what you wanted so much.

‘I will show you.’

This would become eternal shackles and would serve as Chung Myung’s revenge for what the Southern Edge Sect did to Mount Hua.

Chung Myung’s sword gracefully flew across the sky. From the tip of the sword, small plum blossoms bloomed.

First one, and then another.

The plum blossoms constantly bloomed.

A flower that radiated life erupted into the world.

The martial arts are divided into Yin and Yang, and tai chi is divided into five elements. The five elements make up the world, and within that world, life is born.

After all, the world is an endless cycle of decay and rebirth.

In this blooming, there is a path that the ancestors of Mount Hua tried to reach.

Mount Hua’s disciples entered Chung Myung’s sight. Seeing them mesmerized by Mount Hua’s sword evoked a strange sense of sorrow within Chung Myung.

‘This is also my atonement.’

What he should have done but couldn’t.

‘So, look at this now.’

This was what Mount Hua ended up losing.

This was where these disciples would need to climb one day.

“Ahh…”

Hyun Jong exclaimed at what he saw.

He didn’t know why he felt this way. The scene before his eyes had touched his heart.

Plum blossoms were fully blooming once again.

The plum blossoms that were out of season were suddenly blooming all around the bleak Mount Hua.

And in that place

There was a spring that never seemed to come.

A spring that never came to Mount Hua, even as the seasons changed.

Spring had never come, even when a young boy grew into a healthy young man. When that young man grew into an old man whose shoulders were crushed under the weight of responsibility, he still waited for the spring to arrive as his hair turned white and his body withered.

Finally, a spring that he had never seen despite the long wait had finally arrived.

Tears welled up in Hyun Jong’s eyes.

Right here.

The Mount Hua he longed to see. The long-awaited sword of Mount Hua.

It was right here.

Hyun Jong smiled.

The tears didn’t stop, but Hyun Jong smiled.

“Mount Hua.”

Mount Hua was still here.

After enduring and enduring all these harsh years, flowers were finally blooming.

“Mount Hua didn’t disappear.”

Feeding his life, perseverance, and patience, the plum blossom finally bloomed after a hundred years.

And disappeared.

Jin Geum-Ryong’s beautiful technique had disappeared like fantasy. The cold and bitter snow flowers were pushed away by the warm wind, and plum blossoms filled the gaps left behind.

Blossoming again and again.

The blooming red plum blossoms filled Jin Geum-Ryong’s vision.

A sea of plum blossoms.

A forest of plum blossoms with no end.

‘This… is Mount Hua.’

The sword of Mount Hua.

Mount Hua’s sword. The sword that the elders of the Southern Edge Sect feared so much and tried to recreate.

Only now could Jin Geum-Ryong understand why his elders were so afraid of Mount Hua.

Something about this sword didn’t exist in the Southern Edge Sect.

This sword was unique to Mount Hua and could not be attained by others.

The wind blew, and the plum blossoms began to flow together in unison.

The entire world seemed to be filled with them.

The sight of countless petals soaring at once was spectacular.

‘Beautiful.’

Jin Geum-Ryong was mesmerized and lost himself in the scene.

Even though he understood his situation, he could not help but be entranced at the sight of the plum blossoms fluttering in front of him.

A sight that didn’t seem to belong to the real world. His soul felt as if it was being sucked in.

‘What’s the difference?’

Why couldn’t he create this splendor?

Why wasn’t his sword so beautiful?

Why?

The plum blossoms didn’t answer him.

They simply covered the world. Gently, splendidly, and majestically.

And

Capturing a scene that he would eternally be unable to forget, a plum leaf softly descended onto Jin Geum-Ryong’s forehead.

And silently.

It sank down.

Chapter 111: It is enough that you are a disciple of Mount Hua (1)

The snow flower and plum blossoms that filled the world faded away.

Like a fantasy.

Those who witnessed this sight stood in stunned silence. Lost in the afterglow, they were unable to escape the lingering imagery of that majestic sight. As the dreamlike visions faded, two people were left standing in their place.

Just two.

Chung Myung and Jin Geum-Ryong.

Everyone observed the two with bated breath.

‘What happened?’

‘Who won?’

Most people didn’t notice what happened during the fight. They only saw a flurry of white snow flowers and red plum blossoms.

But soon, they would be able to clearly see the results they were looking for.

Jin Geum-Ryong appeared to be standing tall, but soon his knees began to tremble.

In a world where time had stopped, only Jin Geum-Ryong seemed to move. His knees bent to the floor, and his body crumbled.

Thud!

The sound of his body hitting the floor broke the stifling silence.

That awkward and unfamiliar sound caused time to flow within Mount Hua once again.

“…”

Baek Cheon looked at the fallen Jin Geum-Ryong with his eyes wide open.

‘Jin Geum-Ryong has….’

A wall that Baek Cheon could never overcome had been defeated and lay collapsed on the ground.

Was Jin Geum-Ryong weak?

That was not the case.

Jin Geum-Ryong’s strength this time had far exceeded Baek Cheon’s expectations. He could understand why Jin Geum-Ryong was so proud and had such confidence in himself. Even if they had battled a thousand times, Baek Cheon would still never defeat him.

But such a man was now lying on the floor.

Baek Cheon’s gaze shifted to the side.

Chung Myung was looking at Jin Geum-Ryong with his sword lowered. It was not just Baek Cheon; everyone was looking at Chung Myung.

There was a slight unease.

And a sense of excitement that arises from the bottom of the heart.

Everyone was naturally aware of what this meant. The scene they had just witnessed would probably be spoken about forever.

As long as Mount Hua and the Southern Edge Sect continue to exist, the story of what happened today would live on through the mouths of the public, along with the names of the Southern Edge Sect and Mount Hua.

In other words.

A legend was born here today.

“… we won.”

Yoon Jong mumbled without realizing it.

He couldn’t believe it despite seeing it with his own eyes.

Ten wins in a row.

Mount Hua’s third-class disciple, Chung Myung, defeated the Southern Edge Sect’s second-class disciples ten times. He even faced off against their strongest disciple, Jin Geum-Ryong.

“Uh…”

Many thoughts complicated Yoon Jong’s mind, and nothing seemed to make sense.

All he could do was groan and stare at Chung Myung.

Shhh.

Chung Myung finally sheathed his sword to his waist and looked around. Those who met his eyes flinched and stepped back.

And…

His lips formed into a smile, and he slowly said.

“This time’s Mount Hua-Southern Edge sect conference….”

He declared in a voice that was neither too high nor low.

“Ends with the victory of Mount Hua!”

And with that came the reaction!

“Ahhhhhhhh!”

Yoon Jong was startled to see Baek Cheon screaming in front of him.

Although Yoon Jong had spent a lot of time together with Baek Cheon since entering Mount Hua, he had never seen Baek Cheon scream this excitedly.

But after thinking about it, it made sense.

Yoon Jong was only a third-class disciple; his feelings towards the Southern Edge Sect were naturally more shallow than Baek Cheon’s. Baek Cheon and the second-class disciples had been crushed by the Southern Edge Sect for at least a decade more than the third-class disciples after experiencing many more conferences.

As such, Yoon Jong’s emotions couldn’t be compared to Baek Cheon’s. Even so, Yoon Jong felt like he was losing his mind in the excitement.

The same was true for the other disciples.

“Woahhhh! We won! We won over the Southern Edge Sect!”

“The first victory in all these years! The first! Damned Southern Edge Sect!”

“Ten wins! Ten wins! That crazy bastard won ten straight times!”

“Right! Hahahaha, Chung Myung! Chung Myung, you brat!”

They had never won a single fight. Seeing the second-class disciples rejoicing for Chung Myung even more than the third-class disciples, Yoon Jong smiled.

‘This is a martial arts sect.’

People argue with each other, and they may not get along well. However, when matters involving the sect’s name occur, all those complicated feelings vanish.

Ah, of course.

“Ahhhh! Sahyung! That crazy bastard won! He beat Jin Geum-Ryong! Woahhh!”

That didn’t mean that the third-class disciples were any less happy.

Jo Gul, who was next to him, grabbed Yoon Jong’s head and began to shake him with a force that could break his neck. He seemed to completely lose his mind.

“Hey, let go of—”

“Ahhh! This is crazy! Crazy, I say! Ten wins! Ten wins! I knew he wasn’t a human, but oh my God! Ten wins! That crazy bastard! Hahaha! He is seriously insane!”

“Let go of me, you idiot!”

Even as Yoon Jong screamed, he couldn’t erase the smile covering his face.

Jo Gul, who was shaking Yoon Jong’s head, nearly began to rip his hair out. Yet, they couldn’t help themselves. A sense of joy and satisfaction was rising from their hearts.

Had they ever felt like this in their lives?

‘Chung Myung. You did well, you punk!’

Yoon Jong looked at Chung Myung, who was still standing in the center.

Chung Myung raised his hand and pressed hard against his chest.

Then he gulped down a rush of blood that was seeking to escape from his mouth.

‘I overdid it.’

The difference between what Chung Myung was capable of and what his body could handle was still as extreme as ever. It was good to overpower Jin Geum-Ryong with the Seven Sages Sword, but he suffered several internal injuries in the process.

But…

“This should be fine.”

He can handle this much internal damage.

In the past, he was the Plum Blossom Sword Saint and lived as an object of fear and respect to others. But had he ever done something like this in his life?

‘I didn’t sever the Heavenly Demon’s head alone.’

Everyone knew the name of the Plum Blossom Sword Saint and his role in history. However, there weren’t many achievements of his own that people could discuss.

Especially not when he was as young as Chung Myung is now.

But this battle today will be remembered and spoken about for a long time and follow Chung Myung throughout his new life in Mount Hua.

‘Am I proud?’

‘No. It’s bittersweet.’

Chung Myung lifted his head and looked at the Southern Edge Sect. Seeing the disciples all dazed and mesmerized, something bloomed within him.

When life is this good, even plain rice would taste sweet!

A cold glint flitted through Chung Myung’s eyes as he smiled and looked at the Southern Edge Sect.

A victory that could be seen on the surface was important, but what mattered to Chung Myung was that they had been ensnared by his hidden intentions. It was certain from how the disciples appeared to be lost and in a daze.

They had understood.

They will never be able to forget what happened here; this was going to be firmly imprinted in their memories. Thinking about how this would impact them in the future, they would surely struggle for the next decade to overcome this trauma.

“You should have never touched us.”

Losing the present is a great crisis, but losing the future results in a complete collapse.

Today, Chung Myung stole the Southern Edge Sect’s future.

‘How is that! Sahyung! My sahyung! Can’t this be called an act of perfect revenge?’

- Are you really a Taoist!?

‘Seriously!?’

Chung Myung contorts his face. A Taoist has no enemies!

Well, at least for this moment, Chung Myung felt thankful that his Sahyung wasn’t alive. If he was alive or if they had returned together, he would have said that the Southern Edge Sect had sinned in the past, but their present disciples were innocent.

And Chung Myung would be asked to stop.

‘But the debt hasn’t been paid in full.’

Chung Myung stared at the Southern Edge Sect.

As long as both sects live near one another, they will continue to find themselves entangled together in the future. So, Chung Myung decided to steadily take his revenge on them.

But for now, this would be the end.

On one side, there was a burst of tearful cheers echoing loudly. On the other, a despairing crowd of mournful gazes.

“Sasuk.’

“Huh? Uh!”

Un Am, who still hadn’t pulled himself together, returned to his senses at Chung Myung’s words.

Un Am looked around and gulped.

‘H-How am I supposed to do this?’

If not him, then who else would do it?

Un Am clenched his fist and looked around, then he shouted with a radiant cheer.

“This Mount Hua and Southern Edge Sect conference ends in the victory of Mount Hua!”

The screams grew even louder.

The place where Mount Hua’s second and third-class disciples gathered was chaotic. They were hugging each other, running around, and screaming out loud.

“Tch. Tch. Without any sense of shame.”

Chung Myung smiled.

Then he looked over at the fallen Jin Geum-Ryong. Even though their disciple had been defeated, no one from the Southern Edge Sect had come to recover him.

No, it wasn’t as if they simply weren’t in the mood to do it. However, their shock was unlike anything they had ever felt before.

“Take him back.”

“…”

“Get yourselves together.”

Startled by Chung Myung’s words, the Southern Edge Sect’s disciples rushed to retrieve their comrade.

“Sahyung! Sahyung! Come to your senses!’

“To the treatment room! Move!”

Chung Myung, who was watching them, turned his head and began to return to his seat in the crowd.

Then, the second and third-class disciples that had been keeping an eye on Chung Myung quickly rushed to him.

“Oh, my god—”

Chung Myung’s words were swiftly cut short.

“Ahhhh! Chung Myuuuuuungg!”

“You idiot! You crazy bastard!”

“No! Well, such men are needed! Seriously!”

The disciples rushed around him. Chung Myung felt like screaming as the immense weight of those around crushed him.

“Ack! My body! You idiots! My body…!”

“Uhahaha!”

“Crazy! Insane!”

“My body! You bastards!”

But it seemed like his words fell on deaf ears. The excited disciples continued to assault Chung Myung in unison, hurling praises and curses as they pushed, pulled, pressed, and hit him….

What sort of son of a bitch just hit him?

After a long period of suffering, Chung Myung somehow managed to escape from the disciples. He staggered. It felt like he collected more injuries from the celebration than he did from the battle.

But.

‘I don’t feel so bad.’

Chung Myung smiled.

In the past, he always played the role of savior for Mount Hua, but he rarely received praise like this. Back then, everyone took his victory for granted. The expectations were different.

Chung Myung returned to life and had to handle many bothersome issues, but thanks to that, he was able to experience many things that he couldn’t experience before.

One thing was certain.

‘Today’s event will change Mount Hua.’

The water in the stream began to flow.

The disciples, who had lost their confidence and suffered from a spiral of defeat, finally regained their pride. One day, that pride would lead them to higher planes.

‘Sahyung. Is this good?’

- You did well. Chung Myung.

Getting a compliment from him was so hard.

A proud smile settled on Chung Myung’s lips.

Chapter 112: It is enough that you are a disciple of Mount Hua (2)

“Huh, uhh? Huu–hahaha….”

Hyun Sang was breathing heavily as a strange windy sound leaked from his mouth.

“T-this. Hahaha!”

There was nothing he could say.

It took all of his effort not to burst into laughter.

The victory was a great pleasure, but it wasn’t appropriate to express it openly since the opponent had suffered horribly.

‘If I was a first-class disciple, I would have run over there by now!’

This was the first time Hyun Sang felt so heavily burdened for being an elder.

‘We really beat them!’

To be precise, Chung Myung had won, not Mount Hua. But who cares? Hyun Sang’s only regret was that he couldn’t join the children in celebrating because of his dignity as an elder.

“Uhahahaha! We won! We won! Did you see that? Sahyung! Chung Myung raised our wealth again!”

“… raised the sect’s name, is that what you meant?”

“Didn’t I say that!? Hahaha! Where did that golden pig even roll in from? Hahaha!”

“S-Sajae! Think of your words….”

“To shit with that! Why should I care about dignity in this situation!? This is the first victory I’ve had to celebrate since I entered this damned Mount Hua!”

“L-let’s calm down….”

“Hahaha! Look at the faces of those Southern Edge bastards! It pissed me off every time I had to watch them leave so triumphantly! Ugh! I couldn’t even eat! Their whole journey home is going to be hell! Hahaha!”

Hyun Sang gave up trying to control Hyun Young and smiled.

‘He’s right. Who cares about decency right now?’

What good ever came to Mount Hua when they kept up their appearances and stayed polite? All they received was applause for being well-mannered.

“Kuhahaha! Sect leader! Sect leader! Did you see!? That Chung Myung… sect leader?”

Hyun Young, who ran to Hyun Jong, flinched the moment he saw the gentle expression on Hyun Jong’s face.

“Everything… has been achieved….”

“No! This idiot keeps trying to pass on anytime something good happens! Come to your senses! Sahyung!”

Hyun Jong shook his head.

‘I feel like my soul escaped for a bit. Wait, that’s not important now.’

“This wasn’t a dream?”

“There’s no dream that’s as absurd as this!”

“Right, you’re right.”

Hyun Jong looked at Chung Myung with a proud smile. Chung Myung, who was surrounded by other disciples, appeared to be screaming and scolding them for their harassment, but all the Sahyungs were embracing him regardless.

‘This is it.’

How long had it been since the disciples of Mount Hua gathered and rejoiced?

Hyun Jong was more satisfied to see the disciples so happy than he was at the fact that they’d defeated the Southern Edge Sect.

“Sect leader.”

Un Geom approached him with a brilliant smile.

“The joy is indescribable, but why don’t we end this now? It wouldn’t be good to keep making the Southern Edge Sect watch this.”

“I suppose so.”

Hyun Jong smiled and looked at Un Geom.

“Did you know this would happen?”

“I didn’t expect this much. But…”

“But?”

Un Geom looked at Chung Myung and said,

“I expected that kid to raise the name of Mount Hua.”

“You have high hopes for him.”

“Right. He’s someone that exceeds all expectations in many ways.”

“R-right, I see.”

It was true that there were many doubts surrounding Chung Myung, but what did that matter right now?

“We should go. Let them be; we need to greet the other side.”

Hyun Young quickly jumped to help out as well.

“Shouldn’t you bring them some gifts? That way, they’ll be sure to spread this story, Sahyung! Let’s open our wallets! We have some money left, so let’s use it! We need to use the money to bribe these people into complimenting Mount Hua and—um! Um!”

Hyun Jong sighed and shook his head as Hyun Sang grabbed Hyun Young and dragged him away.

Sama Seung kept silent.

It was often said that a person driven to the extreme doesn’t feel anger; it would seem that was correct. The anger that had dominated Sama Seung’s mind before had vanished. In its place, there was merely a hollow feeling of disappointment.

‘Why did it turn out like this?’

The Southern Edge Sect had never been defeated in the conference until now. Of all times, it happened now. At the very last conference, they suffered a devastating defeat that could never be washed clean by future generations.

The Southern Edge Sect, a member of the Nine Great Sects and One Union, lost to a crumbling sect that they sought to destroy.

What happened here was unbelievably ridiculous.

‘Why?’

This was no simple defeat.

This defeat would change the flow of power in the surrounding regions. Anyone who knows will regard the Southern Edge Sect as a loser in Shaanxi. The future of the sect would be unknown.

And…

Sama Seung looked at the disciples standing in front of him.

Some were unconscious, while others were caring for the fallen. However, most just seemed bewildered.

As he watched the vitality drain from their eyes, he felt something prick his heart.

‘They will also fear Mount Hua.’

Just like their ancestors did.

After the Demonic Sect’s attack, Mount Hua’s disciples felt the same despair that the Southern Edge Sect felt. They must have also experienced frustration and hopelessness when faced with a wall that could never be overcome.

‘Why?’

It was all because of him.

Sama Seung’s eyes shone.

‘We didn’t lose to Mount Hua.’

They lost to one man.

Had it not been for Chung Myung, such an outcome would have been impossible. What the third-class disciples achieved could be written off as an accident. After all, the Southern Edge Sect’s third-class disciples are younger when compared to Mount Hua’s anyway.

However, Chung Myung defeating the second-class disciples left no room for excuses. From now on, whenever the Southern Edge Sect’s name is mentioned, Chung Myung’s name will surely follow.

‘What kind of humiliation is this?’

Shame.

A disgrace that will never be repeated.

“This…”

Seeing Sama Seung grinding his teeth, the disciples bowed their heads.

‘This… damn it!’

Now that he’d realized the situation, his eyes shone with anger and humiliation. His heart began to pound as if it would explode as his eyes turned distant.

“How do I face the sect leader?”

The faces of the disciples turned a ghostly pale when they heard Sama Seung’s murmuring.

In the eyes of Sama Seung, who was grasping for a way to explain this, he saw the sect leader of Mount Hua approaching.

Crunch.

He bit his lip enough to make it bleed again. But he couldn’t allow his pain to be shown to Mount Hua. They would only mock him further.

Sama Seung controlled his expression and spoke to Hyun Jong.

“Congratulations, sect leader.”

“You did well too.”

Hyun Jong smiled.

“We were lucky this time.”

“… then we must be out of luck.”

Sama Seung’s eyes flashed.

Hearing Hyun Jong’s words, he wanted to scream out, but he spoke coldly.

“You can rejoice as much as you like, Sect leader. Isn’t victory a rarity for Mount Hua? You never know if this will be the last time you experience it, so you should be happy! Ah! Be happy!”

“T-that…”

Hyun Young was about to yell, but Hyun Sang quickly pulled him back.

Sama Seung continued to speak as his tone began to shift.

“I admit that we lost the conference today, but don’t forget that Mount Hua didn’t win against the Southern Edge sect! Only the third-class disciples won, not the second-class! The fact is that you haven’t changed a thing.”

Hyun Jong smiled brightly as he listened to Sama Seung.

“We think the same too.”

“…”

“I am grateful for your comments. I would appreciate it if you could send my regards to the Southern Edge Sect’s leader.”

Hearing those words, Sama Seung’s eyes went wide.

‘How dare he say this!’

Hyun Jong didn’t even dare to look him in the eye just the other day. But now he was acting so defiantly, just because he won once…

’You—“

That moment.

“Ha. Cheap stuff never goes very far.”

“…”

Sama Seung turned his head.

It was a familiar voice now. A voice that he would never forget in this life. Chung Myung approached the elders, along with his sahyungs.

Sama Seung’s eyes were bloodshot as his gaze pierced Chung Myung.

‘All because of him.’

Sama Seung seemed to be holding back a belly full of raging fire as he glared at Chung Myung. Receiving the elder’s gaze, Chung Myung punched Jo Gul, who was standing next time him.

“Sahyung! Cheap stuff!? Huh? Cheap! How could you say that!?”

“Hey! I’m the Sahyung here!”

“So? If you are the Sahyung, you should at least try and protect my face. How can you act so rudely!”

“… are you really talking to me right now?”

“Who else? Sahyung!”

Chung Myung kicked Jo Gul once again and turned to Hyun Jong.

“Sect leader. The conference is done, so I felt that it would be polite to come and greet the other side.”

“Huhu. I see.”

‘Don’t be polite to them, you bastard.’

Seeing that he had the sect leader’s permission, Chung Myung shifted his focus to Sama Seung.

Seeing a disgustingly wide smile on Chung Myung’s face, Sama Seung’s body trembled to its core.

‘This is all his fault.’

And…

Perhaps this man will be the biggest obstacle for the Southern Edge Sect in the future.

Then, he’d rather…

Inside his sleeves, Sama Seung’s hands twitched.

As long as he was prepared to live in infamy, a contribution of unprecedented importance could be made to his sect. He may never be able to return to the Southern Edge Sect, but for the sake of their future…

At that time, Chung Myung smiled and said,

“Would you like to take a swing at me?”

“…”

Sama Seung’s eyes shook.

‘This brat…’

Sama Seung’s face turned white upon realizing that Chung Myung discerned his intentions.

‘What young man could….’

If Chung Myung’s guard was down, Sama Seung might be able to kill him in a surprise assault. However, with the strength that he’s shown, it would be impossible to slay Chung Myung in one stroke as long as he was prepared to defend himself.

And if Sama Seung failed to kill Chung Myung, then he would be stigmatized and hated without accomplishing anything. In fact, his sect’s reputation would suffer for having raised a villain.

Chung Myung smiled at the elder who couldn’t do anything to him.

“I think we’ll see each other often in the future. Next time, I’ll greet you first.”

“…”

Sama Seung stared at him for a long period and then turned away with bloodless eyes.

“We’re going back!”

Without even waiting for his disciples, he quickly left Mount Hua.

“That…”

“Hmm.”

Hearing the sighs that freely flowed from the crowd around, Chung Myung laughed.

‘Why act like that?’

He couldn’t understand.

“Chung Myung.”

Chung Myung turned to the voice that called for him.

Hyun Jong was looking at him with a very complicated expression. There was a complex mix of affection, pity, pride, and regret all at the same time. Recognizing that look, Chung Myung closed his eyes without realizing it.

In this case, Hyun Jong had the same expression as his Sahyung.

He would also have that same expression when looking at Chung Myung.

Chung Myung didn’t understand what that face meant in the past, but now he did. He naturally came to understand when he led Mount Hua.

After a long time, Hyun Jong’s voice cut through Chung Myung’s ears.

“… you’ve worked hard.”

Chung Myung smiled brightly.

“It was nothing, Sect leader.”

Chapter 113: It is enough that you are a disciple of Mount Hua (3)

The start was grand, but the ending was pretty sloppy.

There were several reasons.

First of all, Mount Hua had never imagined they could win, so they never made any plans to celebrate if they did. Even if they wanted to celebrate, the feeling seemed vague.

Secondly, since Sama Seung had already left, the disciples from the Southern Edge Sect had no choice but to leave Mount Hua in a hurry.

Finally…

“Sect leader! Can we talk for a moment?”

“Don’t push! Didn’t I come here first?”

“Sect leader! Wait for a second, sect leader!”

As soon as Sama Seung left, the officials of Shaanxi, who had seen the events, rushed for Hyun Jong. They had set their sights on Mount Hua’s potential, and they couldn’t just leave empty-handed.

‘I need to make a deal!’

‘I need to secure some business with them!’

‘We can’t let the Eunha Guild soak up all the profits!’

Mount Hua may have won the conference, but that didn’t mean they had completely overpowered the Southern Edge Sect. Still, it was undeniable that Mount Hua was growing stronger at an incredible rate.

Such is the logic of the world. Where there was power, money was bound to flow. The people of Shaanxi had seen the results of the conference for themselves, and they hoped that the money that would soon flow into Mount Hua could trickle down to themselves as well.

“What is wrong with all of you!?”

Hyun Young shouted so loudly that the officials flinched and looked at Hyun Young.

‘Did I overdo it?’

‘Right. Still, he is a sect leader. I should behave politely….’

‘Everyone arrived at once, so he must be flustered.’

However, the words that followed were different from their expectations as Hyun Young spoke.

“You should be discussing the matter with me, the finance head of the sect. I’ve prepared refreshments, so please come this way. I will prepare enough time for you all, so we don’t need to rush through this.”

“…”

“Ah, and I’ve prepared rooms for you to stay, just in case. If anyone wants to stay, let me know.”

“…”

As the crowd watched Hyun Young humming as he headed toward the finance office, they realized that there would be a difficult day of negotiations ahead of them.

Just before all the Southern Edge Sect’s disciples headed home, Chung Myung found himself face to face with a certain disciple again.

“Thank you for the guidance.”

“… What?”

“Thank you, young disciple.”

Chung Myung looked at Lee Seong-Baek with a stiff expression.

“All your other sahyungs must be gnashing their teeth right now. Is it alright for you to come and say this to me?”

Lee Song-Baek scratched his head with an awkward face.

“We’re already halfway distant.”

‘Halfway?’

Should he be called optimistic? Or simply stupid? The disciples of the Southern Edge Sect were clearly glaring at Lee Song-Baek with eyes full of hatred.

It was only natural that they’d feel that way.

A traitor is always more hated than the enemy. From the Southern Edge Sect’s point of view, the most terrifying enemy was Chung Myung. So, how could they think positively of Lee Song-Baek when he so openly fraternized with the enemy?

Although, it seemed like Lee Song-Baek didn’t care about that at all.

“Before, I couldn’t understand what the young disciple was saying.”

Lee Song-Baek spoke with determined eyes.

“But now I think I understand what you were trying to tell me and the path I need to take.”

“… hey, I am from Mount Hua, you know?”

Lee Song-Baek smiled brightly.

“What does it matter which sect you belong to? Anyone can be a teacher as long as you have something to learn and are willing to listen.”

“Excuse me, you…”

“Huh?”

“Do you want to join our sect?”

‘He should just join Mount Hua.’

‘He’s way more like a taoist than me!’

“After all, you’ve already made an enemy of the Southern Edge Sect.”

Lee Song-Baek smiled humbly and looked over at Jin Geum-Ryong, who was still unconscious and being carried out.

“Sahyung must have felt a lot from today’s match. Be careful. Sahyung is an amazing person. He’ll surely train with the young disciple as his goal from now on. He’ll become much more powerful and frightening.

“Yes, well, whatever.”

Seeing Chung Myung’s response, Lee Song-Baek smiled bitterly.

“It might be meaningless for you, young disciple.”

Chung Myung will become stronger much faster than Jin Geum-Ryong. As time passes, the gap will only widen, never closing. Lee Song-Baek was also well aware of that.

“I just wanted to thank you again. Then, until we meet again….”

“Wait.”

This time, Chung Myung called for Lee Song-Baek.

“Yes?”

Chung Myung and Lee Song-Baek stared at each other without exchanging a word for what seemed like a long time, then Chung Myung began to speak in a different, more serious tone.

“It will be a difficult road.”

“…”

Lee Song-Baek looked at Chung Myung and sighed.

“Young disciple really seems to read people’s minds. I can’t hide anything from you.”

“You’ll still stay with them?”

Lee Song-Baek nodded.

“I didn’t choose this path because I wanted to. I need to take this path, so I will follow it.”

Chung Myung nodded.

“Sure.”

Chung Myung was struck by a strange emotion as he watched Lee Song-Baek return to his fellow disciples.

Lee Song-Baek will probably have to fight a lonely battle from now. The Southern Edge Sect’s disciples would never be able to forget Chung Myung’s sword and would live with that as their goal.

It would be difficult to protect the Southern Edge Sect’s techniques in that environment. People reject those that are different from themselves.

It will be a lonely and difficult battle, but…

“If he can do that, maybe he will become the hope of the Southern Edge Sect.”

Chung Myung turned and looked at Mount Hua’s third-class disciples.

Seeing Jo Gul and the others smiling, he couldn’t help but sigh.

‘At least one sect seems to be doing well.’

Why was his sect made of such people!?

If only Mount Hua had a single person like Lee Song-Baek, Chung Myung’s job would have been twice as easy!

“Ugh.”

Chung Myung shook his head.

What could he do?

‘Even if I die, I’m still a man.’

Humans do their best in a given environment. There’s no point in blaming others or being envious of what they have.

Chung Myung turned around to watch the Southern Edge Sect leave.

With this, the matter with the Southern Edge Sect was concluded. From now on, Chung Myung would no longer take the initiative to strike at the Southern Edge Sect. They might not know, but he had already taken enough revenge.

So, did his relationship with the Southern Edge Sect end here?

‘Of course not.’

Now, for the Southern Edge sect, Chung Myung went far beyond just being a thorn in their eyes and had become their number one enemy.

It was understandable. At least, if Chung Myung was the Southern Edge Sect’s leader, he would do anything to avenge this humiliation.

Because that is only the way that they can survive.

“Then they’ll get what’s coming to them.”

Chung Myung smiled.

Then someone quickly rushed in looking for him.

“Chung Myung!”

It was Yoon Jong.

“What is it, Sahyung?”

“Come here. The sect leader is looking for you.”

“…”

Chung Myung didn’t feel like going.

‘Again.’

He raised his head and looked up at the distant sky.

‘I should have held myself back.’

Actually, the series of events was far from over.

After all, didn’t Chung Myung take down all of the Southern Edge Sect’s second-class disciples and make plum blossoms bloom from his sword?

Naturally, the elders had no choice but to harbor doubts about him. Until now, the conference had been ongoing, so they couldn’t concentrate on him. However, now that the conference had concluded, they were bound to have questions they wanted to be answered.

‘What kind of excuse would work here?’

Should he say that he’s their ancestor?

No, he couldn’t say that.

How about saying that he just happened to pick these techniques up by chance?

No, no one would believe that.

“Ugh.”

While Chung Myung scratched his head and struggled to devise a way out of this scenario, Yoon Jong just tilted his head in confusion.

“What are you up to? Come on, let’s go.”

“Yes.”

Chung Myung took a deep breath.

‘Ah, my life.’

Now, even after winning, he would have to make up some excuses.

‘My sahyung! Are you watching? Should I really live like this?’

- Then just die.

‘No! You bastard’

‘You’re just saying that because you are dead!’

In the end, Chung Myung headed to the sect leader’s residence like a cow being led to the slaughterhouse. Given that there were quite a few shoes in front of the room, it seemed like the elders and the first-class disciples had all gathered.

“Sect leader. I, Yoon Jong, brought Chung Myung.”

“Come in.”

“Yes.”

Yoon Jong beckoned Chung Myung inside.

“…”

And he beckoned again.

“…”

“What are you doing, brat! Get in!”

“… hmmm.”

Chung Myung sighed and entered.

Now that he was entering, he would have to deal with being questioned…

“Oohhh! Chung Myung!”

“Oh-ho! You did well! Very well! My Chung Myung did well!”

“…”

‘What?’

As soon as he entered, the elders and the first-class disciples waiting for him all applauded.

It was strange to see all these men that should be doubting him clap for him.

‘What is wrong with these people?’

When he looked up, everyone was smiling and full of laughter. Even though they couldn’t bloom plum blossoms from their swords, they seemed like they would bloom at any moment from these men’s smiling faces.

Seeing Hyun Jong, who was seated in the middle with a smile so wide that it reached both ears, Chung Myung realized one thing.

‘Ah, they never felt this.’

Seeing the adults of the sect smiling and laughing as if it was nothing important, Chung Myung felt both a bit dreary and emotional at the same time.

‘What was it?’

It was a bit like a child seeing his father fail to live up to his expectations…

Hyun Jong began to speak while trying to calm himself.

“Right. Chu—ugh! Right, Chung Myung….kuk!”

Hyun Jong lowered his head and covered his mouth with his hands. Even the word ‘Chung Myung’ seemed too good for him to say.

“Kuahahah!”

The old man seemed to cough. However, his face turned red, and it seemed like he was still struggling to hold back his laughter.

“Right. Are you hurt anywhere?”

“Just a slight cut.”

“The wound might fester. So, after leaving here, go straight to the medical practitioner.”

Hyun Sang spoke with dazzling eyes.

“Just call the medical practitioner here! Why ask such a busy man to go to them?”

“… I feel like that’s a bit strange. Who’s busy?”

“That child is busy! What work does the practitioner even have to do?”

“…”

Hyun Jong looked at Hyun Sang with blank eyes, but he simply puffed up his chest feeling proud.

And everyone gathered there nodded their heads as if it was the natural course to take.

“…then let’s do that.”

“Yes, Sect leader.”

“You’re Mount Hua’s—”

It was then.

Slam!

The door burst open as Hyun Young sprinted in.

“Sect leader! Money is pouring in! Hahaha! A lot of money is rolling in! I’ve never even heard of a story where we make money without doing anything! That guy is the God of Wealth! God of Wealth! Earning money… Chung Myung, this child! You are here!”

Hyun Young rushed to Chung Myung and grabbed his cheeks.

“What a cute child! Hahaha! If I had a grandson like you, I wouldn’t wish for anything more in the world!”

Chung Myung, whose cheeks were stretched out, looked like he was going to pass out.

‘My sahyung!’

‘Look at how I have to live.’

‘Now, a child that’s too young to even be my grandson is stretching out my cheeks. Huk! Do I really have to live like this? Huh?’

“Look at you. You seem quite happy.”

“Uhahah! What? Right. I am happy too. Uhahahah!”

All the adults in Mount Hua seemed to have lost their minds.

Chapter 114: It is enough that you are a disciple of Mount Hua (4)

Chung Myung looked at Hyun Jong’s back as they climbed up the mountain.

Hyun Jong, who congratulated Chung Myung, called him to talk alone.

And they were now climbing the mountain alone.

Chung Myung’s eyes stayed fixed on Hyun Jong’s back as he followed behind him.

It was the second time he was staring at the elder’s back like this. The last time was when he witnessed the tragic sight of the sect leader unable to open the door to the underground warehouse.

The back of Hyun Jong, who carried the fate of the crumbling Mount Hua alone. That sad back, which was unable to be shown to others, remains firmly imprinted in Chung Myung’s memory.

But today, his back seemed a bit less burdened than before.

Hyun Jong, who finally reached the summit, looked down at Mount Hua.

Chung Myung also looked around. Taking in the sights of Mount Hua’s rugged mountains.

“Chung Myung.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“This is the highest peak on Mount Hua.”

“Yes.”

“Did you feel anything when climbing up?”

It was a random question, so Chung Myung just honestly answered what he felt.

“It’s high.”

“…”

Hyun Jong turned and looked at Chung Myung. However, Chung Myung just proudly puffed out his chest. As if to ask, ‘was it wrong?’

Hyun Jong smiled seeing that.

“Yes, yes, you’re right.”

Hyun Jong’s face softened.

“I’ve called you here because I have something I want to ask you.”

‘Is this where it starts?’

Chung Myung’s face turned grim.

He wasn’t sure what the question would be, but he knew that he needed to avoid being entangled or confused…

“Chung Myung.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“The plum blossom on your sword.”

Chung Myung licked his lips. Firstly…

“Thank you.”

Hyun Jong bowed his head towards Chung Myung.

At the unexpected action, Chung Myung flinched and took a step back.

“Why are you doing this, sect leader!?”

“This isn’t being done as the sect leader of Mount Hua. I am thanking you from one human to another. I have always wanted to witness that scene, at least once in my life.”

“…”

“But my position as the sect leader of Mount Hua is more important than me being a human, so I cannot help but ask you. How did you manage to make the plum blossoms bloom with the Seven Sages Sword?”

Chung Myung looked at Hyun Jong and spoke.

“It just happened naturally.”

“… Naturally?”

“Yes. As I learned the Seven Sages Sword, the plum blossoms naturally bloomed. I don’t know why either.”

“I see.”

“It’s just….”

“Hmm?”

Chung Myung looked at Hyun Jong and asked.

“Aren’t all the swords of Mount Hua like that?”

Hyun Jong looked down at the view beneath his feet without answering. After staring down at the mighty figure of Mount Hua, he said.

“Wise.”

He thought that maybe there was a secret behind what Chung Myung did. However, Chung Myung’s answer denied his thoughts.

‘Right. That is Mount Hua’s sword.’

Chung Myung was simply saying that he was ahead of the others. In other words, if the others continued to train, then one day, their swords would also make plum blossoms bloom.

‘Plum blossoms.’

If the day comes when all of Mount Hua’s disciples can do that, the era of Mount Hua will begin again.

“Plum Blossom Swordsman…”

These were words that no one dared to say now.

Plum blossoms were the symbol of Mount Hua. Naturally, the name of the one that could wield that symbol was the Plum Blossom Swordsman.

Right now, no one in Mount Hua deserves that title. However, as Chung Myung said, as long as the day comes when every disciple can make the plum blossoms bloom, that title will surely be passed on properly.

“It’s still a long way off, hahaha.”

“…”

The atmosphere was nice, definitely!

Looking back at Chung Myung, Hyun Jong saw that mischievous smile, which weirdly put his heart at ease.

Hyun Jong spoke with a large smile.

“Chung Myung.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“What is Mount Hua to you?”

Chung Myung shook his head without answering.

He seemed to see his sahyungs in the blue sky above.

‘Mount Hua.’

“For me, Mount Hua is….”

As his sahyung said.

“Is just Mount Hua.”

Now he understood a little of what that meant.

Hyun Jong lightly nodded his head when he heard that answer.

“It is enough that you are a disciple of Mount Hua.”

A warm smile formed on his lips.

“People just want to be here, but the world doesn’t leave them alone. That’s the way the world works, after all. Can you manage to hold your ground?”

Chung Myung chuckled.

“If I couldn’t hold my ground, I wouldn’t have started.”

“I see.”

Hyun Jong looked at Chung Myung and softly said.

“If that’s how you think, then Mount Hua will protect you. Mount Hua and I will protect you from everything you might have to bear.”

Chung Myung smiled.

Nothing was asked.

Hyun Jong didn’t ask a single thing. There must be countless things he wanted to ask, but he was saying that Chung Myung being here was enough for him.

‘The sect leader of Mount Hua.’

Hyun Jong was born later than Chung Myung, and compared to Chung Myung, he didn’t have a reputation built on strength. In terms of power or prestige, he was someone that couldn’t be compared with Chung Myung.

But Chung Myung acknowledged him.

Because this man possessed something that Chung Myung lacked. He was never the sect leader, and Chung Myung was unable to call himself a Taoist. So, he couldn’t help but respect this man who chose to follow his own path.

“Sect leader. It isn’t about protecting me.”

Hyun Jong seemed confused.

“We’re just going together. Under the name of Mount Hua.”

Hyun Jong’s slightly hardened face cracked a small smile.

“You are right.”

Hyun Jong smiled softly.

“Chung Myung.”

“Yes, Sect leader.”

“Promise me one thing.”

Chung Myung raised his head and looked at Hyun Jong’s soft eyes.

“I hope to hear more from you someday.”

Chung Myung opened his mouth slightly and then closed it.

It felt strange; it was like something was being squeezed within his chest.

He pressed down on the emotions he couldn’t understand and looked up at the sky.

“I will.”

Someday.

Right, someday.

Excitement doesn’t end so easily.

Especially if they have been through something incredible that’s never been experienced before. For months, such excitement can dominate a person’s mind, let alone a few days.

Mount Hua’s third-class disciples were currently in such a state.

Although the conference was over, the third-class disciples weren’t free from the results of the conference.

“We really won?”

“… I still can’t believe it!”

“It’s like a dream. We seriously won against the Southern Edge Sect.”

It would have been easier to accept had they been confident of their skills and regarded the Southern Edge Sect as a worthy opponent.

However, most of the third-class disciples believed that they were weak and lacked faith in their skills.

It was understandable. Their skills weren’t developed through their own efforts; it would be more accurate to say that Chung Myung forcefully injected their skills into them.

Moreover, Chung Myung was a tyrant that made one understand the cruelty of this depressing world. He wouldn’t even explain what kind of effect the training would have on them or what level they would reach once they completed it.

So, their dumbfounded reactions were only natural.

“I don’t know what that bastard’s thinking!”

“Who?”

“Who? Who else, if not Chung Myung?”

Everyone gathered nodded in unison.

As the aftermath of the incident swept over them, and they started to calm down, they realized how terrifying Chung Myung truly was.

No one among the third-class disciples was unaware of Chung Myung’s greatness. But what he did this time was so great that he single-handedly overturned everyone’s understanding of him.

Jo Gul, who seemed strangely mesmerized, spoke to Yoon Jong.

“Sahyung.”

“Huh?”

“I can’t sleep.”

“… are you even going to ask me to give you counseling?”

“Not like that….”

Jo Gul scratched his head and spoke.

“Whenever I close my eyes, the sword Chung Myung showed keeps flashing in my mind. It almost feels like I’m being possessed… I can’t explain it well. But it’s like that.”

Yoon Jong gulped.

‘He is the same?’

It was the same for Yoon Jong.

Whenever Yoon Jong would close his eyes, he would see the swordsmanship that caused plum blossoms to bloom. No, even when his eyes were open, he was constantly thinking about it.

At first, it was fine.

Most of the work was done by Chung Myung, but the other third-class disciples also defeated their opponents.

The more they thought about their victories, the more it became difficult to calm their hearts.

But as time passed, the excitement faded, and they started to think about what they saw.

‘That Sword…’

Fantastical.

Could it be explained further?

Yoon Jong felt like he had a good fight against the Southern Edge Sect.

But that sword…

If only he could unleash that sword on his own…

“Sahyung.”

Yoon Jong looked at Jo Gul.

“Will we ever be able to display a technique like that?”

Yoon Jong fell into deep thought.

‘Someday…’

“Gul.”

“Yes, Sahyung.”

“I don’t know if this is something I should say when I’m just a third-class disciple of Mount Hua….”

Hearing those words, everyone’s eyes focused on Yoon Jong.

“To be honest, I just wanted to be strong.”

“…”

Yoon Jong continued to honestly speak his mind.

“I never thought about reaching a certain level or wanting to show any particular techniques. I just had a vague desire to get stronger.”

“It was the same for me.”

Jo Gul spoke like it was a confession.

Most of them probably felt the same, which helped Yoon Jong to relax slightly.

“But this time, seeing that sword...”

‘How should I put it?’

Yoon Jong shut his mouth to carefully choose his words.

He never felt that he was bad at speaking, and it wasn’t that he couldn’t find the right words. For some reason, he just found it difficult to express how he felt right now.

After thinking about it for a few moments, Yoon Jong spoke frankly.

“… I thought. That’s what I want to do. I want to be able to display that swordsmanship myself.”

Everyone nodded.

Perhaps these words represented what all of them were thinking.

Perhaps that was the sword of Mount Hua.

That’s the direction they should engrave in their hearts and strive to achieve for the rest of their lives.

Several years after their initiation into the sect, they had finally seen Mount Hua’s true swordsmanship.

“Can we really unfold that technique someday?”

Yoon Jong received everyone’s attention and silently endured it as he nodded.

“I believe that we can.”

There was determination in his eyes.

“We are the disciples of Mount Hua. There’s no way that a disciple of Mount Hua would be unable to display Mount Hua’s swordsmanship. If we work tirelessly, one day, we will surely be able to achieve that goal.”

“Sahyung!”

“We need to train well!”

“I’ll surely reach that level one day. I have a goal now.”

“Right. I will work hard too. Along with you all.”

After a long time together, the third-class disciples had begun to believe in each other and unite as one.

“Even if we have shortcomings, won’t Chung Myung solve them?”

“Because he’s like a goblin.”

“Won’t he make us stronger?”

“Right.”

At the same time, confidence in Chung Myung began to rise within them.

But…

It was then.

Bang!

The door opened violently.

‘I must have told him fifty times to open the door with his hands. You can’t just kick it open.’

It seemed like Yoon Jong’s thoughts were read as the door was closed normally.

And a very familiar face began to slowly scan through the disciples in the dorms. The calm faces quickly contorted in panic.

‘It’s s–starting again.’

‘What is he going to say now?’

Chung Myung’s lips seemed to twitch, as if he was annoyed, before violently opening.

“What are you all doing exchanging warm words of encouragement like kids! Huh?”

… why haven’t the ghosts taken this demon back with them yet?

Well, they could never catch that kind of person.

Chapter 115: It is enough that you are a disciple of Mount Hua (5)

“Y-you are back?”

“You worked hard. You should rest a little….”

They were good words. Very good words.

Good words to resolve the awkward atmosphere.

The third-class disciples were desperate, but unfortunately, Chung Myung wasn’t the kind of person who changed his mood to accommodate others.

Rather, he tilted his head to the side.

‘Why is he doing that again?’

‘Something good just happened! Why is he like this again!?’

Chung Myung, whose head was turned, began to speak. Even his voice seemed eerie and distorted.

“You all seem to be in a great mood, aren’t you?”

“…”

“Wow, look at everyone resting. Resting after all that trouble. I would have been thinking about going out and swinging a sword one or ten thousand times if it were me. Or maybe, training my body with some weights and running.”

These third-class disciples could cope with all the harshness in the world, but they couldn’t cope with this insubordinate sajae of theirs.

Everyone desperately glanced at Yoon Jong. They were implying that it was up to him, as great sahyung, to save them from this predicament.

‘You only think of me as great sahyung at times like this, you rotten bastards!’

‘Why don’t you show me some respect in peaceful times too!? It’s not normal!’

But what could be done? The truth is that he is the great sahyung.

“Hahaha.”

Yoon Jong began to speak with an awkward smile.

“Why are you so angry? I think we all did well this time.”

Yoon Jong was trying to subtly imply that Chung Myung shouldn’t be so cruel after they finally turned a chain of losses into their first victory, but that bastard didn’t seem to understand Yoon Jong beating around the bush.

“Well? Sahyungs?”

Chung Myung stared at the others.

Seeing the madness in his eyes, all of their expressions darkened.

“What amazing people, and now you are gathering to hold a celebration too! Aren’t you supposed to be training instead of wasting time? Train! Have your life goals been achieved just because you won a conference?”

That’s what it was.

That was it.

Chung Myung covered his face and continued to speak.

“When I was a kid! I went to war and got stabbed, and I still got up and trained the next day! Seriously, kids these days, uh….”

‘When did he go to war?’

‘Aren’t we older than him?’

“Isn’t it good enough that we defeated the Southern Edge Sect’s third-class disciples? We should celebrate.”

Yoon Jong decided to rebel and speak out, at least a little. But such rebellion doesn’t always lead to good results, especially against Chung Myung.

“Defeated them? Ah, right. Well said.”

“…”

“Just looking at them, weren’t they at least five years younger than all of you? Are you really happy that you beat up those kids?”

“…”

“They looked so young; how old could they have been two years ago? You must have been weak as shit to lose to them!”

“…”

Chung Myung always knew how to stab where it hurts most.

The excited air in the dorms quickly turned melancholic.

“If the fight went well, I wouldn’t have said anything! But you! You twisted on your own foot and almost fell!”

One of the disciples flinched and looked away.

“How could you miss and strike the shoulder when you were aiming for their head!?”

Another disciple flinched.

“The bastard who lost his cool, declared his victory, and rushed in only to get hit and almost lose!”

“…”

Chung Myung, who was speaking loudly, almost as if to yell, waited and took a deep breath before looking up at the ceiling.

“I taught you all wrong. I… sahyungs made no mistake. It’s my fault.”

“…”

Jo Gul and Yoon Jong exchanged hesitant looks.

‘What’s wrong with him?’

‘How should I know?’

‘Try to fix it.’

‘Sigh…’

Yoon Jong had a dead look in his eyes as he tried to resolve this situation.

“O-of course, there were some mistakes made. But didn’t it end well? In practice, mistakes happen all the time.”

“Mistake?”

“…”

Yoon Jong was suddenly struck with the ominous feeling that he had said something terribly wrong.

“Then being stabbed and dying on the battlefield is probably just a mistake to you as well, right?”

‘Huhuhu. Is this where I went wrong?’

“You don’t even try to avoid making mistakes when training! It’s natural to make mistakes!? This is what happens when you train with such a weak mental state! All you needed to do was swing the sword properly, and you couldn’t even do that?”

Yoon Jong gave up on stopping this demon anymore.

“And what? Someday you’ll do it properly? Someday?”

Chun Myung smiled brightly.

“When will that day come?”

“…”

“I wonder how you manage to drag yourselves out of bed and train each day with that mentality! You’re playing around and treating this conference as just another training session!? Someday you’ll get it right and take it seriously!?”

Jo Gul smiled.

‘Mother. I miss you.’

He would yell at his mother to stop nagging, but now he wanted to apologize to her. Her nagging couldn’t even be considered nagging anymore.

‘Does this bastard have a knife in his mouth?’

How could each word hurt so much?

Chung Myung lowered his voice.

“Don’t be so happy.”

“…”

“This was only the first battle. We will have to fight countless times in the future. Right now, this may be a big deal for Sahyungs, but in hindsight, it’s nothing.

The third-class disciples nodded their heads.

“Can I ask one question?”

“Anything.”

“If we really train like you say, will we also be able to display such swordsmanship?”

Chung Myung’s face contorted again.

“Sahyungs. You seem to be misunderstanding something.”

“…”

“It doesn’t matter what you want; you will have to.”

“…”

Chung Myung blinked his eyes.

“Does it make sense for Mount Hua’s disciples to be unable to display Mount Hua’s techniques and make even a single flower bloom? Do you think I’ll sit still and let that happen?”

It was strange.

They were also thinking the same thing, but how can it sound so different depending on who’s saying it?

The third-class disciples, who were filled with motivation to unleash the techniques that Chung Myung had shown, suddenly lost the will to continue.

Their eyes, which were brightly burning like the sun, quickly decayed into a dead and hopeless expression.

“What are you doing?”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung directed them with a nod of his chin.

“We need to go. Are you going to skip training today?”

“…Chu–Chung Myung. The time is already….”

“You said you wanted to learn that sword, didn’t you?”

‘No, yes, but….’

‘No, Chung Myung, we aren’t in a hurry to do that. We can do it later.’

“Are you going to come or not?”

“Eik!”

The third-class disciples rushed out of the dorm. The dorm that had been buzzing with hope was now void of such optimistic feelings.

Chung Myung watched the disciples rushing out and grinned.

‘I can’t let them get too excited.’

This was just the first step. It was good that this victory instilled confidence in them, but confidence often turned to arrogance.

Real progress would be made when these disciples took their victories and followed them up with continuous training. He felt like he pushed them too much, but…

“I’m only doing this because I want them to grow!”

Chung Myung shrugged his shoulders and began to follow the disciples outside when someone entered the White Plum training hall.

“Huh?”

Chung Myung titled his head at the unexpected face.

“What brings you here?”

“…”

The eyes of the person trembled.

“If you see your sasuk, you should greet them first… no, such things probably don’t mean anything to you.”

Baek Cheon stared straight at Chung Myung and asked.

“Could you spare a few moments?”

Baek Cheon, climbing up the mountain’s peak, snuck a peek at Chung Myung.

“Ah, my legs.”

Chung Myung looked around and sat on a tree stump. He seemed to perfectly fit the image of an elderly man!

‘That little jerk.’

‘You’re too young to be acting like an old man!’

But there was no way Baek Cheon could point that out.

“Thank you for giving me some time.”

“It is nothing. You are my sasuk.”

Baek Cheon felt glad.

“But what brings you to me? To summon me to this humble place, are you going to attack me?”

“…”

Although they didn’t know each other for very long, Chung Myung was aware that Baek Cheon didn’t like him. So, what could he be thinking to ask Chung Myung for his time, as if there was no bad blood between them?

“I saw the battle between you and Jin Geum-Ryong.”

“He already worked quite heavily against you.”

“You were overwhelming.”

“It was nothing.”

Baek Cheon stared at Chung Myung in silence; he slowly opened his mouth after a long period.

“All the sasuks are quite shaken up. At first, it seemed like they were all fine, but now, everything seems complicated.”

That much could be guessed.

As long as they had eyes, they couldn’t deny what Chung Myung did. It was also true that the third-class disciples were noticeably stronger than before.

The second-class disciples were meant to serve as examples and lead the third-class disciples. However, how were they supposed to feel now that the third-class disciples had the potential to become stronger than them?

No, maybe the third-class disciples had already become stronger than them.

“So, what are you trying to say?”

“We want to be strong.”

“… ohhh.”

Baek Cheon looked at Chung Myung with determined eyes.

“I don’t know if you’re aware, but, as your senior, it isn’t easy for me to come and say this.”

“I fully understand.”

Who wouldn’t understand Baek Cheon’s feelings, especially Chung Myung, who had seen Baek Cheon’s struggles for himself?

‘His mind must be a mess right now.’

For the first time, he felt sympathy for Baek Cheon.

“But no matter how much I think about it, this seems like the best choice I can make. It’s not that I don’t believe in my sasuks, but what I can learn from them is different from what you can teach us.”

Chung Myung just looked at Baek Cheon.

“So, you’re here and setting aside your pride because you want me to teach the second-class disciples by myself?

“Yes.”

Chung Myung laughed bitterly.

“Why should I do that?”

“…”

Maybe it was because of the unexpected response, but Baek Cheon was at a loss for words and stared blankly.

“It’s annoying, and I don’t get anything out of it, so I don’t see why I should agree.”

“… I am your sasuk. Don’t we belong to the same sect?”

“So? Have the second-class disciples been watching and guiding the third-class disciples? Or did you just leave and do your own training?”

Baek Cheon went silent. He had no response. It was true that he had never paid any attention to the third-class disciples’ training.

‘I always assumed that was Un Geom sasuk’s role and left it up to him.’

“But haven’t you already taken control of the third-class disciples’ training?”

“Why do you think that is?”

When Chung Myung asked back, Baek Cheon struggled to respond.

‘Why? Why….’

The reason is too simple. It was because the third-class disciples are the same rank as Chung Myung. It was annoying and troublesome now, but if they were raised well, then Chung Myung would be able to live without raising a finger in the future.

Baek Cheon sighed deeply.

“You mean that you want me to bow my head.”

“Ehh. You’re making me look bad. How could I dare think that?”

It was implied that you shouldn’t say it out loud even if you understand.

Baek Cheon hated that he understood what Chung Myung meant.

“… But we are still Mount Hua’s disciples.”

“Sasuk.”

“Yes?”

Chung Myung spoke calmly.

“Did you see the third-class disciples training?”

“… I did.”

They seemed barely human by the end, more like stones rolling around.

Just being alive seemed like a great achievement. But Baek Cheon didn’t say anything.

“Do you think I can make the sasuks do that?”

“…”

The answer was…

‘He could definitely treat them harshly; the only reason he holds himself back is so that he doesn’t get caught by others’

That’s what Baek Cheon thought, but he’s a smooth talker and knew that he shouldn’t say that out loud.

“It would be difficult since you’re a good person, but I think you’d somehow manage.”

“Yes, yes.”

‘What bullshit.’

Chung Myung just shrugged.

“But that’s why I can’t do it. I can make it work for the sahyungs, but I can’t do anything for my sasuks. If I do, would the first-class disciples let me continue?”

Baek Cheon looked at Chung Myung.

‘It’s possible.’

Chung Myung was pointing out the problems, but he never said it was impossible.

“Then, if all the problems are taken care of, you can make us stronger, right?”

“Haven’t you seen the results with your own eyes?”

Baek Cheon had certainly seen the results.

That was why he was here.

Baek Cheon took a deep breath.

Chung Myung had managed to train the third-class disciples to the point that they could overpower the Southern Edge Sect’s disciples and even defeated Jin Geum-Ryong and the other second-class disciples himself.

Not a single second-class disciple could even touch him.

Baek Cheon bit his lip tightly.

“I will fix that issue.”

“How?”

“During the training, we won’t be the sasuks. Those who receive guidance will be the disciples, and we will respect you as a teacher.”

“Wow.”

Chung Myung looked interested but shook his head while looking at Baek Cheon.

“That won’t be enough.”

“… why?”

“If you curse me after the training, then there is no way out for me.”

“…”

Baek Cheon spoke bluntly.

“No, we wouldn’t sink so low….”

“With just one day of training, you’ll change your words. Even the sahyungs were troublesome at first.”

Baek Cheon was at a loss of words.

“T-then what do I do?”

“If you’re going to do it, you need to make it clear.”

Chung Myung snapped his finger.

“If you want to learn, whether it’s time to train or not, you’ll have to bow to me. Then I’ll help. But if that doesn’t work, then I can’t do a thing for you. I need to be able to live here as well, you know.”

“…”

Baek Cheon agonized, but not for long.

‘Do I have any pride left?’

It was disgraceful to bow to a sajil. But it was a greater disgrace to be weak. And…

‘I want to be able to display that sword one day.’

The sword that destroyed Jin Gem-Ryong. Mount Hua’s sword was branded deeply into his memory.

“Fine.”

Baek Cheon answered firmly.

“From this moment on, you aren’t a sajil for the second-class disciples. Your title may be sajil, but none of the second-class disciples will attempt to use that against you. I guarantee it with my name on the line.”

‘Caught you!’

A happy smile crept onto Chung Myung’s lips.

He was thinking about how he could catch these idiots, but they jumped into the net with their own feet.

“Really?”

“Yes!”

“Are you sure?”

“Yes!”

“Alright. Then everyone will gather and come out tomorrow morning.”

“…”

“What?”

“Ah, no. nothing.’

Baek Cheon would only realize later on what a grave mistake he had made.

Chapter 116: Plum blossoms will cover the sky someday (1)

Dawn of the next day.

“… Sahyung.”

“…”

“Why are they here?”

“Well.”

‘How am I even supposed to answer that?’

Mount Hua’s third-class disciples trembled as they watched the second-class disciples approaching in the morning light.

Since Mount Hua is located on a high mountain, the morning air is rather cold. A white fog was created as warm breaths were exhaled against the frigid air. Compounded with the second-class disciples marching forward, the sight of it looked like aged warriors heading for the battlefield.

“Are we going to die today?”

“I doubt that would happen.”

Before long, all the second-class disciples came out and lined up across the third-class disciples.

Finally, Baek Cheon slowly walked out and stood at the front.

“Is everyone here?”

“Yes, Sahyung!”

“Yes.”

Baek Cheon lightly nodded and looked at everyone with a soft gaze before turning his sights to the sky.

‘No way.’

‘It can’t be.’

At that moment, the White Plum Blossom dorm door opened, and Chung Myung came out yawning.

“Ywan!! Why is it that I can never get enough sleep?”

‘Then just sleep in!’

‘Why don’t you just skip a day!? How can you complain like that and still train every day? Everyday!’

Chung Myung trudged out and approached Yoon Jong. As if he had been waiting for this, Yoon Jong quickly clung to Chung Myung and asked,

“Chung Myung. Why are they out here?”

“Ah. Sasuks.”

“Right. The sasuks!”

“Sahyung.”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung reached out and put his arm around Yoon Jong’s shoulder.

“You must have gone through so much trouble.”

“What’s this all of a sudden?”

“I know very well just how hard the sahyungs have suffered and been bullied by the sasuks.”

‘No, they’ve never done that.’

‘If we’ve ever been hit, it was always by you. Why are you suddenly dragging the sasuks into this?’

“But you can relax. From now on, we’ll live in a beautiful world where all people are equal, at least during training.”

“A place where all are equal?”

“Yes.”

“Isn’t that what happens in hell?”

“… Huh?”

‘That sounds plausible?’

Yoon Jong’s face contorted.

‘In the end, he even got the Baek disciples.’

This man’s beastly hands stretch out without end. How long had it been since he first drove the third-class disciples to hell? Now you are saying that he even has the second-class disciples in his hands?

‘What’s going to happen to Mount Hua?’

While Yoon Jong suppressed his rising sadness, Chung Myung went to the center.

“You’ve all worked hard getting here this early in the morning.”

“…”

“This instructor is very moved to see everyone ‘voluntarily’ participating in the training like this.”

‘Conscience-less bastard!’

‘When was the last time you let someone rest from training? Hell is going to have a grand time punishing you!’

The third-class disciples bit their lips, but the second-class disciples surprisingly didn’t show much of a reaction.

“Train hard. If you feel refreshed and rewarded after you’re done, then it can’t be called training. As soon as training ends, you will gasp, curse, and you won’t even have the strength to lift your chopsticks. You need to be prepared to shove your face onto your plate just to eat after experiencing real training.”

What encouraging words.

“There is no gentle path to becoming strong. Pushing harder and harder with your best effort is the only way to become strong. If you trust and follow this instructor, you will become strong. Do you understand?”

Yoon Jong’s face contorted.

‘No, he can’t act like that to the seniors… it will sting him back…!’

It was then!

“YESSSSS!”

The loud response from the second-class disciples made the third-class disciples step back in shock.

“W-what?”

“What is wrong with them?”

Being taught by someone, a sajil at that, who might be the age of their younger brother, must be embarrassing. But that didn’t seem to bother them at all.

‘It would be a disgrace if we fall behind the third-class disciples!’

It was shameful to receive Chung Myung’s training, but the thought of becoming weaker than all of the third-class disciples was frighteningly shameful.

But it was happening.

The second-class disciples were still stronger for now, but the third-class disciples would likely stand above them in a few years. How would they retain their pride and dignity if they allowed themselves to fall behind their juniors?

‘I can’t allow that to happen.’

‘I’d rather die than see that.’

The eyes of the second-class disciples were bloodshot.

Sometimes a person’s spirit is ignited the most by impure motives. No, to be precise, the more impure, the greater the motivation.

A pure desire for strength alone wouldn’t result in the second-class disciples going this far. Their pride and insecurity pushed their backs and moved their feet forward.

And lastly….

‘I don’t know how. But if we learn from that guy, we might be able to defeat the Southern Edge Sect’s second-class disciples.’

‘No, we can do more than that.’

‘It is better to be looked down on in the sect than to be ridiculed out in the world for being weak.’

‘Look at them.’

As he received the sparkling gazes of the second-class disciples, Chung Myung said,

“This is it!”

They were eyes that craved to learn!

Chung Myung was proud to see the second-class disciples burning with passion for learning while holding back their complaints. It was a refreshing change from the third-class disciples that were always gloomy and bitter.

Of course, the third-class disciples used to be brighter and more optimistic before he arrived, but Chung Myung didn’t think much about such things.

“Well then.”

Chung Myung smiled.

“The basics are important in anything. Let’s start with strength training. Sahyungs? What are you doing? You need to teach the seniors how the strength training is done.”

At those words, the rest of the third-class disciples also smiled.

“Ah, right.”

“Ahem. I will do my best.”

The third-class disciples’ eyes were gleaming in madness as if screaming,’ You should get a taste of it too.’

‘You thought this training would be good for you, didn’t you?’

‘If they try it once, their screams will be heard for at least three months.’

‘Their cries will make a wonderful song!’

The third-class disciples bore sinister smiles that made the second-class disciples anxious.

But unexpectedly, there was someone who came forward amid the impending crisis.

“Huh?”

Chung Myung tilted his head when he saw the person standing in front of him.

“What now?”

“To learn.”

“Learn from the kids over there.”

“No one came to me.”

“… Uh?”

Chung Myung tilted his head while looking at Yu Yiseol.

“No, why would no one… what are the sahyungs doing?”

The disciples heard Chung Myung and quickly turned away, looking at the dawning sky.

“To feel awkward just because she’s a woman… wait. Wait, come to think of it, why don’t we have any girls in our class? Why do we only have men? There are a lot of women among the Baek disciples.”

“…”

Chung Myung turned to Yoon Jong and said,

“No, Sahyung. Did you only accept men as disciples for our class? That’s why our dorm is so dark and gloomy.”

“Chung Myung.”

“Huh?”

Yoon Jong looked at Chung Myung and spoke with an expression that seemed as if he would cry tears of blood at any moment.

“There are some subjects in the world that shouldn’t be touched.”

“…”

Chung Myung looked at Yoon Jong for a long time and bowed his head.

“I was wrong. I apologize. Please forgive me.”

“… be careful from now.”

“I will.”

After apologizing, he looked at Yu Yiseol.

“I won’t think of you as a woman.”

“That’s what I was hoping for.”

“Even if you cry, I won’t go easy.”

“That won’t happen.”

No fear.

“Promise me one thing instead.”

“What?”

“If I endure this, will you teach me how to make the plum blossoms bloom on my sword?”

“Everyone is saying such strange things.”

Chung Myung spoke with a stiff face.

“If sahyungs and sasuks are the disciples of Mount Hua, you shouldn’t be aiming to make plum blossoms. That’s just a part of the process. What you should be aiming for is completion.”

“Completion…”

“Well, right. Then…”

Chung Myung shrugged.

“First, let’s build the foundation for enlightenment. Let’s go!”

Seeing the second-class disciples moving, Chung Myung smiled wickedly.

‘In the past, I only cared about my own skills and didn’t pay attention to my sajaes or sahyungs.’

Back then, Chung Myung took it for granted, but not now. Had he not realized it at the end? After all, Mount Hua’s opponent wasn’t just one strong man but an entire sect.

There were limits to what could be done alone.

What if one day they become strong enough to support Chung Myung?

“Kuhahaha. It’ll be done. A strong team, and then I’ll draw plum blossoms on the heads of the Shaolin.”

The disciples of Mount Hua, who thought they heard something they shouldn’t have, decided to close their ears and turn their heads.

“Ummm.”

Un Geom let out a pleasant sigh as he looked at the disciples of Mount Hua immersed in training.

‘Now it’s the Baek disciples?’

‘Well, this was bound to happen. After what they had seen, they must have had some complex feelings.’

Un Geom remembered the conversation he had with the sect leader yesterday.

- Leave him alone.

The sect leader continued.

- He is a child that we cannot restrain regardless. Interfering with that child may instead hinder his path and get in the way of what he has planned. We’re old. What we must do is make sure that the children are able to grow and shine in the future. So, we’ll leave it at that. That child is on the path of Dao, so I believe that he will never lead the others down the wrong path.

Hyun Jong believed that Un Geom shouldn’t poke around and make the child wary or question his intent for no reason.

Un Geom also agreed to it.

Chung Myung’s plum blossoms, incomprehensible skills, and unknown origins obscured the child in many mysteries. There were numerous questions, but Un Geom didn’t want to ask.

‘Path of Dao.’

The path of the Dao is to go with the flow and embrace what may come.

There was no reason why Chung Myung couldn’t have his way as long as he was a disciple of Mount Hua.

The path of a Dao is known to be large.

Rather…

‘Should I learn it too?’

After observing the children for a long time, Un Geom slowly turned away with a bitter smile.

‘I’m being greedy.’

Even if he could become stronger, Un Geom knew that it would be better for him to focus on his current task. He was already old now; it would be difficult to try and become stronger.

It was fortunate that the Baek disciples were still young enough to learn.

‘But I cannot just stay still and watch.’

How can he be lazy when the children are trying so hard? Even if he left teaching to Chung Myung, he should help teach them as much as he can.

“Mount Hua will grow stronger.”

‘The Southern Edge Sect isn’t the end.’

Mount Hua had changed since Chung Myung arrived. Un Geom also recently realized that he was being pulled into that flow.

Now, the atmosphere of the elders had begun to change.

At least these children shouldn’t be burdened. He had to do everything to help them.

And…

When the day comes that those children complete their martial arts path, the world will see the second coming of Mount Hua.

It was a far-off goal.

Un Geom turned his head slowly.

“Straighten your back and practice! Waist too! If you still have strength to breath, then you shouldn’t have a problem training! What? It’s fine! It’s fine! You won’t die from this! Have you ever heard of anyone dying from training? Just train!”

Un Geom trembled.

“Enough? Enough? Aigoo. Are you really saying that? Just because you mastered a little bit of martial arts? Maybe we should take a look at those martial arts of yours? Come on! Let’s see if it’s quicker to die from the training or from shame!”

Having seen the third-class disciples rush in to stop Chung Myung and assist with helping the others train, Un Geom stared off into the distant sky.

‘Maybe it isn’t that far-off after all.’

Chapter 117: Plum blossoms will cover the sky someday (2)

Chung Myung climbed the Lotus peak and looked up at the sky.

There was no longer any need to hide his training, but climbing up here calmed his mind, probably because this training had become a habit.

Chung Myung, who had been looking into the sky for a long time, turned around and looked at Mount Hua.

“Hmmm.”

He had overcome the first mountain.

But he wasn’t satisfied yet.

“We still have a long way to go.”

Even though he understood that impatience leads to anger, he secretly began to feel impatient.

The development of the third-class disciples wasn’t slow. If they continued at this rate, one day, they would become warriors that no one in the world dared to ignore.

However, that would be in the distant future.

Currently, Mount Hua is nothing more than a weak sect.

“This is the start.”

Chung Myung felt a tremendous weight bearing down on his shoulders. Now, the disciples would instinctively come looking for him whenever something happened. The same thing happened countless times in the past, but there was a clear difference between how his sahyungs looked at him then compared to the sahyungs now.

“Sahyungs must have had a tough time.”

It wasn’t difficult to push a leader’s back forward. However, even if they’re supported, it takes extreme courage to take the lead.

In the past, Chung Myung thought he was leading Mount Hua.

The most well-known figure from Mount Hua was the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, and it was his presence that secured Mount Hua’s dominance.

So, did Chung Myung really lead the sect?

‘No.’

His heart ached.

Back then, if Chung Myung had known what he understood now, perhaps Mount Hua’s fate would have been different. Not only Mount Hua’s descendants but Chung Myung’s sahyungs may have been saved as well.

Despite knowing they were walking to their deaths, they all calmly marched forward with a smile.

“It’s pointless.”

Chung Myung shook his head.

The past was already settled. What mattered now wasn’t lingering on past attachments but living in the present while using the past as a guide towards a better future.

To do that…

“More than anything, I need to be stronger.”

That was the only way to avoid losing everything, like in the past.

Chung Myung knew.

This world of martial arts is ruthless.

Agreement? Of course, it exists. Loyalty? That does too. However, those are simply powers that exist for the strong to bestow on the weak. Those that lack strength don’t have the opportunity to decide on the terms of any agreements, nor do they have the right to dare discuss loyalty.

Mount Hua’s disciples would likely think they’ve already experienced the world’s cruelty and heartlessness. They may mistakenly believe that Mount Hua has already suffered it all over the course of its collapse.

But it wasn’t the end.

Sooner or later, they will learn. They were protected by this rugged Mount Hua and protected by the deeds that Chung Myung and the former Mount Hua accomplished.

But that would all come to an end.

Mount Hua would enter the open world again. When that happens, they will face cruelty they have never seen before.

‘I have no intention of carrying it on my shoulders.’

Chung Myung needed to create a place for them to trust and rely on, whether it be Mount Hua or himself.

Sitting cross-legged, He closed his eyes and inspected his foundation.

He could see.

The dantian inside him had grown to the size of a small fruit. Compared to his previous dantian, this was like a small drop of blood.

But it was growing.

Slowly but surely, step by step.

Mount Hua’s martial arts were methodical.

It was an honest style that could be used to reach the peak by steadily advancing and overcoming each mountain with your own two feet.

There were no shortcuts.

‘I will get stronger.’

He would grow not as the Plum Blossom Sword Saint from the past but as Chung Myung in the present.

He would become stronger.

‘And one day, surpass ‘him,’ the Heavenly Demon.’

An endless journey towards perfection of nothingness.

Chung Myung quietly lifted his head and looked up.

- Have our plum blossoms bloomed?

Chung Myung.

“Not yet”

But…

“Someday, it will bloom.”

One day, when the plum blossoms truly bloomed on Chung Myung’s sword, not only Mount Hua but the entire world would be covered in their scent.

Chung Myung jumped up.

“Don’t worry, my Sahyung.”

Chung Myung laughed.

“I am Chung Myung.”

It was a subtle statement, spoken as if it was a commitment to himself.

Chung Myung slowly descended the mountain.

“Hmm?”

Chung Myung, who was heading down with a slight smile, widened his smile at the scent of plum blossoms coming from nearby.

“Has to be spring.”

Plum blossoms were blooming.

Basking in the scent that tickled his nose, Chung Myung continued his descent with lightened steps. Looking down at Chung Myung’s back reflected the figure that would silently continue to look after Mount Hua.

Time continued to flow ceaselessly as Mount Hua, which had embraced Chung Myung, began to embark on a new path.

The blossoms bloomed again, and then once more.

The plum blossoms bloomed twice and faded.

The years continued to flow like water running down a stream.

Hua-Um village.

Someone carrying their own luggage entered the village that was bustling with people.

“… is this Hua-Um?”

It was a man.

No, it was a face that looked closer to a boy than a man. He looked around with a slightly flustered face.

“Is this the right place?”

What he could see with his eyes seemed so different from the memories he knew.

The Hua-Um that he had seen in the past was a small place that was something between a town and a city. It wasn’t underdeveloped and had a prosperous history, but it wasn’t anything noteworthy and even seemed quite gloomy.

However, now it was no different from a busy city.

Of course, it couldn’t be compared to the big cities in terms of scale. However, the word ‘village’ seemed meaningless when newly built buildings lined the sides of the main streets and the shops overflowed with customers.

‘Did I come to the wrong place?’

So, he asked a passerby.

“Excuse me? Is this Hua-Um?”

“First time?”

“No. It’s not my first time. I came here once about a decade back, I think. It seems so different from then though.”

The passerby answered back in response.

“If it’s your first time back in ten years, then it makes sense that you’re confused. Even those coming back to Hua-Um after one or two years were shocked.”

“Ah… then this is Hua-Um.”

“Yes, it’s strange since it changed so much, but this is the Hua-Um you knew.”

“Thank you. But… Why has the village changed so much?”

“Why? All thanks to Mount Hua.”

“Huh?”

“You don’t know Mount Hua? Mount Hua? Mount Hua sect?”

“Ah-no. I know. I know about Mount Hua.”

The man. Wei Soheng nodded quickly.

If you told the people of Hua-Um that you don’t know Mount Hua, they would treat you as if you were inhuman. For the people here, Mount Hua was more than just a sect.

It was their pride and confidence, a family.

“I’m here to visit Mount Hua.”

“Oh? Is that so? You were a guest. Come on then, if you have any questions feel free to ask me, I can answer them.”

As soon as the man heard this man was here to visit Mount Hua, he smiled brightly.

“What did you mean when you said that Hua-Um changed because of Mount Hua?”

“It’s exactly as I said. These days Mount Hua’s influence is piercing the heavens! Haven’t you heard that their reputation is spreading everywhere?”

‘No, because I’m not from around here. But I don’t think he’d like me saying that.’

He couldn’t bring himself to say that to the man in front of him. If he said anything slightly ignorant about Mount Hua, it felt like this man would blow his chin off.

“R-right.”

“So recently, more and more people come to visit Mount Hua. As more and more people visit, they end up passing through Hua-Um. As you can see, it is pretty crowded, right?”

“Yes.”

“Where people gather, money flows. So, naturally this place changed.”

“… It’s quite a dramatic change.”

“Hahaha. All thanks to Mount Hua. You have to know, right? At the conference with the Southern Edge Sect two years back, Mount Hua smashed those bastards.”

“I know.”

It was a story that no one could avoid knowing even if they wanted to.

Known to have fallen… no, even the memory of the fallen Mount Hua had faded from people’s minds. That dying sect suddenly halted the Southern Edge Sect, which had been gaining momentum in recent years. With such a prestigious sect being humiliated, the news naturally traveled like lightning around the world.

Humans enjoy the misfortunes of others. It was a case of disgrace falling upon a well-known sect, so there was no reason that people wouldn’t talk about it.

Word traveled fast, and the news spread for thousands of miles as everyone discussed what happened to the Southern Edge Sect. Now, even the children playing in the neighborhood knew the story.

There were people who called it the Fallen Dragon Conference because the Southern Edge Sect that had ascended to heaven came crashing to the ground.

“The Southern Edge Sect, not any other sect, but THE Southern Edge Sect. How high has Mount Hua’s reputation soared after that incident? I can’t even fathom how many people have come to Mount Hua since then.

“I see.”

Wei Soheng nodded.

No one understood those words more than himself. After all, he had come here because of the change in Mount Hua’s status.

If the rumors of the conference hadn’t circulated, Wei Soheng would have never thought about coming here.

“It’s just a little unfortunate.”

“Huh?”

The man had a slightly annoyed expression.

“It’s been two years since then. Something needs to happen now.”

“Ahh…”

“Well, a giant doesn’t move so easily. Isn’t there a legend about the Great Bird that rested for a thousand years before traveling thousands of miles in a single flap of its wings? Perhaps our Mount Hua is like that too.”

It was a statement that carried an enormous sense of pride for Mount Hua.

Wei Soheng, who saw that, thought that a lot had changed.

It wasn’t just the appearance that changed.

When he visited this place in the past, it seemed devoid of vitality. But now, the people of Hua-Um are vibrant and full of life.

“If you are planning to visit Mount Hua, find a place to stay. The sun will set soon, and if you start the climb now, you’ll be climbing through the middle of the night. It would be better to start your journey tomorrow morning.”

“Yes. Thank you.”

“Sure.”

The elderly man waved his hand and walked away, and Wei Soheng mumbled.

‘It changed so much.’

The village had grown prosperous just because the sect gained a little fame. He started to understand why everyone, whether it be people or sects, was willing to risk their lives for fame.

Wei Soheng raised his head and looked at Mount Hua.

Looking at the transformed village, something became clear. The current Mount Hua is different from the Mount Hua that he knew of.

So…

‘We must somehow seek to cooperate with Mount Hua.’

Wei Soheng looked at Mount Hua with determined eyes.

- Mount Hua will surely help us. Go to Mount Hua and ask for help.

‘I hope my father’s judgment isn’t wrong.’

Wei Soheng bit his lip and quickly headed into the village.

Chapter 118: Plum blossoms will cover the sky someday (3)

“Kuaaak.”

Tak!

At last, Wei Soheng climbed the final hill and exhaled harshly.

‘What a steep mountain.’

As he felt before, this mountain didn’t make it easy for people to approach. Aside from being incredibly steep, the problem was that one also had to climb countless cliffs that were barely reachable in order to climb to the top.

However, he was able to climb the mountain more easily than expected.

Unlike how it was in the past, stakes were embedded in each cliff to make the climb easy. These stakes even had ropes connected to each other. The climb became much easier than scaling the bare cliff if one held onto the rope.

“Huk! Still, it is hard.”

Wei Soheng wiped the sweat from his forehead with his sleeve.

The Wudang Sect had a code that required those entering the sect to remove their weapons and dismount their horses. But there was no need for such rules on Mount Hua.

Because no horse could make this climb anyway.

That was why it was said that everyone who entered Mount Hua was equal.

Because everyone must walk the same rugged mountain path with their own hand and feet. That is how tough Mount Hua is.

“I don’t know who thought of it, but it was a great idea. It makes it easier for those climbing Mount Hua to understand their intentions.”

Mount Hua has a long history, so it wouldn’t have been strange for them to change this. The fact that they kept this tradition the same showed that they were still humble.

Sweaty and gasping, Wei Soheng finally set sights on the giant gate of Mount Hua.

“… why isn’t there a single thing that’s familiar?”

Even the gate was different from the past.

When he visited Mount Hua in the past, the collapsed gate remained so impressive that this new magnificent gate felt awkward to him.

At a glance, there were the words ‘Great Mount Hua Sect’ written in beautiful calligraphy. The moment he saw this signboard, he felt overwhelmed.

‘It’s definitely different from before.’

Even the rivers and mountains are known to change in ten years, wasn’t that more than enough time for a sect to change?

With anticipation rising in his bosom, Wei Soheng approached the gate.

There was no one guarding the large gate. Perhaps the gate was also firmly closed because it was still early.

Wei Soheng took a shaky breath and knocked on the great gate.

“Is anyone here!?”

Thud! Thud! Thud!

“I am here to visit the sect.”

‘Isn’t anyone here?’

He wondered if it was right to shout, but he couldn’t think of any other way.

“A guest wants to visit Mount Hua, is anyone here!?”

Wei Soheng tried to shout as politely as he possibly could. Soon, he stopped knocking and waited for someone to come.

‘If anyone had heard it, they should have come by now….’

Kiiik!

Unsurprisingly, the gate opened, and a man stuck his head out from inside.

Wei Soheng happily opened his mouth to speak but was quickly cut off before he had a chance.

“We aren’t taking any visitors today.”

“… Huh?”

“Mount Hua isn’t accepting any visitors today, please come back tomorrow.”

“Ah, I-I didn’t hear about such a thing.”

Well, he really did wonder why no one else was climbing the mountain today.

‘Seriously!?’

“Bye.”

“Wait, one moment!”

Wei Soheng shouted urgently.

“I’m sorry, but is there really no way? I need to see the sect leader of Mount Hua.”

“We aren’t allowing visitors today. If it isn’t too urgent, then tomorrow—”

“I–I’m not a visitor.”

“Hmm?”

Baek Sang, who opened the door, looked at Wei Soheng.

It was a man that Baek Sang had never seen before, but he said that he wasn’t a visitor?

“I am from Huayoung Gate.”

“Huayoung Gate?”

Baek Sang’s tone changed.

“Yes, I have to meet with the sect leader about matters concerning Huayoung Gate. Urgent matters. I know that it’s my fault for climbing the mountain without recognizing the situation, but could you please at least leave him a message for me?”

Baek Sang spoke in a polite tone.

“I apologize, but I have very limited knowledge and haven’t heard of Huayoung Gate.”

“That—”

“But I can’t know everything. I’ll head in right now and ask about Huayoung Gate and deliver this message to the sect leader right away.”

“Thank you!”

“Then, please wait for a moment.”

Baek Sang closed the door and went inside. Still, the worst was avoided, so Wei Soheng sighed.

‘Such an incredible presence.’

Going by his appearance, he wasn’t much older than Wei Soheng. Just standing in front of him made Wei Soheng feel as if a sword was being held against his throat. It made him wonder what would happen if he really did wield a sword.

‘So, this is Mount Hua?’

Wei Soheng nervously waited for Baek Sang.

‘What if they kick me out?’

As Wei Soheng realized that Mount Hua had changed, his anxiety grew. Now that Mount Hua had spread its wings and begun to make a name for itself, perhaps Huayoung Gate no longer mattered to them.

After all, it had been decades since they had communicated properly…

It was then.

Thud!

The door opened more violently than before, and Baek Sang rushed out with a stiff face.

“You said Huayoung Gate, right?”

“Yes? Ah… ah. Yes! Fro—from Huayoung Gate.”

“Please come inside. The sect leader said he’ll meet you right away.”

“Huh?”

“Come in!”

“Ah, yes!”

At the sudden change in attitude, Wei Soheng had a bewildered expression as he entered the sect along with Baek Sang.

‘I’m so nervous.’

Wei Soheng gulped.

Sitting across from him was Hyun Jong, the sect leader of Mount Hua, who was looking at him with a kind face.

For Wei Soheng, who was just a disciple of a small sect, simply facing the sect leader of Mount Hua was a sort of burden in itself.

And the burden didn’t end there.

To the left and right of Hyun Jong, dignified-looking people were seated.

‘How did it end up like this?’

Wei Soheng had rushed to Mount Hua as one final hope, but he didn’t think he would be given a chance to meet the leader of the sect.

But now that he was seeing the sect leader and elders, he couldn’t stop his pounding heart.

“Okay.”

Hyun Jong opened his mouth,

“You said that you came from the Huayoung gate?

“Yes, yes! Sect leader! I am Wei Soheng from Huayoung Gate.”

“Hm. I see. I am Hyun Jong, the sect leader of Mount Hua.”

“It’s an honor to meet you.”

Hyun Jong smiled.

“You don’t have to be nervous.”

“… I am naturally timid.”

Hyun Jong reached out and pointed to the tea.

“Then have some tea. It might calm you.”

“Thank you.”

Wei Soheng reached out and drank the tea, but he couldn’t even tell how it smelled or tasted; he was too nervous.

“Huayoung Gate. Huayoung Gate. I know that it was part of Mount Hua’s inner circle, but perhaps the last visit was around thirteen years ago?”

“You remember?”

“Of course, you must have been the little boy from back then.”

“Yes.”

At that time, he wasn’t nervous at all. Back then, he was at an age where he didn’t understand what it meant to climb Mount Hua.

‘Mount Hua was very different from how it is now.’

The changes in Mount Hua were an incredible shock. Wei Soheng, who entered the gate, looked at the majestic tiles in the training area and almost fainted.

Mount Hua, in his memories, was a desolate place that was crumbling. What could have happened in the last ten years to bring about such change?

The position makes the person… no, the clothes make the man…

‘Money gives a man wings!’

When Wei Soheng recognized the financial power of Mount Hua, he felt depressed. Was it possible for him to make such a request?

“Right. Let’s see why you had to come all the way here?”

“Yes. Sect leader, the thing is….”

He couldn’t speak so easily despite the chance being given.

Thud!

The door swung open, and an old man with a cold expression burst in.

“Huayoung Gate!? Did a person from Huayoung Gate come to visit, sect leader?”

“Give your greetings first when you—”

“Are you the person from Huayoung Gate!?”

Hyun Young fiercely looked at Wei Soheng, who nodded with a frightened face.

“Yes. I am…”

Before he could finish speaking, Hyun Young approached him and waved his arms.

‘Am I going to get hit!?’

Wei Soheng shut his eyes; however, Hyun Young smiled and tapped his shoulders.

“Huayoung Gate! Right Huayoung Gate came! Hahaha! Look at his dedication, he has to be a disciple from there!”

“…”

“What is it? Feel free to talk about it! Did you come because of any difficulties? Just say it, we’ll solve it!”

“…”

Wei Soheng was puzzled as he looked at Hyun Young.

What? What was this hospitality?

Hyun Jong, unable to watch this any longer, dissuaded Hyun Young.

“Won’t he be flustered if someone barges in and behaves like that?”

“Sect leader! This is the Huayoung Gate!”

“Right?”

Hyun Young smiled.

“Among all of our sub-sects, Huayoung Gate is the only one that has consistently sent money for us to use over the past thirty years! Now they’re all bringing money to cozy up to us. When we were struggling, others treated us like beggars, but Huayong Gate never neglected us! How often can one find such a loyal place?”

‘No, calling the sect a beggar in front of someone else….’

‘Think of the sect’s name….’

“Huayong Gate is the place that sent everything they could to help Mount Hua to meet our daily needs! They sent us money; you know? Money!”

“I know that….”

“There’s no other place like that. Huayoung Gate is the best of Mount Hua’s subsects! They’ve sent us money for over thirty years and never asked for anything in return! What a nice sect!”

His words were slowly becoming more radical, but it was understandable.

It didn’t matter how much money was sent. What mattered was that any additional help when Mount Hua was struggling surely helped to ease some of the sect’s worries, at least for a bit.

Money can always be paid back, but a debt of the heart can never be repaid. That was why Hyun Young appreciated them.

“Right. What is it? Are you short on money? Just tell me! I will lend it to you with a special low interest rate!”

“… Hyun Sang.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

When Hyun Sang got up, Hyun Young squinted his eyes and closed his mouth.

“Ah, I get it. I should shut up, right?”

Hyun Young, who said that, quickly sat in his seat.

Hyun Jong sighed deeply.

‘When will he grow up?’

To be precise, he wondered whether or not Hyun Young would return to how he once was. Hyun Young’s character flew out the window with the appearance of Chung Myung, and he still hadn’t returned to normal, even after all this time!

“You seem less nervous now. What happened for you to come to Mount Hua?”

“Yes, Sect leader.”

Wei Soheng took a deep breath and spoke.

“Huayoung Gate has a request. So, my father sent me to ask for help from the Sect leader.”

“What kind of help?”

“Chung Myung.”

“…Huh?”

Wei Soheng spoke with a bit of power.

“We want to take disciple Chung Myung, Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon.”

As soon as the name Chung Myung came out, a deep grimace began to spread on the faces of everyone there.

Chapter 119: Plum blossoms will cover the sky someday (4)

“Chung Myung?”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“… look here. Was it Wei Soheng?”

“Yes, Sect leader.”

“Rather than jumping to the main point, why don’t you explain the situation first??”

“Ah. Sorry. I wasn’t thinking straight. The situation…”

Wei Soheng began to explain what happened.

Huayoung Gate^1 is a sub-sect of Mount Hua.

Generally, the disciples of a large sect are divided into two categories. The first is the full-time disciples that have decided to live and dedicate their lives to Mount Hua. Those who become full-time disciples receive their names from the sect and are raised within Mount Hua to polish their swords and pursue the Tao.

However, the second category is the temporary disciples. These disciples study and learn from Mount Hua but eventually leave and head out into the world.

A sect founded by such a disciple is called a sub-sect or family sect. Although separate from Mount Hua, these sub-sects are bound to be operated under Mount Hua’s influence.

The sub-sects send a reasonable amount of money to the main sect every year, and in return, the sect leader solves various difficulties that the sub-sect faces. It was a good system as it provided an additional source of income for the main sect, while the sub-sects received more prospective disciples by using the main sect’s name. At times, the main sect would even send some disciples to assist in training the disciples in the sub-sects.

It was said that Mount Hua had hundreds of such sub-sects back in its heyday, but now there were no more than ten left.

Even the remaining sub-sects failed to properly communicate with the main sect.

On the other hand, Huayoung Gate had consistently sent money to Mount Hua.

“It’s not a sect that’s particularly accomplished in the martial arts, but Huayoung Gate has continued to recognize Mount Hua for what we are.”

“Right. That’s the kind of place Huayoung Gate is.”

“The problem started with the opening of a new martial arts training center that was set up across the street called Path’s Edge Training. As soon as the sect established itself as a sub-sect of the Wudang sect, it began to vigorously attract young potential.”

“Hmm.”

“But because of Huayoung Gate’s influence in the region of Nanyang, there was a lack of response toward the training hall. Unfortunately, this caused them to begin viciously hunting us down.”

“Hmm.”

“My father, who couldn’t stand their harassment and constant provocations, was defeated and badly injured by the master of the Path’s Edge.”

“O-Oh my god!”

Hyun Young jumped up from his seat.

“A great man like Huayoung Gate’s master was injured!? We need to catch that bastard, chew him up, and spit him out right now….”

Hyun Sang pulled Hyun Young’s sleeve.

Hyun Young, who was forced to sit down, ground his teeth as he seethed in a fit of persistent anger.

“If it ended there, then I wouldn’t have come all this way. However, the Path’s Edge training hall said that they planned to completely drive us out of Nanyang. They’ve even requested assistance from the Wudang sect. So, my father sent me here to meet with the sect leader and ask for help.”

After saying that, Wei Soheng dropped to the floor and bowed down.

“Sect leader! Please help us! If Mount Hua doesn’t help, then Huayoung Gate will have to lower its signboard and cease to be.”

“Hmmm.”

Hyun Jong heard all of it and sighed.

“So, the Path’s Edge training hall is affiliated with the Wudang sect?”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“Haaa. How can they do that to a fellow sect that seeks the path of dao…?”

Hyun Young snorted at Hyun Jong’s sigh.

“What nonsense is that! What sort of place is the Wudang sect? It’s the richest sect in the world. You can’t believe that the money in their pockets came from selling incense or their own purses? They are the most poisonous group one can find when it comes to expanding their power.”

“Hmm.”

Hyun Jong nodded.

‘Power…’

Clearly, this wasn’t something that could be overlooked.

The issue of their sub-sect being attacked by the Wudang was a secondary concern.

‘Now is the time for Mount Hua to look outside.’

The number of sub-sects one has is an indication of how strong the main sect is. A strong sect has many, while a weak sect has few.

If Mount Hua wants to regain its former glory, it can no longer work alone. Soon, there would be second-class disciples who wished to descend and leave the mountain. If they started a sub-sect, shouldn’t Mount Hua be supportive?

This wasn’t a simple task. Furthermore, this was a problem that would determine how the world viewed Mount Hua.

As Hyun Jong fell into thought, words began to flow from those around him.

“Shouldn’t we help?”

“It isn’t easy to help. After all, there’s an unwritten rule that only the main sect’s younger generations can get involved in fights between sub-sects, right?”

“R-right.”

There have often been cases of children quarreling, escalating into fights among the adults. What began as a problem for a sub-sect quickly turned into a war between the main sects. As a result, the Kangho^2 came to an implicit agreement that matters involving sub-sects should never escalate beyond the main sect sending second-class disciples to prevent any unnecessary damage.

This also served as a way to send children into the world to gain experience, rather than the older generation that has already completed their paths.

“If we send assistance, then it would be right to send the second-class disciples. How does sending the Baek disciples sound?”

“Umm.”

“And…”

It was then.

“That…”

Wei Soheng, who was listening to the conversation, hesitantly opened his mouth.

“Can’t you send the third-class disciples?”

“….”

“My father made an earnest request. I need to bring Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon, Chung Myung… maybe disciple Chung Myung is the only one….”

Hyun Jong’s face turned pale.

“That… well, you want to take Chung Myung?”

“I would like to, if possible.”

“Um. Right. Well… that’s good. Uh… yeah.”

The elders said it was fine, but their faces seemed to say it was anything but fine.

“Okay. For now, I understand the situation. There’s something we need to discuss, so please wait outside for a moment.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

Un Geom took Wei Soheng outside, and Hyun Jong spoke with a seriously stiff face.

“What do we do?”

“It’s nothing to worry about!”

Hyun Young yelled.

“This is the Huayoung Gate! The same Huayoung Gate that sent us money during our darkest hour when we struggled to make a living and nearly died! No matter what the situation is, grace is grace! We need to release the children and go bite those bastards!”

“… we aren’t dogs. Why would we bite them?”

“Is there anything worse than a dog?”

That’s the problem.

That’s the very problem!

Hyun Sang spoke with a serious face.

“Sect leader sahyung. This isn’t a matter that we can casually jump into. Isn’t our opponent the Wudang sect?”

“Well…”

“Wudang is a tough opponent. No matter how far removed from the main sect their sub-sect’s problems may be, the Wudang sect is known to always send their best to sort the issues out. You never know how things may turn out.”

“That’s true.”

When you think about it, such an unwritten rule was established because conflicts between sub-sects often spread further and escalated.

“I feel bad for the Huayoung Gate, but there needs to be another way to help them. I want to avoid sending our disciples to collide with them.”

It was a bit harsh, but it wasn’t like Hyun Sang wanted Huayoung Gate to suffer. No sect in the world would want to clash with the Wudang sect.

Where is Wudang?

Wasn’t it the leader of the north, known for their incredible strength?

Hyun Jong looked at Un Am.

“What do you think?”

“Sect leader.”

Un Am took a deep breath and began to speak.

“There are two things to think about. The first is whether now is the right time for our sect to resume external activities. Whatever our opinion is, if Mount Hua sends disciples to confront the Wudang sect, then the rest of the world will believe that we’ve resumed our foreign activities.”

“Right.”

“The second question is whether our children will be able to handle the disciples of Wudang.”

“Well, that…”

Hyun Sang didn’t think it was a huge issue, and Un Am said,

“Actually, there is a third.”

“Third?”

“Can we really release him?”

“…”

Sympathy and anxiety manifested themselves on everyone’s faces in unison.

“Sect leader. Actually, what that child said earlier is correct. If we need to send someone, we have no choice but to send Chung Myung. Right?”

“R-right.”

“But can we let him enter the Kangho? What’s more, against Wudang?”

“Ugh.”

Hyun Jong scratched his head in disbelief. His neatly combed hair was in a mess.

Two years was not a short time.

At this point, everyone fully understood what sort of person Chung Myung is. Choosing to send him down the mountain was a great burden on all of them.

“Un Geom.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“What do you think?”

Un Geom smiled slightly.

“There is nothing to think about. Send him.”

“… send him?”

“Is there a reason not to let him go? Chung Myung will have to enter the Kangho someday. Delaying this won’t solve anything. If he could become a master and walk the path of Dao in a couple months, then I would also be opposed to it. But don’t we all know that’s an undesirable dream?”

“….”

“Then we should let him go. It’s better to set sail early.”

Hyun Jong laughed.

“Right.”

What a wise answer.

Hyun Jong closed his eyes for a moment and then nodded as he spoke.

“Call for Yoon Jong.”

Yoon Jong soon entered together with Wei Soheng, who was outside and paid his respects to the sect leader.

“I was called?”

“What is Chung Myung doing now?”

“He recently entered closed-door training and hasn’t come out yet.”

“How much longer will he be?”

“It may be close to being done.”

“Hmm. I see.”

Hyun Jong’s gaze alternated between Yoon Jong and Wei Soheng.

“Yoon Jong.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“It seems like Chung Myung is needed, so let’s call his training to an end and have him come out.”

“Yes.”

“On the way, you will guide the guest from Huayoung Gate. Chung Myung will probably have to travel a long way with them, so make sure to introduce them appropriately.”

Yoon Jong flinched.

“… you said it was a long way?”

“Yes.”

“So, Chung Myung will be going a long way out?”

“Yes.”

A slightly irreverent light flickered in Yoon Jong’s eyes.

If that light could be translated into words, it would say

‘Are you all crazy?’

But no matter how shocked he was, he couldn’t speak those words out loud.

“… I understand.”

Yoon Jong, who couldn’t speak his true thoughts, made his intentions clear by speaking in a different tone.

“Then, let’s go.”

“Ah… ah, yes!”

Wei Soheng followed Yoon Jong. Hyun Jong let out a low sigh as he watched Yoon Jong leave.

‘I don’t know if this is good.’

But this was a sign.

Wei Soheng glanced at Yoon Jong walking next to him.

‘He seems to be the same age as me.’

‘Or maybe a couple years younger.’

But just because they were similar in age didn’t mean that their skills were equivalent. The atmosphere around Yoon Jong was like a lake.

Quiet and deep, like being submerged in a lake.

It made Wei Soheng realize that Mount Hua was genuinely superior. This was the difference between a disciple of the main sect and one from a sub-sect. Wei Soheng was in a state of admiration for this disciple, who was even younger than himself.

“Excuse me…”

“What is it?”

“What kind of person is Mr. Chung Myung?”

“…”

Yoon Jong’s eyes slightly trembled when he heard this question.

In his excitement to know more, Wei Soheng didn’t seem to notice and continued.

“Everyone knows the name of Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon, Chung Myung. But, after the Fallen Dragon Confere—I mean, after the Mount Hua–Southern Edge Sect conference, there hasn’t been any word about him. So, everyone wonders about what kind of person Chung Myung could be… some say that he’s a great person….”

“…. A great person?”

“Yes!”

“Is that what others think?”

“Yes. Right! What kind of person is Mr. Chung Myung?”

“… evil.”

“Huh?”

“I think it would be better for you to experience it yourself, rather than hear it from me.”

“Ahh…”

Yoon Jong, who was walking ahead, thought to himself.

‘Great person, my ass! He’s a bastard! If that guy is a great person, then I’m Confucius.’

Wei Soheng seemed to hear Yoon Jong mumbling to himself, but…

‘I must have misheard him just now.’

It was difficult to think that such an austere-looking disciple could say such a thing.

After leaving the sect and climbing the mountain for a long time, the two arrived at a large cliff. It seemed like a bloody cliff.

“Here?”

“This is Plum Blossom Peak. It’s a place we go in order to isolate ourselves from human resources, train, and seek enlightenment.”

“Disciple Chung Myung is seeking enlightenment?”

“… you can think that.”

Yoon Jong, who was about to say something else, shook his head.

‘He has to experience it to understand.’

“Wait for a moment, I will call Chung Myung.”

“Ah, of course!”

Yoon Jong left Wei Soheng and went forward. He stood in front of a huge cave that was blocked by a massive boulder, and then… let out a deep sigh.

Soon after

“… Chung Myung.”

A whisper so quiet that a mosquito’s buzzing would drown it out.

“Chung Myung.”

If someone could hear such a tiny whisper from inside that cave, rather than a person, wouldn’t that be a ghost?

While Wei Soheng wondered what the hell Yoon Jong was doing, Yoon Jong whispered again.

“Chung Myung?”

Finally, Yoon Jong quickly turned around and ran back to Wei Soheng.

“It seems like Chung Myung is deeply engrossed in his training and can’t hear me, so we might not see him today.”

“What?”

‘What bullshit!’

‘How could anyone hear your whispering from inside that cave?’

“Ah, no disciple.”

Yoon Jong put his index finger on his lips.

“This is good for both of us. Let’s just pretend we don’t know anything about this. I’m not doing this for me, I’m—.”

It was at that moment.

Baaaaang!

An explosive sound roared out as if the sky was collapsing. The boulder blocking that huge cave exploded and shattered everywhere.

“… kuak.”

Wei Soheng panicked, but Yoon Jong just covered his face with both hands.

The entire area was filled with dust.

Wei Soheng looked at the scene around him with a blank face.

A vaguely human silhouette began to emerge from the cloud of dust.

Step!

Step.

Hearing the daunting footsteps approaching, Wei Soheng had a gut feeling.

‘That man is Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon!’

One of the world’s most prominent young geniuses, who defeated ten of the Southern Edge Sect’s second-class disciples single-handedly! His reputation may be even greater than Mount Hua’s.

The silhouette in the dust became clearer and more human as the form stepped closer. Leaving the dust cloud behind, Chung Myung walked out like a hero from legends before looking at Wei Soheng.

‘It feels overwhelming.’

‘This man is the—’

It was then.

“Ah! Shit! I almost died in that place! This is why I didn’t want to do the closed door training! I cannot! I cannot eat and live off those pills! I cannot! I will not! Change the training!”

“….”

‘Ah,’

‘I guess it’s not him after all.’

‘No way.’

Chapter 120: Plum blossoms will cover the sky someday (5)

He was taller than expected.

Wei Soheng knew that Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon was very young, but he seemed larger than anticipated.

But he wasn’t too tall. Overall, he seemed very solid, and…

‘He’s handsome?’

Pretty decent.

With a well-balanced body that harmonized with his appearance, anyone would nod in approval of his looks.

…except for that expression of annoyance and disappointment that he wore.

“Cough! Cough! Ehhh! Why is it so dusty!?”

‘Didn’t you cause that?’

‘Why did you do it if you were just going to get annoyed by it?’

Chung Myung wore a faded uniform and brushed his robes to shake off the dust. He then looked at Yoon Jong with a sour expression.

“Is it today?”

“No.”

“Huh? It isn’t today?”

“There were three days left.”

“Then why?”

“Sect leader was looking for you.”

“Kuak! Sect leader is always so kind to me, he even released me from the closed training early! Sahyung. Sahyung you shouldn’t do this training. I’ve been eating those fasting pills for three months and I feel like they’ve started sprouting in my stomach.”

“… no, it seems like something’s come up.”

“Huh? What happened?”

Chung Myung tilted his head and turned to look at Wei Soheng.

“Who is he?”

“Wei Soheng from the Huayoung Gate.”

“Huayoung Gate?”

“You know about it?”

“…. How would I know anything?”

After saying that, Chung Myung looked at Wei Soheng.

‘Huayoung Gate.’

‘There was a Huayoung Gate in the past too.’

‘I thought that with Mount Hua being ruined, those places would have collapsed as well.’

The rise and fall of a sub-sect depended on the main sect.

Since Mount Hua fell, they must have had a hard time even raising their signboard and accepting disciples. It was surprising that they still existed.

“Huayoung Gate is a sub-sect of Mount Hua.”

“Oh, really? But why are you here?”

“Let’s go see the sect leader and hear from him.”

“Well, sure.”

When they were talking, Wei Soheng looked at Chung Myung with wide eyes. After a while, he looked at Yoon Jong and asked.

“Is… this the person?”

“I’m Chung Myung.”

“Oh, yes. Hahaha. I thought so…. What?”

‘This bastard… no, this person?’

‘This man here?’

Wei Soheng seemed flustered.

When he saw Yoon Jong, he sensed a deep presence that belonged to Mount Hua. Didn’t it feel like what a true master should be? To see a man whose entire body seemed to exude the aura of a true Taoist. Wasn’t the depth of his character what it meant to be a disciple here?

But this other person…

‘He seems like a back-alley thug!’

Without Yoon Jong around, Wei Soheng felt like he would be caught by his neck and dragged into the cave. He carefully guarded his belongings, as he was worried that they would be stolen.

Stimulated by sad memories from his childhood, Wei Soheng looked at Chung Myung hesitantly.

‘Were the rumors wrong?’

This person didn’t seem like someone who could destroy the Southern Edge sect’s disciples and defeat Jin Geum-Ryong.

“For now, wash up, and then come to see the sect leader.”

“Why?”

“Please.”

“Fine, fine. I’ll be back after washing up then.”

As Chung Myung walked away, Wei Soheng quickly asked Yoon Jong.

“… he’s Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon?”

“I don’t know about any dragon, but if you’re talking about Chung Myung, that’s him.”

“… really?”

“Evil.”

“Yes?”

“… don’t act so surprised. There’s still a lot to come.”

Wei Soheng couldn’t bring himself to ask what more was left; fear was already gripping him.

“So.”

Having tidied his appearance, Chung Myung sat in front of the sect leader and frowned.

“It wasn’t enough for the Wudang sub-sect bastards to attack our sub-sect bastards, so they called for a bitch from the main sect?”

“… you’re a disciple too.”

‘Why are you calling them a bitch? Do you know what you’re saying!?’

But Chung Myung didn’t even listen to Yoon Jong.

“So, they asked for help.”

Chung Myung nodded, and a serious light flashed in his eyes.

“Sect leader!”

“Hmm!”

“Don’t worry about it. This disciple will go, clean up the mess, and return!”

Everyone present flinched when they heard those words.

Chung Myung spent the last three months training without even seeing the light of day. How could he suddenly say something so trustworthy?

But even if everyone else was deceived, Yoon Jong wasn’t.

“… and how are you going to clean this mess up?”

“What do you mean how!? I’m going to run to Nanyang or wherever and then… Edge… was it Southern Edge training?”

“Path’s Edge training!”

“Ah, right! We can just crack their skulls and kick down the Wudang as well, that should be enough! Then I’ll set fire to the training hall so they can never set foot in Nanyang again. It’ll be super efficient!”

“That is a Taoist training hall, you idiot!”

“Do Taoist sects not burn? They definitely burn! Every building in this world is equal before a glorious inferno! Even Mount Hua is equal.”

“Why are you bringing up Mount Hua!?”

“Why? We might also burn; don’t you think so?”

Hyun Jong smiled with a happy face and then looked at Un Geom, who was sitting next to him and asked.

‘Can we really send him?’

‘I think we need to reconsider.’

How can a person grow older without ever-changing?

It wasn’t easy to be consistent like Chung Myung.

Yoon Jong pulled at Chung Myung’s clothes.

“Calm down. Please.”

“Huh? But I am calm.”

Chung Myung blinked his eyes.

“You said that Huayoung Gate is the only place that kept paying Mount Hua a lot of money, right?”

‘It’s not just a place that gave us money… it’s a sub-sect of our sect! Surely, it gave money but….’

“The main branch is supposed to protect the children that pay their bills properly! Otherwise, we shouldn’t take their money!”

“Right! We shouldn’t take the money!”

Hyun Young clapped. And when everyone’s eyes fell on him, he coughed lightly and lowered his hands.

Chung Myung continued to speak.

“Weren’t they the ones that started the fight? Then we need to accept it! Leave it to me! I’ll go and break their heads!”

Hyun Jong smiled and said,

“Chung Myung.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“… you shouldn’t break the heads.”

“How about their waists?”

“I mean that you shouldn’t seriously injure or crippled anyone.”

“…”

Hyun Jong sighed deeply before looking at Chung Myung and thinking to himself.

‘Is it really fine to let this brat go?’

However, regardless of any concerns, it was impossible to exclude Chung Myung from this situation. Aside from his personality, Chung Myung is the one person that can definitely resolve the problem.

“Anyway, that’s the current situation, so you should go.”

“Don’t worry. I will clean it up and come back. Shall we leave now?”

“A few more children will go with you. Start your journey tomorrow or the day after.”

“Won’t it take too long to arrive?”

“We need to investigate a bit more into this matter, there are a few things that are bothering me. So, be mindful of that, okay?”

“Yes.”

Whether they departed tomorrow or the day after, the only thing Chung Myung was worrying about was that he couldn’t beat the Wudang sect bastards until after he arrived!

“Right. You must have gone through a lot during your closed-door training, get some rest and recover.”

“I understand, sect leader.”

“Right. Go. We’ll decide which disciples will journey with you and inform you later.”

“Yes, of course.”

Hyun Jong suddenly called out as Chung Myung was about to head outside.

“Chung Myung.”

“Yes?”

Chung Myung turned his head, and Hyun Jong looked at him carefully before asking.

“Has your training yielded any results?”

Chung Myung chuckled.

“The Wudang bastards will experience it with their bodies.”

“Ah, I see.”

Chung Myung then bowed and left.

“Yoon Jong, please show Wei Soheng his accommodations. I’m sure he must be hungry as well, so get him something to eat.”

“Yes, sect leader. I will make sure he doesn’t feel inconvenienced.”

Hyun Jong had a subtle expression as Yoon Jong and Wei Soheng walked outside.

“Hyun Sang.”

“Yes, sect leader sahyung.”

“I don’t know if I’m just saying this because I am getting old, but do you think it’s a coincidence that the Wudang’s sub-sect came to Nanyang, where we haven’t had any problems in ages, and suddenly picked a fight with our Huayoung Gate?”

Hyun Sang didn’t respond.

This could have happened by chance. But the more they thought about it, the more it felt like some sort of scheme.

“I’m not sure if sending Chung Myung is the correct choice, if that’s what they’re after….”

“That can’t be, sect leader.”

Un Am shook his head.

“It’s a bit much to think that they’d be scheming to ensnare Chung Myung by picking this fight. Aren’t they the Wudang sect? They don’t need to pick a fight with Mount Hua. They have nothing to gain here, right? Why would such a great sect focus their efforts on such a small area like Nanyang?”

“Well…”

Hyun Jong sighed.

However, a deep worry inside his heart didn’t let him agree with Un Am’s words.

“Since the last conference Chung Myung’s name has spread rapidly. Now, he stands at the head of any discussions concerning the top geniuses in the world.”

“Right.”

“Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon is too grand a title, too exaggerated. The Wudang sect may not care about the petty benefits in Nanyang, but they’re a sect that cannot tolerate when another sect’s disciples overshadow their own. Maybe…”

It was then.

“So what?”

“Huh?”

Un Geom smiled and spoke.

“Sect leader. Do you know what the children of Mount Hua call Chung Myung?”

“… does he have some nickname?”

“Mount Hua’s Mad Dog.”

‘Uh… that’s a bit….’

Un Am, who had been silently listening, gulped.

“Mad dog is a bit too much, maybe we should go with blind dog?”

‘That’s still a dog!’

‘No, why is no one moving away from the dog?’

First, it was a mad dog, and now it’s become a blind dog.

Un Geom smiled.

“For the past two years, our children have been working really hard. Now, whether it be the Wudang sect or the Shaolin, they cannot ignore our children.”

“Yes.”

“Well, that is true.”

Everyone here understood just how much the second and third-class disciples had accomplished over the past two years. To be honest, it was mostly Chung Myung that taught the others, rather than Un Geom.

“Among them, that guy is….”

Un Geom scratched his head with a face that showed how he struggled to find the words to explain Chung Myung’s growth.

“Well, anyway. Those who dare to challenge Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon will understand why he has that name.”

“Divine Dragon?”

“No, Mad Dog.”

“…”

It shouldn’t be like this, but it was difficult not to sympathize with that nickname.

“Send Baek Cheon and Yoon Jong with him. If those two are there, they should be able to stop him when he begins to act up.”

“… Really?”

“Out of everyone, they have the best odds.”

“Then why don’t we send Yu Yiseol too? She might be able to restrain him a little.”

Wasn’t that too obvious?

“Sect leader.”

Hyun Young began to speak his mind,

“Sending the children isn’t everything. Sending the children means that Mount Hua is stepping out into the world and that means that a lot of work will come our way.”

“Yes!”

Hyun Jong nodded and said,

“Listen.”

“Yes, sect leader.”

“If our main mountain is the face of Mount Hua, then the sub-sects are like the hands and feet of Mount Hua. Huayoung Gate has made a great contribution to us till now. We must do everything we can to support them. We must let the world know that Mount Hua will not abandon our own.”

“We will remember your words, sect leader!”

Seeing the others bow their heads in unison, Hyun Jong’s face was filled with determination.

‘Two years is not a short period of time.’

Now was the time to announce to the world that Mount Hua’s image had changed.

Chapter 121: I’ll show you what happens when you touch Mount Hua! (1)

"…"

Wei Soheng looked around with a puzzled face.

'These are the people of Mount Hua.'

It was common for sub-sects to keep the same disciple distribution as the main sect. In that sense, Wei Soheng could also be considered a third-class disciple.

Until he arrived at Mount Hua, he thought that there would be nothing special about being a disciple of the main sect. However, seeing those gathered here, he could see how wrong his thoughts were.

'Every single one of them feels like the blade of a sword, such a sharp essence.'

Now he seemed to understand why his father always emphasized Mount Hua's prestige.

Despite being similar ages, there was a clear difference between them and him. There was dignity in each of their movements and the subtle taste of Taoism in each gaze.

Even when eating.

It wasn't easy to maintain an air of modesty while eating; that's why he believed the sect lived up to its prestige.

Nom! Nom! Nom!

Nom! Nom! Nom!

"…"

Wei Soheng turned his gaze to the side.

While everyone was eating in a well-mannered fashion, only one person in the corner was violently binging on his food.

'I don't understand.'

Chicken legs vanished into that man's mouth in an instant. It was impossible to understand just how he could clean the bone so well.

'Did he hear me?'

Even stranger was the fact that no one criticized the person for eating so loudly. Everyone simply acted as if that ravenous glutton in the corner didn't exist.

'Is that person really Mount Hua's Divine Dragon?'

Wei Soheng looked at Chung Myung in disbelief.

Of course, his appearance is fine. No, just looking at his appearance, the title suited him very well.

The problem was that only his appearance was acceptable.

Chung Myung's personality lacked the majesty to match his glorious title.

'Were the rumors wrong?'

That was impossible.

Rumors were typically more exaggerated than reality, but they couldn't be this time. The Southern Edge sect wouldn't sit still if the rumors were exaggerated.

The Southern Edge sect's silence was evidence that this man's achievements were true.

'So, he must be the person that beat up the Southern Edge sect's second-class disciples.'

Wei Soheng scratched his head.

Of course, each person had their own inclinations, but shouldn't there at least be a certain level of dignity that a warrior should maintain?

However, Chung Myung seemed to lack even the slightest poise of excellence befitting a warrior. If he was stripped of Mount Hua's uniform, then he could easily be mistaken for a common thug from the back alleys.

'Is it really okay to take that person with me?'

Just then, the door opened, and a man entered.

Yoon Jong.

Wei Soheng unconsciously sighed as he watched him approach.

'I'd rather believe that he's the Divine Dragon.'

Wei Soheng would have raised his hands and cheered for him!

That man called Yoon Jong had everything Wei Soheng hoped for from Mount Hua's Divine Dragon. The refined bearing of a young disciple, the vigorous energy felt in his presence, and his soft yet relaxed expression.

Wasn't this the ideal appearance that anyone would expect?

'But why did that guy have to be the Divine Dragon?'

Yoon Jong approached Chung Myung and frowned.

"Waah. You're going to get a stomachache. Eat slowly."

"I'm trying to make up for the months I missed."

"… did you starve yourself for three months?"

Chung Myung gulped down his food and drank a glass of cold water that was next to him. After putting the glass down, he patted his stomach and responded.

"I lived off those pills for three months straight, now even the air tastes like those pills."

"…"

"Oh, man. People should eat meat! I don't know how those Shaolin bastards survive on grass!"

'We also used to live off grass just two years ago, you bastard!'

Well, it was Chung Myung who changed that.

"So, did you have any success?"

"Success."

Chung Myung smiled.

He just needed some time.

Chung Myung's martial arts were a bit different from his previous life. Since his foundation changed, the development built on that foundation must also take a different shape from the past.

So, he needed a little time to sort those things out without worrying about other matters.

"Did the training go well while I was away?"

"…"

Yoon Jong looked around with a sullen face.

The resentful gazes of his sajaes fell on.

'I thought there were still a few days left, why did you bring that guy out!?'

'For three months I got to live like a human! Those good old days are gone, damn it!'

'We should have blocked that cave with something stronger!'

Yoon Jong sighed deeply and said,

"Everyone trained hard."

"Huh? Is that so?"

As Chung Myung started to get riled up, Yoon Jong decided to change the topic.

"That's not important now. Huayoung Gate is what's important."

"Ah, yes! Those Wudang bastards."

Chung Myung's face contorted.

"We need to break those bastards' heads! Sahyung, when do we leave?"

"Sect leader told us to leave tomorrow morning."

"Tomorrow? That's earlier than he said."

"The situation there is probably urgent. If someone from the Wudang sect has already departed, they might arrive soon. If we arrive too late, you won't be able to hit their heads, right?"

"Right!"

"So, when you are done eating, go pack your bags. We need to leave as soon as possible!"

"Okay!"

Chung Myung got up from his seat and went outside, and the third-class disciples around all let out a sigh of relief.

"… I thought I was going to die."

"This isn't living. Seriously."

The back door to the cafeteria opened, and someone slightly poked their head inside. They briefly glanced around before quietly asking.

"Did he leave?"

"… Yes."

"Haaa…"

Baek Sang opened the door and walked inside. Behind him, two second-class disciples followed behind with gloomy faces.

"I can't even eat a single meal in peace! A single meal!"

"I don't get it! There were a couple more days before he was supposed to come back! Why did he get out early!?"

"Peace is dead. I want to die."

"…"

Watching this, Wei Soheng couldn't understand what was happening at all. He was about to burst from curiosity.

'What the hell is going on?'

From the looks of it, Chung Myung was the youngest of them all. The sahyungs clearly understood that, but even the second-class disciples seemed uncomfortable with Chung Myung.

'I'd heard that the difference between junior and senior was very clear."

Wei Soheng's shaky gaze met with Yoon Jong.

"Uh… disciple Yoon Jong."

"Oh."

Yoon Jong looked at Wei Soheng and scratched his head.

"I wonder how this works…."

Yoon Jong responded while looking at Wei Soheng with a strange look in his eyes.

"You don't have to try to understand, young trainee Wei."

"What?"

"Because soon you'll understand even if you don't want to."

"…"

An unfamiliar sense of unease began to grow in Wei Soheng's chest.

The next morning.

Wei Soheng patiently waited to depart in front of the sect leader's residence. Beside him, both Yoon Jong and Jo Gul were already waiting for the others to arrive. Carrying additional luggage as well.

"He should be coming soon…."

"There he is."

Wei Soheng turned to where the others were looking.

"Ah…"

He exclaimed without realizing it.

A man dressed in a white robe, with the bearing of a hero, was approaching them.

'Amazing.'

He couldn't think of any other word to describe him.

Yoon Jong gave off the refined atmosphere of an expert, but this man coming toward them felt different. It was like seeing a hero straight from a story.

It was a bad habit to judge people by their appearance, but anyone who saw this man would feel the same way.

Yoon Jong bowed his head.

"Baek Cheon sasuk. Did you rest well?"

'Baek Cheon? Then he is…?'

'Righteous Sword of Hua, Baek Cheon?'

If Mount Hua's Divine Dragon was the most mysterious disciple in the sect, then the Righteous Sword of Hua was the most famous one. It was a story that everyone had heard; this man led his fellow disciples to clear out a horde of wicked bandits to save countless people.

'Didn't the people he saved commend him for being eye candy?'

'Indeed, he really looks like a hero.'

Baek Cheon approached them with a soft smile and said,

"Would you be able to rest peacefully if you were me?"

"…"

Baek Cheon's face distorted

"Damn it, it's terrifying that he's back out again, and I need to go with him too. What the hell did I do to deserve this?"

"Still, Sasuk can at least express your dissatisfaction. We're just stuck with it."

"Yes."

Baek Cheon scratched his head.

"Even the sect leader is ignoring this."

"That's true."

The three sighed together.

"I… I am Wei… ak! Oh, my god!"

When Wei Soheng began to hesitantly introduce himself, he suddenly found a person standing next to him, panicked, and backed away.

'When!?'

He couldn't feel anyone approaching, so how long was this person standing next to him? But alas, Wei Soheng was the only one surprised; the others didn't seem bothered at all.

'A woman?'

Wei Soheng observed the woman standing next to him and slightly dropped his jaw unconsciously.

'Beautiful.'

Wei Soheng would swear that he had never seen anyone as beautiful as her.

A woman whose cold expression seemed to be coated in a layer of ice.

Normally, that cold expression would reduce the original beauty, but it only seemed to amplify this woman's attractiveness.

"Yu Samae. Did you bring your things?"

"Yes, sahyung."

"There is no need for samae to even come on this journey."

"I said I'd go."

"Well..."

Baek Cheon, who wanted to say something, just nodded and remained silent.

Wei Soheng, who watched from the side, realized one thing.

'It might not be a sect with many people, but no one here is ordinary.'

Everyone seemed unique.

But there was a reason he only realized it now, and that 'reason' was currently trudging towards them from afar.

"You're early, aren't you?"

Chung Myung waved at the crowd as he approached. Everyone's expression became distorted, except for Yu Yiseol.

'Sleep a little more, being late doesn't matter.'

'Needlessly diligent!'

Chung Myung looked at the people gathered and tilted his head.

"Sasuk, you too?"

Baek Cheon answered with a shaky face.

"That's how it ended up."

"Well, sasuk is fine…."

Chung Myung slightly frowned.

"Sago too?"

"Yes."

"Seriously?"

"Yes."

"…"

Just as Chung Myung was about to continue, the door opened, and Hyun Jong came out.

"Everyone has gathered?"

"Yes."

Hyun Jong came out and took Wei Soheng's hand.

"Young trainee Wei."

"Yes, sect leader."

"I know there are a lot of things you are worried about. But these children are trustworthy, so they will surely help you."

"Thank you, sect leader."

Wei Soheng bowed his head.

Even though Huayoung Gate was connected to Mount Hua, he didn't think they would help this wholeheartedly. The warmth that Wei Soheng felt from the elder's hand made him want to cry.

"And… Baek Cheon."

"Yes."

"Lead the children well. I believe in you."

"Yes!"

"Yiseol, Yoon Jong, and Jo Gul help Baek Cheon."

"Don't worry sect leader!"

"We will."

"Yes."

Finally, Hyun Jong looked at Chung Myung.

"…Chung Myung."

"Yes!"

"Please don't create trouble."

"… well, I think the concept of trouble differs from person to person."

"Please!"

"… Yes."

Thus, the second and third-class disciples from Mount Hua began their journey to Huayoung Gate.

Chapter 122: I’ll show you what happens when you touch Mount Hua! (2)

Hyun Jong’s eyes, as he watched the party leave through the gate, contained an undeniable sense of unease.

“Will they be fine?”

“We sent Baek Cheon and Yoon Jong along with him for that reason.”

“Isn’t there anyone else we can send with them?”

“… We don’t have anyone, sect leader.”

Hyun Jong looked at Un Am. Un Am turned his head with a slightly nonchalant expression and avoided meeting Hyun Jong’s eyes.

“You don’t want to keep an eye on them?”

“It isn’t a grown-up thing to do. Also, if we do something wrong, things may spiral out of control.”

“If we let them go, won’t things get worse?”

… It was a difficult question to answer.

To be honest, it’s not strange for situations to explode when Chung Myung is involved.

“I am worried. Very worried.”

Hyun Jong took a deep breath.

Hyun Sang, who was watching from the side, burst into laughter.

Hyun Jong looked back at him with a sour face.

“Sajae seems to find this situation funny.”

“I’m sorry, sect leader. But how can it not be funny?”

“What’s so funny about it?”

Hyun Sang smiled brightly.

“Just two years ago we were worried that our disciples would be disgraced by the Southern Edge sect. But now, aren’t you worried that those same children are going to beat the Wudang disciples too harshly?”

“…”

Right.

If you were to see this situation from anywhere other than Mount Hua, then people may say that the sect leader was simply making excuses out of fear for the Wudang sect after they got lucky once against the Southern Edge sect.

However, it was natural to believe in the young disciples after seeing what kind of training the second and third-class disciples endured over the past two years.

“Trust and wait. They aren’t thoughtless children. They will return after increasing Mount Hua’s fame.”

“Fame is sometimes evil.”

“Yes?”

“Infamy is just another side of fame.”

“…”

Hyun Jong deeply sighed as he watched his students move farther and farther away.

“I hope they come back safely.”

Hyun Sang couldn’t bring himself to guarantee that they wouldn’t be hurt.

At first, Wei Soheng thought it was reasonable.

Young trainee. Shouldn’t we get to Nanyang as soon as possible? We don’t have any problems, but your stamina seems to be a bit of an issue here. So, why not try moving in a better way?

As a matter of fact, Wei Soheng had to agree.

First, he wasn’t in his best state. From Nanyang to Hua-Um, he had run the entire way and was exhausted.

Even if that wasn’t the case. Wei Soheng couldn’t catch up to them; even in his best condition, he would never be able to keep pace with Mount Hua’s true disciples.

However, they couldn’t possibly carry him on their back, could they?

It’s fine. It’s fine. I’ll take care of it. Don’t worry.

Until then, they seemed reliable.

When they got two horses and a cart as soon as they reached Hua-Um, Wei Soheng began to feel guilty about judging others based on a shallow understanding of their personality.

Hey! Hey! I’ll take care of everything!

By the time the cart was full of food and ready for the journey, Wei Soheng believed that he could trust the man named Chung Myung.

No, I said I will handle it all! Can’t you understand me?

Unidentified bottles had piled up next to the food. It was only later that he found out that they were alcohol. But it was too late to turn around.

Thanks to that…

“Kuak!”

Chung Myung was drinking while lying in the cart.

“…”

Wei Soheng stared at the absurd scene and turned to Baek Cheon.

“The disciple is drunk….”

“Mount Hua doesn’t forbid alcohol.”

Ah, he knew that since he’s also a member of Mount Hua. But his seniors were here; isn’t it a bit unusual for this man to drink and laze about in front of them?

‘…and what the hell is that?’

Yu Yiseol, who was sitting next to Chung Myung, was tossing a piece of jerky into his mouth. And that bastard would chew it as if this was natural.

“….”

It was a bizarre sight.

Seeing this gorgeous woman serving him jerky, no, she was actually his senior…no, perhaps this is a beautiful display of friendship between disciples. But still, wasn’t this jerky thing a bit too strange?

It wasn’t like tossing a dog some snacks.

The person who gave it was doing it with care, while the other one took it for granted.

Wei Soheng was utterly baffled as he watched while Baek Cheon called for him.

“Young trainee Wei.”

“Huh? Ah, yes!”

“Don’t worry about it. Just because you see it, doesn’t mean you’ll understand it.”

Wei Soheng glanced at Yu Yiseol.

He couldn’t understand what that woman was doing.

“Right.”

“….”

Although they had already departed for Nanyang, Wei Soheng couldn’t help but doubt whether it was right to bring them along.

“We should get there in a couple days.”

Wei Soheng’s gaze shifted to the front.

Two horses were pulling the carriage, and Yoon Jong and Jo Gul were sitting on the coach seat.

‘Those horses look expensive.’

Even at this moment, the cart is speeding forward at an incredible pace. It was definitely much faster than what Wei Soheng could run at full strength.

With the carriage, there was no need to take a break either. This certainly seemed to be the correct choice.

However…

Gulp.

“Kua, it’s so great to be alive!”

Wei Soheng felt his stomach twisting as he watched the disciple gulping down alcohol.

Wei Soheng never thought of himself as the sort of person that would disparage someone else for what they found enjoyable. For some reason, though, when he saw Chung Myung, a strange and twisted feeling rose within him.

“Young trainee Wei.”

“Yes. Disciple Baek Cheon.”

“What kind of place is Huayoung Gate?”

When Wei Soheng hesitated at the sudden question, Baek Cheon added.

“I’m not asking for any particular reason. However, I didn’t get to hear the details as I needed to leave in a hurry. I know that the Gate is a part of Mount Hua, but I think I need to know a bit more to take care of everything properly.”

“N-no, it’s no problem. I was just wondering how to tell you….”

Wei Soheng shyly scratched the back of his head.

“There’s nothing special about the place.”

“It’s special enough.”

Baek Cheong answered in a serious tone.

“Until recently, Mount Hua’s name had no meaning. Nevertheless, your Gate has proudly declared itself to be a sub-sect of Mount Hua. Even if we searched the whole world, there would never be another place like Huayoung Gate.”

Even Chung Myung, who was lying down, turned his gaze towards Wei Soheng.

“I didn’t do it with some great sense of duty. It’s just that my father was very proud to be a disciple of Mount Hua.”

Wei Soheng’s face wasn’t very bright when he spoke.

‘He must have suffered a lot.’

Chung Myung, who was lying down, lightly clicked his tongue as he listened.

Wei Soheng must have wanted to give up on Mount Hua countless times. Such is the way of the world. Students learn martial arts, but nobody wants to learn fading techniques from a dying sect.

Those who knew about Mount Hua would want to learn because they knew how far they had fallen, while those who didn’t know had no reason to choose such an obscure sect.

“I can’t even tell you how much my father loved hearing about the last Southern Edge conference. Even though he never drinks, he downed two entire bottles of alcohol and started talking about how Mount Hua is beginning to spread its wings again.”

“Hmm.”

Baek Cheon quietly nodded his head.

“You said your father was proud to be a disciple of Mount Hua?”

“Yes. To be precise, it was my great grandfather who was a disciple of Mount Hua, not father… Well, it’s exactly as you thought. He often said that being unable to enter Mount Hua as a disciple was his lifelong regret.”

Baek Cheon nodded his head.

“Anyway, my father is very proud to manage Huayoung Gate. Besides, I was lucky enough to live without ever having to starve. If only those Path’s Edge bastards hadn’t shown up….”

“Did you say that the Gate leader was defeated in a fight?”

“Yes. But… frankly it’s strange.”

“Strange?”

Wei Soheng nodded his head.

“Father has never neglected his training. It’s a bit strange for me to say, but there’s no way that he would be defeated by young disciples.”

It was natural.

Those who learn martial arts grow stronger over time. Ordinary people grow weaker and weaker with age, but warriors have no choice but to gradually become stronger by steadily developing their bodies and refining their qi.

Therefore, in the Murim, the elders are strong.

“But the leader of the training center was too young. I can’t understand why my father lost to that young man.”

“Hmm.”

Baek Cheon frowned.

‘There’s more than just one or two things that seem out of place.’

At first, he thought that it was a simple argument between two sub-sects, but now that he heard more about it, there are a couple of things that seemed strange.

Whatever it was, it was enough for the sect leader to call him separately and give some advice.

Wei Soheng glanced at Baek Cheon and then spoke.

“Actually, I should apologize.”

“For what?”

“My father did tell me to ask for help from Mount Hua, but I honestly didn’t think Mount Hua would be willing.”

“Oh.”

Baek Cheon nodded.

“It isn’t easy to handle the Wudang sect. That’s why we were so desperate. But to help us out so quickly….”

Wei Soheng paused for a moment as if he choked on his words. Baek Cheon waited silently until he spoke. Covering his mouth, Wei Soheng started speaking with an emotional voice.

“I think I can understand why my father liked Mount Hua. No matter what the outcome is, I will live my life feeling grateful for it.”

A heartwarming declaration.

Unfortunately, there was a person in this cart who had a disease that made him feel goosebumps when he had to listen to such flowery words.

“Whatever the outcome?”

Chung Myung raised himself up with shining eyes. Yu Yiseol pressed her fingers against his head, and his rising body began to lay down again. However, his words continued.

“Whatever the outcome!? There’s only going to be one outcome! We’ll have to split the heads of those bastards!”

“Didn’t the sect leader tell us not to do that?”

“Will we stop just because of that? I’m sure he wants it as well! The sect leader doesn’t have much time left to live, so I’ll show him how we crack the skulls of those Wudang bastards! That way, the sect leader can smile when hears about it before he heads across the river!”

‘How can you talk about respecting the sect leader at the same time you’re cursing him?’

It felt wrong just listening to Chung Myung speak.

“And honestly, aren’t we here to beat up the Wudang bastards anyway?”

‘What?’

‘Uh… that is true, though.’

“And we have this opportunity!”

A fire was raging in Chung Myung’s eyes.

“I was trying to live as quietly as possible.”

‘Ah, I doubt you were aiming for that.’

“Those bastards touched us first. Then they should be punished! Great sahyung! What are you doing!? Speed up!”

“We’re already moving as fast as we can! If we rush anymore the horses will get tired.”

“How much did they cost us!? It’s fine, it’s fine! We can go twice as fast as normal horses, so don’t worry, and speed up!”

“Yes.”

Yoon Jong shook his head and patted the horse’s ass.

As the cart’s speed increased, Chung Myung’s body shook.

“I don’t know why you did it, but I’ll show what happens when you touch Mount Hua!”

Hearing that triumphant voice, Baek Cheon sighed.

‘The other side can’t even imagine what they’ve caused.’

It was a fact that the unprecedented asshole that even Mount Hua could not handle was heading to Nanyang.

Baek Cheon, innocent and hopeful, sent heartfelt condolences to the disciples from the Wudang sect who were going to arrive in Nanyang full of hope.

Chapter 123: I’ll show you what happens when you touch Mount Hua! (3)

“Has there been any news from Soheng?”

“… no news yet.”

“I see…”

Wei Lishan let out a low sigh; despondent, his face seemed to have lost all its vitality.

“Gate leader. You need to be patient a little while longer.”

“… I know. I know, but….”

Seeing Wei Lishan struggle to find words to express himself, the other person, Yeom Pyeong, sighed.

‘He can’t even relax properly.’

The Path’s Edge training hall has no desire to coexist with Huayoung Gate. They’ve constantly been arguing since the training hall opened. Now, even after defeating Huayoung’s leader, Path’s Edge is unsatisfied and has been demanding that Huayoung Gate leave and never return.

It’s incredibly heavy-handed, excessive treatment.

However, Huayoung Gate lacked the strength to complain about such abusive acts.

Kangho is a world where the strong prey upon the weak. Those who lack power cannot retaliate against the strong. Despite living in the Kangho their entire lives, they were only now understanding this heartbreaking reality.

“Did you say that Wudang’s disciples have arrived?”

“Not yet. But given the time, they should arrive soon.”

“Right…. Cough! Cough!”

“Are you alright? Gate leader!?”

“… I’m fine.”

“You are seriously injured. Please lie down.”

“I will.”

That was how Wei Lishan responded, but he and Yeom Pyong both knew that this was a dire situation where the gate leader couldn’t afford to simply lie down and rest.

If the Wudang sect’s disciples arrive, they will immediately be kicked out of their homes. How could Wei Lishan bear to lie down and rest when Huayoung Gate, which had taken care of him for his entire life, was about to be forcibly disbanded.

“What about the disciples?”

“… they seem agitated.”

“I’m sure they are. Right… they must be…”

A low sigh escaped Wei Lishan’s mouth.

Even though he heard the disciples were agitated, he couldn’t blame them at all. Despite the looming threat of confrontation with the Wudang, the disciples were all still maintaining their posts and guarding the sect.

‘I haven’t lived in vain.’

This loyalty alone felt rewarding enough for Wei Lishan.

“Gate leader.”

Yeom Pyong sighed after calling out.

Yeom Pyong is the great disciple of Wei Lishan. He had followed Wei Lishan for a long time, and they led Huayoung Gate together; but now, they were struggling and unable to find any other solutions.

“… Gate leader. Why don’t we talk to the Path’s End leader again?”

“It’s no use.”

Wei Lishan shook his head.

“If there was anything else that they wanted, we may have been able to resolve this through conversation. But their only desire is to drive us out of Nanyang. What could we even hope to accomplish by trying to negotiate with them? There’s only one thing they want, our goals run parallel to each other but they never cross or intersect.”

“Are you saying that we have to bear this happening before our eyes?”

“… The main sect’s answer will come soon.”

“Gate leader…”

Yeom Pyong’s face contorted.

Wei Lishan was a smart and reasonable man, but his judgment would cloud over whenever Mount Hua’s name entered the picture.

This was Wei Lishan’s disease.

“Our opponent is the Wudang sect. Even though Mount Hua has begun to make a name for itself recently, the Wudang sect is an unparalleled giant. How could Mount Hua help us?”

“…”

“It would be nice if they sent help; but if Mount Hua had any understanding of the situation, they wouldn’t intervene. Would any good come from clashing with the Wudang? Gate leader, you need to be rational. There’s no one coming to help us. This is something we need to deal with ourselves.”

Wei Lishan stared at Yeom Pyong.

He knew that this man wasn’t wrong.

“Still…”

“That’s why I told you to stop sending money to Mount Hua. Why put so much effort into something that won’t help when needed? Would this have happened if you’d sent that to Wudang or Shaolin instead?”

He was right.

Still, Wei Lishan couldn’t agree.

“We are Mount Hua.”

“…”

Yeom Pyong stayed silent.

“Our roots aren’t something we can abandon; they must never be thrown away. Do you think it would be better to deny our heritage and cast aside Mount Hua’s name?”

“Gate leader…”

“If we did that, it would be the same no matter where we go. If the Wudang sect loses their name, we would abandon the Wudang; and if the Shaolin sect’s influence declines, then we’d abandon them as well. No, absolutely not! I don’t want to live like that.”

“No one knows…”

“I don’t need anyone to know. I will protect what I have to protect.”

Yeom Pyong sighed.

He was frustrated and felt stifled.

But…

‘This is why he’s the leader.’

After all, the reason for Yeom Pyong’s nagging was because he respected this man. If Wei Lishan was the sort of man that would easily cast Mount Hua aside, then Yeom Pyong would have never respected him this much.

“And I believe.”

“What?”

“Mount Hua will not forsake us.”

Yeom Pyong shook his head.

“Gate leader, it’s not a matter of sincerity or intent, it’s a matter of ability. Is Mount Hua capable of dealing with the Wudang sect?”

“… There are times when the heart is enough on its own.”

Yeom Pyong was about to respond when…

Knock knock knock!

Someone was knocking on the door.

Wei Lishan and Yeom Pyong’s faces quickly hardened. They had locked the gates and refused to see any visitors. Nevertheless, if someone was knocking on the gate, then it meant that they had business with them.

At this time, the only one who had any business here was…

“Gate leader Wei! Are you there? I have matters to discuss with you, come out!”

Yeom Pyong’s face contorted.

It was the leader of Path’s Edge training hall’s voice.

‘Damn it, already!?’

They wouldn’t have come here without reason. So, he must have brought the Wudang disciples with him.

“What do we do? Gate leader?”

“Do we have any choice?”

Wei Lishan sighed.

“I have to go out. He came here to see me, if I don’t go, they’ll think that I’m a coward.”

Wei Lishan was trembling as he rose from the bed.

“What is it?”

“You obviously know why I’m here. As I said, I’m here to discuss matters with you.”

Watching the leader of the Path’s Edge pushing his way inside like a boar made it hard to believe that he was really a disciple of Wudang once.

At least anyone who studied Taoism shouldn’t behave like this.

“I have nothing more to say.”

“You have nothing to say!? If you’ve lost the battle, you are supposed to leave Nanyang. What are you still doing here?”

“What law says that we need to leave just because we lost a match?”

“There’s no such thing! But don’t you have any pride?”

Wei Lishan sighed.

There was no law that said one needed to leave after a lost match. Unless, of course, they had bet on the outcome.

However, if the situation had escalated into a battle between two sects, it was an unwritten rule that the defeated would leave without a word.

No, to be precise, it would be more accurate to say that the losing side lacked the strength to hold out against the victor.

The leader’s ability is the metric by which a sect is measured. How could a sect survive after it’s been clearly revealed which side is superior? Isn’t it obvious that new recruits would choose to become disciples of the stronger sect?

“I have nothing to say. Please leave.”

“No, I don’t think that I will.”

The eyes of the Path’s Edge leader shone.

“Will you only come to your senses after blood has been drawn?”

As the atmosphere suddenly turned heavy, one of the men watching from the back slowly walked forward.

“Training hall leader, let me speak for you.”

“Ah, you? This is such a trivial thing….”

“It’s fine.”

“Then, I am grateful!”

It was a completely different and very polite attitude compared to how the Path’s Edge leader dealt with Wei Lishan. Naturally, Wei Lishan’s eyes focused on the man that stepped forward.

A black robe.

A prestige that made the training hall leader bow.

Embroidered on his chest was the shape of a pine tree, symbolizing wealth and indicating this man’s identity. There are many sects in the world, but there was only one that engraved a pine tree on their chests.

‘A Wudang sect disciple.’

The man who came forward bowed.

“Nice to meet you, I am Jin Hyeon, a second-class disciple of Wudang.”

“Wei Lishan.”

It was a dignified gesture and a respectful attitude. If they hadn’t met in such a situation, Wei Lishan would have admired this man. But now, behind that modest attitude was a man aiming for Wei Lishan’s downfall.

Wei Lishan observed this man for a moment before going stiff.

“Wait! Did you just say Jin Hyeon?”

“Yes, Gate leader.”

“Then you are… the Indestructible Sword, Jin Hyeon?”

“It’s embarrassing to hear such words.”

Wei Lishan’s face darkened upon learning the man’s identity.

‘The indestructible sword. Today isn’t going to be a good day.’

Jin Hyeon is considered to be one of the best disciples produced by the Wudang sect. The world calls him the Sword Dragon and doesn’t hesitate to praise his abilities.

He’s likely to become the First Sword of the Wudang Sect. Perhaps, in the future, he may be the greatest swordsman in the sect’s history.

The Wudang sect choosing to send Jin Hyeon testified to how seriously they considered this matter.

“I’ve heard about what happened from our training hall leader. You said that you wished to stay in Nanyang?”

“Yes.”

Jin Hyeon lightly shook his head.

“I don’t think that’s a good idea.”

Despite being soft, his voice carried a powerful weight.

“Nanyang isn’t a large area and if there are two sub-sects in such a small place, problems will only continue to rise. It’s difficult because we would have to share the potential disciples.”

“It’s not as if I don’t understand that. But why must we leave when our sect was here first?”

“It doesn’t matter. What’s important is that these two Gates cannot coexist without harming one another, and Huayoung Gate is the sect that will suffer more damage.”

“…”

Jin Hyeon grinned.

“How about this?”

“Huh?”

“It’s true that Wudang’s sub-sect recently opened and damaged your reputation, so we will compensate you for it. If you move away from Nanyang, we will bear all the expenses.”

Yeom Pyong, who listened from the side, frowned.

‘These bastards!’

‘Did they think we refused because of money?’

Settling in a new place meant starting over from scratch. Huayoung Gate is a sect belonging to Nanyang. All the disciples are from Nanyang, and all of the sect’s history resides here!

Leaving this place meant throwing everything away and starting from the bottom.

“Thank you for your offer, but….”

Wei Lishan shook his head.

“Huayoung Gate has no intention of doing that.”

“Well.”

JIn Hyeon had a sly smile as if he didn’t appreciate Wei Lishan’s response.

“Gate leader.”

“…”

“If you really want to remain in Nanyang, there is one other option.”

Wei Lishan glanced at Jin Hyeon. He was truly hoping that they could find some other way to resolve this situation.

“What could that be?”

“If you wish to stay here… remove the Plum Blossom from your signboard.”

Wei Lishan’s face hardened.

Seeing Wei Lishan’s lack of response, Jin Hyeon leisurely continued.

“The two Gates are compatible, but the main sects aren’t. No matter how faded the color of Mount Hua’s influence is, it remains unacceptable for Wudang’s sub-sect to coexist alongside it.”

“W-what…”

“Choose.”

Jin Hyeon spoke coldly.

“If you remove Mount Hua’s name, then we will accept Huayoung Gate. If you want, we can even take you under Wudang’s wing. Then both Huayoung Gate and Path’s Edge can get along. Otherwise!”

Jin Hyeon’s words turned sharp, like a dagger stabbing at their eardrums.

“The name of Huayoung Gate will forever disappear from Nanyang.”

The weight of these words felt so much heavier when they were spoken from Jin Hyeon’s mouth.

Seeing Wei Lishan in shock, Jin Hyeon smiled.

“What is your answer?”

“… we…”

Wei Lishan’s lips were trembling.

It was only a short time, but his expression changed innumerable times. As he pondered over and over again, he eventually sighed in lament and spoke.

“We cannot abandon Mount Hua.”

“…”

“Even if the day comes when we take down our signboard, we will still be a part of Mount Hua. That isn’t something we can abandon.”

“Haa…”

Jin Hyeon shook his head.

“There’s nothing more I can do for you; you’ve refused both options that I’ve given. If you don’t leave within six hours, then we will clear you out ourselves.”

Wei Lishan bit his lip.

“Isn’t this behavior too shameful for a famous sect like Wudang?”

“You’re mistaken.”

“…”

Jin Hyeon said in a cold voice.

“It’s not that Wudang is abusing its fame to do this. Rather, it’s because we do this that Wudang’s name resonates throughout the world. What’s more, we’ve already tried everything we could. You were the one that refused our offers.”

“We…”

“That’s enough. I have nothing more to say. You have six hours.”

Jin Hyeon then spoke in a quiet voice so that only Wei Lishan could hear him.

“If you’re going to beg for help, I’d search for a better place. Do you think Mount Hua will help Huayoung Gate? Against our Wudang sect?”

“… I…”

Wei Lishan couldn’t say anything.

Jin Hyeon’s face had a wide and demeaning sneer plastered across it.

‘Horrifying.’

The Wudang sect is protecting the Path’s Edge training hall and persecuting Huayoung Gate. But Mount Hua was doing nothing to help them.

What had Wei Lishan’s devotion amounted to after all these years?

“Mount Hua doesn’t dare to come. If the Gate leader was a bit wiser….”

At that moment…

“What is he saying? That two-faced bastard?”

“…”

Jin Hyeon turned his head toward the muffled voice coming from the back.

“Who are you?”

“Ah, move! Why are you blocking the gate!?”

His sahyungs, who were standing in front of the gate, were pushed away.

And a man came walking through the gap between them.

‘Who?’

Before Jin Hyeon could even gather an impression about this sudden stranger, he was struck with words he had never heard before.

“It’s me. You unscrupulous little bitch.”

“…”

Jin Hyeon’s mouth fell agape without him realizing it.

Chapter 124: I’ll show you what happens when you touch Mount Hua! (4)

Two-faced and unscrupulous.

Profane insults derived from the fact that the sect would speak righteously while acting deviously.

Simply put…

‘He’s cursing me?’

It was an insult to the disciples.

Of course, Jin Hyeon understood that such insults existed, but he never thought that he would be called out so directly in his lifetime.

It was a normal thought to have.

Inside the Wudang sect, there was no need for such abusive language. It was even less likely that he would hear such profanity when venturing out into the world. After all, who in their right mind would risk cursing a disciple of the Wudang sect?

One wouldn’t dare to say such a thing unless they had ten lives.

What sort of place was the Wudang Sect?

Along with the Shaolin Sect, they are known to be the oldest of the Nine Great Sects, One Union. There are many sects throughout the world, but Shaolin is the only sect that can boast about being equal to the Wudang Sect.

But this unknown man was insulting a disciple from Wudang?

‘Is he crazy?’

But the man that entered didn’t look like he’d gone insane. His behavior was calm, and his eyes were lucid with a glimmer of intelligence.

No, judging solely by his appearance, he almost seemed commendable.

He had a slightly tilted posture with an annoyed expression on his face. It was like this man had taken all of the world’s burdens upon his shoulders.

“Who are you?”

“What good would knowing that do for you?”

“…”

‘Is he really just a mad man?’

Jin Hyeon had no choice but to seriously contemplate the identity of the man in front of him.

Since ancient times, it’s been said that a heavy-handed beating is medicine for the insane. But that was just a saying. In fact, a beating works the same whether a man is crazy or perfectly sane.

“That—”

The moment Jin Hyeon tried to speak, another commotion began from behind.

“I need to pass. Let me through.”

“Why is everyone blocking the door?”

“Jo Gul, enter quietly.”

From the entryway, a new group of people entered.

‘Huh?’

Did people usually enter like this?

Even if these people were unaware that the ones blocking the gate were Wudang’s disciples, it didn’t seem normal to risk pushing aside a group of burly men wielding swords.

However, this group was currently slithering their way into Huayoung Gate, gently pushing their way through the disciples of the Wudang sect as if they were making their way through a busy market.

‘Who the hell?’

It was then.

“Father!”

The last person to enter quickly ran towards Wei Lishan. Seeing this man, Wei Lishan delightedly called out.

“Soheng!”

“Father! I brought people from Mount Hua!”

“Ah!”

Everyone clearly heard what he said.

‘Mount Hua?’

Jin Hyeon’s face hardened. So, the people in front of him were from Mount Hua?

‘Now that I think about it.’

There was indeed a plum blossom pattern on their chests.

Since they had given such a powerful first impression, Jin Hyeon had forgotten to inspect them any closer.

“Ah, Mount Hua!”

Wei Lishan’s emotions began to overflow, especially since Jin Hyeon had just declared that Mount Hua would never come to their aid.

‘No, wait a moment, Mount Hua?’

Jin Hyeon carefully observed the faces of those who appeared.

A swordsman in white that appears wary at first glance, a man that gives a soft impression, and a man next to him that feels sharp and ready to assist.

And

‘Infinite beauty.’

There was a woman so beautiful that Jin Hyeon’s eyes went wide; he had to quickly recall his teachings to stabilize his mind.

It was all good until then.

However…

One man remained that still bothered Jin Hyeon.

‘What the hell is with him?’

Despite its collapse, Mount Hua had once been one of the central pillars of the Nine Great Sects and had a prestigious reputation. So, how could a man like this be accepted into such a sect?

Compared to the other disciples, the difference was extreme.

“Are you also from Mount Hua?”

“Then are you from Shaolin?”

“…”

Jin Hyeon was about to say something before simply shutting his mouth.

Then the swordsman in white, who was watching from the side, stepped toward Wei Lishan and spoke.

“I greet the leader of Huayoung Gate. After hearing that the Gate was experiencing difficulties, the sect leader sent us to assist.”

“Ah… the sect leader.”

Wei Lishan tightly closed his quivering eyes.

He felt a deep rush of emotion inside his chest.

Although he had sent his son to Mount Hua, he felt that he was grasping at straws. He didn’t really think Mount Hua would come to help. What he said to Yeom Pyong was just his own feeble means of escaping from the harsh reality.

But Mount Hua really did send their disciples.

Wei Lishan looked at Baek Cheon and trembled.

Devotion.

Even with Jin Hyeon, the Indestructible Swordsman, right next to him, this man looked strong.

Then…

“Then, are you Mount Hua’s Divine—”

“No.”

Before he could even ask, Baek Cheon cut off Wei Lishan’s words. Baek Cheon quickly continued, but not without Wei Lishan noticing his slightly distorted expression.

“I’m Baek Cheon, a second-class disciple of Mount Hua.”

“Ah! The Righteous Sword of Hua! I’ve heard a lot about you!”

‘They sent the Righteous Sword of Hua!’

It seemed like the sect leader was truly appreciative and sent their finest disciples!

‘Ah, no. then….’

‘They didn’t send Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon?’

Just then…

“Kua!”

One person, who had just been doing something incomprehensible, approached Wei Lishan with a look of admiration and grabbed his hand.

“Ahh. Gate leader.

“…”

“I’ve heard so much about you! Thirty years! I was told that you’ve been consistently sending money to the sect for thirty years! Is that right?”

“R-right, but…”

“Kuaaak!”

The man looked like he was moved by Wei Lishan’s actions. He seemed so moved that his eyes were moist and on the verge of tears.

But why?

“I can’t believe such a wonderful man exists. You constantly sent money to the sect that even beggars had turned their backs on. I thought that all the good people in the world were dead, but there’s still one that survived right here.”

“…”

Wei Lishan was a thick-skinned man.

Since he had protected Huayoung Gate for several decades, the number of people he met had easily exceeded hundreds or even thousands.

But of all the people Wei Lishan had met, there had never been a person like this.

‘He seems to be a disciple from Mount Hua. How could such a person come from there?’

Wei Lishan gently pulled his hand away from the man and asked.

“…And who are you?”

“Ah. My name is Chung Myung. The sect leader sent me.”

“Ah. Chung Myung means you’re a third-class…. Wait. Chung Myung?”

“Yes. Please call me like that! Hahaha! You can call me that! Our excellent Gate leader!”

Chung Myung?

Was this THE Chung Myung?

Wei Lishan opened his eyes wide.

From what he knew, there was only one person named Chung Myung in Mount Hua.

‘Ah, no, I cannot know everything.’

Wei Lishan quickly spun toward his son. Wei Soheng, who received his gaze, trembled while nodding his head with an indescribable expression.

‘It’s true?’

‘Then, this guy that looks like a common neighborhood thug is…?’

“Chung Myung?”

It seemed like Wei Lishan wasn’t the only one that harbored doubts. Even Jin Hyeon called the name with a flustered tone.

Chung Myung titled his head.

“… then are you saying that you’re Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon, Chung Myung?”

“I don’t leave Mount Hua, so I don’t know what you’re talking about. But I am Chung Myung”

“You?”

Jin Hyeon couldn’t believe his eyes.

In an instant, Chung Myung’s face twisted.

“What? Do I need to show you some identification?”

“…”

Chung Myung then shifted his gaze from Jin Hyeon back to Wei Lishan, whom he looked at with a soft smile. The difference in attitude that he showed when dealing with these two men was absurd.

“Don’t worry. We’ll take care of everything now. Sect leader said that Huayoung Gate is the best among Mount Hua’s inner circle.”

That was true.

Because this was the only Gate that helped them when they needed it most.

Chung Myung smiled and turned away. Looking at Baek Cheon, he tilted his head and asked.

“What are you doing, sasuk?”

“… are you done?”

“Yes.”

Baek Cheon sighed and looked at Jin Hyeon.

“I’m Baek Cheon from Mount Hua.”

“Jin Hyeon from Wudang.”

“We came here because there seemed to be a problem with the subsect. It seems like you were speaking directly with the Gate leader, but now you can discuss these matters with me.”

“Are you saying that Mount Hua will be getting involved?”

“Is there a reason we shouldn’t?”

Hearing Baek Cheon’s response, Jin Hyeon narrowed his eyes.

‘How dare they.’

Mount Hua was a broken and ruined sect that only recently started to re-establish itself. Such a sect was getting involved in the Wudang sect’s matters over a small sub-sect?

This was unacceptable.

Furthermore…

Jin Hyeon looked at Chung Myung.

‘That’s Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon?’

It was absurd.

Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon Chung Myung.

The Divine Dragon had suddenly made its name two years ago and rose to prominence overnight.

That name has echoed painfully in Jin Hyeon’s ears, and there was a specific reason that he remembered that name so clearly.

Jin Hyeon, Wudang’s Sword Dragon.

And Chung Myung, Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon.

There were four others with similar titles and were collectively referred to as the Six Dragons. In the Kangho, the Six Dragons referred to the six strongest disciples that would become masters and lead the world of martial arts.

Jin Hyeon wasn’t interested in titles like ‘Six Dragons’ or ‘Sword Dragon.’ There was only one thing he cared about. Among the Six Dragons, the evaluation of Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon was greater than him.

‘This guy is supposed to be stronger than me? That’s nonsense.’

Of course, the evaluations take age into account. Chung Myung is anticipated to be stronger than Jin Hyeon at the same age.

But Jin Hyeon refused to acknowledge that assessment.

And…

‘Sect leader was right.’

- Perhaps Mount Hua’s disciples will come to the Nanyang. If the disciples of Mount Hua come, then Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon, Chung Myung, will also be there. If that’s the case, let the world know that Mount Hua’s disciples cannot compare to the disciples of the Wudang Sect.

Jin Hyeon smiled.

“How do you plan to intervene?”

Jin Hyeon arrogantly looked down on Baek Cheon.

Rather than the Divine Dragon, he was more concerned about this man. Baek Cheon’s momentum and sense of presence from before was no joking matter.

‘I guess his reputation wasn’t in vain.’

Unlike Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon.

“It would be best if we could pleasantly discuss this matter, but….”

Baek Cheon smiled.

“You don’t seem to want to do that, right?”

“Haha. That’s a misunderstanding. It would be great if this could be resolved through diplomacy. However, the difference in ideals is too great to narrow. So, conversation seems fleeting.”

“Isn’t that the same thing?”

Baek Cheon urged him with a sharp tone, a fishy smile formed on Jin Hyeon’s lips.

“Then how should we resolve this? A match? We won’t back down.”

“It seems like Wudang’s methods are rougher than I expected.”

“Rather than rough, it’s efficient. There’s no need to waste each other’s time….”

It was then.

“Ah, your time isn’t worth shit.”

“…”

“…”

Baek Cheon and Jin Hyeon turned their heads at the same time and looked at Chung Myung, who had interrupted.

However, the expressions of these two were completely different.

Baek Cheon thought to himself.

‘Please just stay still, you damned bastard!’

He was trying to express that sentiment to Chung Myung through his facial expression, while Jin Hyeon’s face was beginning to overflow with indescribable fury.

Chung Myung was clearly from a junior generation, but he dared to speak so disgracefully to his seniors.

“Mount Hua must not teach any courtesy.”

“Courtesy?”

Chung Myung laughed.

“What a bunch of shit.”

“You!?”

“You invade another’s sect and demand they shut their doors and leave, or risk being harassed and beaten, then have the nerve to talk about courtesy? For you, courtesy only enters the picture when it’s convenient, right?”

“…”

Jin Hyeon bit his lip.

It was hard to counter Chung Myung’s words. Jin Hyeon knew that what he said wasn’t wrong.

“What is there to talk about? You guys can do whatever you want.”

“What do you mean?”

“You were planning to come back in six hours, right?”

“…”

“So, come back then. Feel free to show off your best skills as much as you want. But…”

Chung Myung smiled.

“You’d better be prepared to have your skulls broken when you come back. Remember, I warned you what would happen.”

Blood drained from Jin Hyeon’s face.

And then, from his pale face, rose a terrifying rage.

Chapter 125: I’ll show you what happens when you touch Mount Hua! (5)

Show off your best skills.

Those words stabbed and twisted like a knife inside Jin Hyeon’s heart.

He couldn’t help it.

There were nine disciples from the Wudang sect guarding the main entrance to Huayoung Gate. Including Jin Hyeon, there were ten in total.

But Mount Hua only sent five disciples.

It would have made sense if they had chosen a representative to have a one-on-one match. These people had come to assist their sub-sect. Even if they recognized that they were no match for the Wudang Sect, since they had come this far, they would still need to act like they tried their best before returning.

But right now, this fool was talking about fighting, not just having a match. Chung Myung was saying that even if all the disciples of Wudang came at once, they would be able to deal with them.

“You…”

Jin Hyeon’s side had twice the number that Mount Hua’s did.

Even so, Chung Myung said they could fight, as if he was utterly ignoring Wudang.

When in Jin Hyeon’s life had he been so neglected?

“Infinite Life Sutra.”

If he didn’t recall his teachings, Jin Hyeon felt that his rising anger would boil over and erupt. He struggled to calm his heart by reciting the sutra before staring at Baek Cheon, a look of unbridled anger still apparent on his face.

“Should I accept this as the will of Mount Hua?”

Jin Hyeon meant that Baek Cheon, as the senior, should voice his position. However, he merely shrugged his shoulders at Jin Hyeon’s question.

“If we take back our words now, the whole world will laugh at Mount Hua.”

“…”

“And.”

Baek Cheon laughed bitterly.

“Even if I wanted to end this peacefully, it doesn’t look like you would let this go.”

“You’ve seen correctly.”

Jin Hyeon bit his lip.

He could tolerate insults directed at him. But now, Chung Myung had not only insulted Jin Hyeon; he had insulted the Wudang sect itself.

“Six Hours.”

Jin Hyeon stared at Chung Myung with a terrifying look in his eyes.

“One day. I’ll give you one day. At this time tomorrow, we will strike Huayoung Gate as you said. Please note that since you were the one that proposed this, we will not be held responsible for any unforeseen accidents according to the Kangho’s laws.”

“Well, just wait until tomorrow. Of course, if you want to play, we could play right now.”

Chung Myung wiggled his finger provokingly.

“Come on.”

“…”

Jin Hyeon’s fists trembled as he tightly clenched them. His breathing grew rapid, and his face went pale.

Seeing this scene, Yoon Jong shook his head.

‘He’ll die from blood pressure before we even fight if he can’t control himself.’

All the disciples of Mount Hua understood. People who don’t know him believe that Chung Myung’s greatest strength lies in his martial arts. However, compared to his ability to piss people off, his martial arts are hardly worth mentioning.

During the relatively short time that Yoon Jong had spent with Chung Myung, there had been dozens of times he thought he might die of anger. At this moment, Yoon Jong couldn’t help but feel sorry for Jin Hyeon despite the barriers between their sects.

‘Just don’t talk to him.’

‘The more you talk, the more he responds, and the angrier you become.’

However, instead of rushing at Chung Myung, Jin Hyeon restrained himself and moved modestly.

Seeing his composure, the disciples of Mount Hua exclaimed.

‘As expected from the Wudang sect.’

‘Oh my, he managed to hold himself back. Hang in there.’

‘Everything looks good now.’

They felt like applauding.

“Tomorrow. At this time tomorrow.”

Grunt!

As soon as Jin Hyeon spoke, he gnashed his teeth.

“I will see you this time tomorrow. Don’t try to ask for mercy from my hands. You’ll understand why you are Mount Hua and we are the Wudang sect! You will understand the difference very clearly.”

“Yeah, yeah. Fine.”

“…”

Chung Myung turned around as if he didn’t care.

“Next, he’ll say that we shouldn’t run away if we doubt our skills. Can we go in and rest now?”

Yoon Jong’s mouth was agape.

‘You devil!’

After three months of closed-door training, had he researched the most effective ways to step on people’s nerves?

Oddly, Jin Hyeon no longer showed any reaction. It seemed true that when a person’s anger boiled over to the extreme, they would become calm and go silent.

Jin Hyeon turned around after giving Chung Myung a cold glance.

“I’ll see you tomorrow.”

With those final words, he decisively left Huayoung Gate.

“Sahyung!”

Wudang sect’s disciples rushed to Jin Hyeon’s side.

“Why are you leaving that arrogant bastard alone!? We don’t need to wait till tomorrow! You need to fix his bad habits now!”

“Right! I’ve never seen such a rude man in my life. I ought to break his head open and bring him back to his senses. No, he’s so out of his mind, even that might not be enough!”

Hearing his sajae’s complaints, Jin Hyeon stopped walking.

“… right now?”

“Yes, now!”

Jin Hyeon took a deep breath.

“Do you know why I said we should wait until tomorrow?”

“We don’t….”

“If we do it now, blood will be drawn.”

The sajaes shut their mouths.

This wasn’t the first time they had come out of the sect. They had already been through such conflicts dozens of times and experienced big and small incidents. Was there anyone among them that hadn’t given or experienced injuries?

Jin Hyeon’s sword had already seen blood many times.

There was no way he would be afraid of seeing blood. Jin Hyeon’s words meant that he would kill Chung Myung if a fight broke out right now.

Jin Hyeon turned his head and looked at Huayoung Gate.

“They’ll soon realize what they’ve done. One day is long enough to let the horror of what’s to come sink in.”

“Yes, Sahyung.”

“Let’s head back.”

Jin Hyeon headed toward Path’s Edge training hall. His sajaes followed behind him, and after a while, the training hall leader also hurried to catch up.

“L-let’s go together!”

“Go.”

“Um. Go please.”

“They left.”

Left behind, Mount Hua’s disciples looked at the empty entrance with slight dismay.

But unlike them, Wei Lishan was on the verge of fainting.

“W-what…. What the hell happened….”

He was sure that he had called for help.

But could ‘help’ mean beating up the Wudang Sect’s people?

In the past, Mount Hua was a prestigious sect and was one of the Nine Great Sects. They should have had some friendship with the Wudang Sect. Wei Lishan hoped that, based on that friendship, they would be able to mediate somehow. He never thought things would get so bad.

Unaware of Wei Lishan’s inner turmoil, Chung Myung smiled.

“Now you can stretch your feet out and sleep comfortably.”

Feet?

Stretch his feet?

“grrr.”

Thud!

In the end, Wei Lishan stepped back and fainted.

“Huh!? Father!”

“Leader!”

Wei Soheng and Yeom Pyong were frightened and rushed to Wei Lishan.

Chung Myung clicked his tongue as he watched the scene.

“I didn’t mean for him to stretch out here. He seems quite impatient.”

The disciples of Mount Hua sighed.

“Huh!”

Wei Lishan jumped out of his bed and looked up at the ceiling with his eyes wide open.

He waited for a while and stroked his forehead with a trembling hand.

‘It was a dream.’

Of course.

Such a nonsensical thing was impossible in real life.

With a sigh of relief, Wei Lishan reached out for his kettle and gulped down some water.

Drinking a bit of cold water, he felt like his heart was calming down.

Clik.

The door opened, and Yeom Pyong entered.

“Are you awake?”

“… how long have I been lying down?”

“It was about four hours.”

“I see…”

Wei Lishan felt like his body was getting weaker as things went on. It was necessary to rest and recover, but he felt like it was abnormal because his body was unable to stabilize.

“I need to get up, we never know when the Wudang sect will come.”

“Didn’t they say they were coming tomorrow?”

“… tomorrow?”

“Yes.”

“Did they come while I was asleep?”

Yeom Pyong narrowed his eyes as he looked at Wei Lishan.

“Did you have any dreams?”

“Yes. Such a strange dream. A person came from Mount Hua, and that thug-like man argued with the Wudang sect’s disciples and risked the fate of Huayoung Gate by demanding a fight.”

“…”

“It was so absurd… even in the dream, I thought I was going to faint. Does it make any sense for such a mad man to come from Mount Hua? He even said that he’s Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon! Hahahahaa. My condition must be worse than I thought….”

Wei Lishan looked at Yeom Pyong and stopped laughing when he saw his serious expression.

And silence fell.

“… it cannot be.”

“It is.”

“I don’t think so.”

“It is quite clear.”

Wei Lishan’s hands trembled.

“I-it happened?”

“Calm down, Gate leader. The water has already been spilled. Now that we’ve reached this point, maybe we should sneak off in the night.”

“Night escape?”

“Isn’t it better than holding out and dying? Seeing the anger on that man’s face, when he comes back tomorrow, he’ll kill anyone in sight.”

“… isn’t he a Taoist?”

“Leader, look at reality. If we counted the number of people the Nine Great Sects have killed, they would fill the entire yellow river. Do you really think there are no wicked men among them?”

Wei Lishan was speechless and closed his mouth.

“If we want to save our lives, we need to think quickly. One day… no, there’s not even a day left.”

Wei Lishan got up with a stiff face.

“Where are Mount Hua’s disciples?”

“I guided them to the annex. They must be there.”

“I see…”

Wei Lishan accepted reality.

If it wasn’t a dream and had actually happened, then now was the time to make a decision.

‘It wouldn’t matter if I was alone.’

But Wei Lishan had a wife and child; he had disciples to protect. And above all.…

‘At this rate, they’ll be upset too.’

Mount Hua’s disciples had come to help Huayoung Gate in their time of need. Although they had chosen a bad method due to their inexperience, Wei Lishan couldn’t bear to see them fall to the Wudang Sect’s sword.

“Pyong.”

“Yes, Gate leader.”

“I think we should lower Huayoung Gate’s signboard.”

“…”

“Even if it isn’t Nanyang, if we can keep the name Huayoung, wouldn’t that be enough?”

“Leader…”

Yeom Pyong felt troubled, but Wei Lishan seemed to be at ease now.

‘It was all greed.’

Wei Lishan never wanted to abandon the land where he lived. His heart didn’t want to be pushed aside by Wudang’s disciples. He was overwhelmed by a desire to protect his Gate.

In the end, it was all because of his greed.

And when he let go of his greed, he felt at ease.

But the world doesn’t always work the way we want.

“That… it won’t work out the way you want, father.”

“Huh?”

Wei Soheng walked into the room.

“What do you mean? It won’t work the way I want?”

“Even if we try to give up now, the disciples of Mount Hua won’t leave.”

“Why?”

“… it’s a bit strange, but they don’t seem to have the slightest thought about losing to the Wudang sect.”

Wei Lishan’s face darkened.

‘What are they? Daredevils?’

No. It couldn’t be.

Even if the others were unaware, Baek Cheon, The Righteous Sword of Hua, is someone who must understand. He led the Baek disciples and would likely become the sect leader of Mount Hua someday.

It didn’t make sense for such a person to be unable to grasp the situation accurately.

“… I need to meet with the Righteous Sword of Hua.”

Wei Soheng’s face turned awkward.

“That’s great.”

“What?”

“Well, he said that father must have woken up by now and he requested to meet you.”

“… the Righteous Sword of Hua?”

“No.”

Wei Soheng spoke with a shaky face.

“Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon.”

That damned dragon of Mount Hua!

“… what Divine Dragon. He has to be the shitty dragon.”

For once, Wei Soheng could fully sympathize with his father’s choice of words.

Chapter 126: The Sword of Mount Hua is Strong (1)

- The current Mount Hua has lost its former light, but Mount Hua once shone brighter than any other sect. Your father has lived his life in pride as a member of Mount Hua.

Gulp gulp.

Dressed in Mount Hua’s uniform, Chung Myung was gulping down alcohol.

“Kuaaa! Alcohol tastes the best.”

- Mount Hua is prestigious. That prestige was not earned without a great history. It took the blood and sweat of countless ancestors before it touched glory and gained such noble status.

“Some meat for me! Give it here, please! Sahyung!”

“There’s nothing left for me to eat! You already ate your own, don’t covet others’ food too! If you don’t want your hands cut off, then keep them to yourself!”

“Selfish!”

- Although Mount Hua is suffering now, it will resurrect and spread its name throughout the world again one day. So, you must not make the mistake of only looking at Mount Hua’s current state. It would be best if you thought of the future as well. Protect Mount Hua. Then, the day will come when Mount Hua protects Huayoung Gate, and we ascend together.

“Kya! Coming down from Mount Hua makes me feel alive!”

“Sasuk is still here! Be careful of what you say, you brat!”

“It’s fine. I’m sure that Sasuk is thinking the same thing I am right now.”

“… No. I feel like I’m going to die staying with you.”

“Hahaha! What a joke!”

“… I wish I was joking.”

Wei Lishan had a pleasant smile as he watched the disciples of Mount Hua, who greedily coveted alcohol and meat while cursing at each other.

‘I want to show this to my father.’

And he would ask

‘What prestige? Resurrection?’

Look!

‘Mount Hua is doomed, father.’

And horribly so!

Tak!

Wei Lishan pressed down the pain rising in his belly. Since earlier, he had been experiencing a sharp stomach ache, like a nail had been driven deep into his core. Yet, this sight before him seemed to hurt even more.

“Kuak.”

Unable to bear this sight any longer, Wei Lishan coughed and attracted the attention of Mount Hua’s disciples, who all turned to look at him in unison.

“Ah.”

Chung Myung sighed and offered Wei Lishan a bottle of alcohol.

“Would you like a drink?”

“He’s in recovery!”

“Didn’t he have internal injuries?”

“Think before you speak, think!”

“No, you bastards!”

And it grew noisy once again. At the same time, Wei Lishan’s stomach began to ache even worse.

‘A name and its pride die first.’

When he visited Mount Hua ten years ago with Wei Soheng in his arms, Wei Lishan could feel the nobility and pride emanating from Mount Hua despite its collapse.

But, whatever the hell happened over the past decade, Mount Hua’s disciples have grown rotten. They’re far from the prestigious and noble image he’d previously experienced.

Instead of Wei Lishan, Yeom Pyong, who was standing next to him, spoke.

“Look here.”

“Yes.”

“… do you understand just what kind of situation we’re in?”

Baek Cheon stood up, and he bowed his head slightly.

“I’m sorry. These guys are a bit free spirited.”

Wei Lishan sighed.

“I’m not going to blame you. Thanks to you we earned an extra day of time. But disciple Baek Cheon, now we have to make a decision.”

“Decision?”

“It’s not easy to set aside everything and leave the home that I love, but now that things have come to this, there seems to be no other way. Huayoung Gate will give up on Nanyang and retreat. So, please listen and return to Mount Hua.

“…. Gate leader.”

Baek Cheon had a complex look on his face.

“I know things got a little out of line….”

“That’s not it. If it was any opponent other than Wudang, I would have stayed and endured to the end. But you don’t know what it means to stand against the Wudang sect. Since they’ve sent their disciples, isn’t it clear that their sect is trying to take over Nanyang?”

“Hmm.”

“Even if you manage to stop them this time, the same thing will happen again.”

Chung Myung poured himself a glass of alcohol and drank it in one gulp.

“Kuak.”

And he spoke to Wei Lishan.

“I was going to ask you about that anyway.”

“Yes?”

“What’s so great about this place? They’re acting way too aggressively for this place.”

The Wudang that Chung Myung remembered didn’t operate like this.

Wudang was one of the most dignified and respected sects in the world.

‘They were the type that would chant their sutras until death.’

Of course, a lot of time had passed since Chung Myung died, but the fundamental nature of a sect doesn’t change that easily.

Would the Wudang sect really use such extreme measures just to spread their influence in Nanyang?

‘There’s something happening here.’

Wei Lishan asked.

“Great?”

“Yes.”

“There’s nothing like that. If there was anything great here, would people have left Nanyang alone till now?”

“Um, I see.”

He didn’t get the answer he hoped for, but Chung Myung wasn’t disappointed. If Wei Lishan had any information, it would probably already be widespread.

Information that Wei Lishan didn’t know was more meaningful.

‘If this doesn’t work, then I can just rip the truth from the Wudang bastards.’

“Rather, you should all head back to Mount Hua as soon as the sun rises tomorrow. I will take care of the rest.”

“What? That’s impossible.”

“… Impossible?”

“Yes. Sect leader told us to solve the Huayoung Gate’s problem. If we leave Huayoung Gate and let it get kicked out of Nanyang, our sect leader sigh to himself and refuse to even see us for at least three months.”

“Wow, I can’t imagine that.”

“I sympathize with you, Sahyung.”

Yoon Jong and Jo Gul trembled, not wanting to imagine it.

“Look, this is no joke.”

“We aren’t joking either.”

As Wei Lishan was about to lose his temper, Chung Myung cut in and spoke with a firm voice.

“Mount Hua has not forgotten the grace Huayoung Gate has shown us.”

Wei Lishan’s eyes trembled.

Unlike before, there was a serious light in Chung Myung’s eyes. Wei Lishan was instantly overwhelmed by Chung Myung’s poise.

“Now it’s time for Mount Hua to repay Huayoung Gate. Mount Hua never betrays its ideals. The world will know that clearly.”

Wei Lishan nodded his head without realizing he’d been swept up in the momentum.

‘Chung Myung’

The one known as Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon.

Wei Lishan began to think that he might have judged Chung Myung too easily in the morning.

“But before that.”

“Yes?”

“I have a favor to ask, Gate leader.”

Wei Lishan nodded his head.

“Say it. I will get anything I can procure.”

“Then…”

Chung Myung shook the bottle in his hand.

“If there is any alcohol left in Huayoung Gate, please give me a bottle.”

“…”

“No, at least three.”

“…”

“You don’t have any?”

“…”

No, maybe Wei Lishan had judged him properly the first time.

“All the preparations are done, disciple Jin Hyeon.”

Jin Hyeon nodded his head.

“You worked hard.”

“Just one more day and this damned work will finally be over. It’s been tough, this role doesn’t fit my character.”

Jin Hyeon smiled.

“We are all fully aware of how hard you’ve worked. When this work is done, the sect leader will surely show you favor back in the main sect.”

“Oh, don’t say that. How could I dare hope for that? If there’s some help for the training hall, that’s all I could hope for.”

Jin Hyeon smiled and nodded.

It didn’t matter if his words were sincere or not. This training hall leader wasn’t important at all. Even if he refuses, the Wudang sect would still reward him, and that would be the end of his role.

“By now Mount Hua has to be trembling.”

“Well. They were quite proud yesterday.”

“Wasn’t that just a bluff? Can Mount Hua even put up a fight against Wudang? I bet there isn’t even a single ant remaining within Huayoung Gate. Isn’t that why disciple Jin Hyeon gave them a day’s time?

Jin Hyeon smiled softly and didn’t respond.

“You must be exhausted from the long journey, I shouldn’t waste your time here.”

“No.”

“Have a good rest. I will see you tomorrow.”

“Have a good night.”

Jin Hyeon sighed as the training hall leader left.

“Sahyung.”

Jin Hyeon’s sajae, Jin Mu, called him.

“Did Sahyung expect Mount Hua to come?”

“I didn’t. But the Sect leader mentioned the possibility. It’s difficult to follow the sect leader’s insight.”

“He’s a man that stands so far above that when he looks down, he sees the heavens.”

“Right.”

Jin Hyeon quietly nodded his head.

“What do you think Sahyung? As the hall leader said, do you think that Huayoung Gate could run away tonight?”

“Huayoung Gate can.”

Jin Hyeon continued calmly.

“But the disciples of Mount Hua cannot.”

“Why not?”

“Because they recently gained fame.”

“Ah…”

Jin Hyeon smiled.

“Normally, people don’t grow overly attached to a reputation that has been rightfully built. But when they get more fame than they deserve, they tend to become obsessed with it. Perhaps Mount Hua’s Divine Dragon will be unable to let go. If he runs away after such light provocation, he’ll become the laughingstock of the whole world.”

“But won’t his reputation suffer anyway if he stays and gets defeated?”

Jin Hyeon’s eyes narrowed.

“Are you saying that losing to me would be a shame to him?”

“I-I didn’t mean that, Sahyung.”

Jin Hyeon smiled and patted Jin Mu on the back.

“I’m just joking. Why wouldn’t they wait? Losing is less shameful than running away.”

“It would be good for them to learn some shame. They don’t seem to understand the concept.”

“Huhuhu. That is true.”

Jin Hyeon smiled as Chung Myung’s face surfaced in his mind.

‘That cheeky bastard.’

Jin Hyeon understood.

Having gained such a reputation at a young age, he must not put others in his sights. There was a time when Jin Hyeon also shrugged his shoulders and arrogantly overlooked others because of his fame.

Wasn’t it the role of the elders to cull that behavior?

“If they don’t know, all we need to do is let them understand.”

“Of course.”

“But.”

Jin Hyeon spoke with a firm expression.

“We shouldn’t focus too much attention on that. You haven’t forgotten our true purpose in coming here, right?”

“Yes, Sahyung. I haven’t forgotten for even a single moment.”

Something that even the other sajaes didn’t know.

Only Jin Hyeon and Jin Mu knew about it. The reason the two of them knew was to prepare for an unforeseen situation. Otherwise, it was something that Jin Mu shouldn’t have known.

“Huayoung Gate and Mount Hua are fine. What’s most important is to draw people’s attention away from Nanyang. If this goes well, we will be able to rise above the Shaolin sect and stand at the peak of the world.”

“I’ll keep that in mind.”

Jin Hyeon turned to look out the window. The moon floating high above, and the stars that shone in the sky reflected in his eyes.

‘Sword Tomb’

The tomb of a sword.

That was why they created a fake subsect and came all this way out here.

“First we drive those Mount Hua bastards out of Nanyang, and then we’ll slowly proceed with the plan.”

“Yes, Sahyung!”

A low smile formed on Jin Hyeon’s lips.

‘Soon the world will be under the Wudang Sect’s feet.’

It was a night of deep conspiracy.

Chapter 127: The Sword of Mount Hua is Strong (2)

Wei Lishan, unable to sleep all throughout the night, stared up at the sky with bloodshot eyes.

The sun was already in the middle of the sky.

‘This is insane.’

Yesterday, Wei Lishan found himself swept along by the atmosphere Chung Myung’s party had created and nodded his head along with them. It should have been impossible for a man his age to lose himself and fall into the rhythm of some children as young as his son, but these weren’t any ordinary people.

In the end, Chung Myung fell asleep after raiding Huayoung Gate’s warehouse and emptying all their liquor bottles. It was even scarier that his sahyungs were there, yet no one stopped him.

‘Is this really alright?’

Mount Hua’s disciples had clearly behaved excessively yesterday.

Hadn’t they hurled such venomous words at the Wudang disciples? Even Wei Lishan would be unable to escape retribution after such insults.

If a fight occurs, the disciples of Mount Hua will not be safe.

But…

Wei Lishan opened the window. He looked out and saw the disciples of Mount Hua, who had come out early to bask in the sun.

“Yhaaaan.”

Jo Gul, who was yawning heavily with droopy eyes, looked at Yoon Jong.

“When are they coming?”

“Didn’t they say they would come today?”

“The sun’s already up.”

“They said they would come at the same time as yesterday, so there’s still a lot of time left. If you have nothing to do, go and sleep.”

“I made a habit of waking up early, I can’t sleep now.”

“… What a sad story.”

It was unknown how he felt about it, but Jo Gul’s body had become faithfully accustomed to Chung Myung’s methods. The sad fact was that it wasn’t just him; Yoon Jong was the same.

“What about Chung Myung?”

“Sleeping. It’d be even weirder if he was awake after drinking that much.”

“… go and wake him, the Wudang will be here soon.”

“Would he even wake up if I asked him to?”

“Pour water on him.”

“… okay.”

Wei Lishan quietly closed the window.

‘Father. I don’t know anymore.’

It felt like his deceased father was looking down at him from the sky.

Suddenly, Yeom Pyong and Wei Soheng entered as the door opened.

“Father.”

“… what is it?”

“What should we do?”

“Hm?”

“The Wudang will attack us soon. Shouldn’t we fight together?”

Wei Lishan took a deep breath.

Actually, he hadn’t yet decided what to do. In fact, it was Mount Hua who provoked the Wudang, not Huayoung Gate. In the worst-case scenario, as long as they are prepared to leave Nanyang, they could withdraw without participating in the battle. At least then, Huayoung Gate might not suffer much damage.

If they say they will leave Nanyang on their own, even the Wudang sect will not persecute Huayoung Gate.

But if they fought, then everyone would need to be prepared to suffer some damage. Wei Lishan and Wei Soheng, in particular, would need to be prepared to shed their blood.

‘What should I do?’

A deep sense of agony tormented him.

In the end, Wei Lishan was unable to decide and looked at his son.

“What do you think we should do?”

It wasn’t a question asked with high expectations. It was just a light question, released in a moment of overwhelming confusion, but his son’s answer was more serious than he thought.

“I think we should fight.”

“… and the reason?”

“They are the guests, and we are the owners. It would be unacceptable for the owner to flee the battle and watch from the sidelines while the guests who came to help are fighting for them.”

“…”

“And…”

Wei Soheng spoke again.

“The reason I respected my father and cherished Huayoung Gate is because my father and I were equally proud of this place. Father never felt bad for supporting the ruined Mount Hua, nor did you expect anything for it. Because we belong to Mount Hua.”

“… Yes.”

“Even if we are a simple sub-sect, a disciple is a disciple. How can we just stay by and watch them fight?”

Wei Lishan turned his head.

He found it difficult to look his son in the eyes at this moment.

“I met the sect leader. Without any hesitation, the sect leader sent the disciples to help us. Their method may not be right, but their hearts aren’t wrong. Even if I die today, it will be at their side. I will fight.”

‘I’m ashamed of myself.’

This was what Wei Lishan thought.

While Wei Lishan turned away and hid from the crisis, Wei Soheng was alone in defending the virtues his father had taught him to uphold.

How could he not feel ashamed?

“Yeom Pyong.”

“Yes, Gate leader.”

“Tell the disciples. Those who want to fight can stay, and those who don’t may return home.”

“… gate leader.”

“We will not hold anyone responsible if they leave, and if Huayoung Gate survives today, we will accept them back without any conditions.”

“Then no one will stay.”

“No.”

Wei Lishan smiled.

“I will stay, and so will Soheng.”

“…”

“That’s enough. We will fight for the name of Mount Hua.”

Yeom Pyong shook his head.

“You two should do that.”

“Will you leave?”

“I will fight for the name of Huayoung Gate, not for Mount Hua.”

“…”

“The weather is fine today, gate leader.”

After falling silent for a time, Wei Lishan smiled and nodded.

“I know.”

Wei Lishan, who was looking at the sky, seemed determined.

“Such nice weather.”

“Kuaaak. I don’t feel well.”

“… stop drinking so much!”

“You drunk bastard!”

Chung Myung grabbed his head.

“Ah, don’t shout! My head is ringing.”

“Did you have to drink alcohol amid all this? We need to fight soon.”

“I can just sober up.”

Chung Myung snapped his fingers, and a translucent haze rose from his fingers.

He cleansed the alcohol poisoning his body.

Baek Cheon watched this scene and stood up. With a more serious tone than ever, he spoke.

“Everyone, listen!”

“Yes!”

“Until now, no matter what you did, I didn’t speak up. But it’s different now. Today’s fight isn’t just our fight, don’t forget that we fight with the name of Mount Hua on our backs.”

“We will keep that in mind.”

Jo Gul, Yoon Jong, and Yu Yiseol looked determined. Even Chung Myung nodded with a smile.

“Sect leader said that this would signal to the world that Mount Hua has resumed external activities.”

Baek Cheon looked at Chung Myung.

“Chung Myung.”

“I know. I know. Gently—”

“No!”

“—Huh?”

Chung Myung looked at Baek Cheon with wide eyes.

“If you are going to do it, do it perfectly.”

“Oh?”

It was strange to hear such words from Baek Cheon.

“It’s inevitable that they will lose. If that’s the case, it’s better to do it perfectly and cleanly.”

“Sect leader told me not to.”

“Wasn’t it you that said the sect leader probably wants to see those Wudang bastards get their skulls cracked before he crosses the river?”

“Oh?”

Chung Myung smiled

‘I like this.’

In the past, Baek Cheon was a man that was overly obsessed with fairness and impartiality. However, after a short couple of years of Chung Myung’s corrosive influence, he had begun to ignore the sect leader’s words… no; he learned to interpret them better.

“Wow, the sect will be running wild!”

“…”

Chung Myung smiled.

“But do you understand what that means?”

“What do you mean?”

“That Mount Hua is ready to resume external activities.”

“… Isn’t it literal?”

Chung Myung smiled bitterly.

“External activity means that we’re interested in the world outside the sect. But what kind of action can Mount Hua take?”

“… Well.”

“Didn’t you see Huayoung Gate?”

“You mean the sub-sects?’

Chung Myung nodded.

“Right. We are going to increase the sect’s influence. Then, the same thing that’s happening now will happen again, but with the positions reversed.”

“_Hmm.”_

“That means the good old days, where our only concerns were training, are over.”

“By ‘the good old days’, you mean that training?”

“Wasn’t that training the best time?”

“You’re crossing the line.”

Chung Myung flinched at the intense backlash over his comments.

It was then…

With Wei Lishan at the head, Wei Soheng, Yeom Pyong, and roughly ten disciples of Huayoung Gate approached them with grim expressions.

Wei Lishan, who arrived right in front of Chung Myung, moved towards Baek Cheon.

“Disciple Baek Cheon. I was so distracted that I couldn’t properly tend to my duties. I bow my head to express my gratitude to you, your party, and even Mount Hua for rushing to assist us in Huayoung Gate’s time of need.”

As Wei Lishan bowed his head, Baek Cheon immediately reached out and made him stand tall.

“Don’t do this, Gate leader. We just did what we had to do.”

“I don’t know what the outcome of today will be, but I will lead Huayoung Gate and fight alongside you all.”

There was no hesitation to be found on Wei Lishan’s face. Seeing that good expression on his face, Baek Cheon also felt at ease.

‘As expected.’

It seemed like it was true that this man had the qualities of a great leader. It made sense; if this man was lacking, then he would never have been able to rouse any support to fight alongside him.

“Thank you, gate leader.”

“Wow!”

Chung Myung applauded.

“As expected of such a loyal person.”

“…”

Baek Cheon had the distressing thought that the word ‘loyal’ sounded like ‘money’ when it came from Chung Myung…

“But, um…”

Chung Myung scratched his head.

“The number?”

“Those who want to leave have left.”

“Still, this many chose to stay.”

Chung Myung nodded his head.

“It’s a good place, and they’re good people.”

Chung Myung spoke in a distant manner that seemed a bit faint as the others focused on him.

“No, well.”

Chung Myung, who was about to say something, just smiled and laughed.

‘It was the same with Mount Hua, in the past.’

Maybe it was just Chung Myung’s idea of the sect.

But even the current Mount Hua is the same.

“Well, it doesn’t look like you can do anything special though.”

“… what?”

“Hm. How do I explain? Just watch and you’ll know soon enough.”

Chung Myung turned his head and shrugged.

Soon after, his eyes centered on the sect’s main gate.

“Looks like they’re coming.”

“You can feel them already?”

“They are coming from the front, aren’t you a bit too relaxed?”

“… monstrous bastard.”

Baek Cheon shook his head. He still couldn’t feel anything yet, but Chung Myung already seemed to have the entire situation within his grasp.

‘Hell, he was drunk until just a moment ago!’

“They’re coming!”

Baek Cheon, Yoon Jong, Jo Gul, and Yu Yiseol stepped forward and put their hands on the swords around their waists. Since everything that needed to be said had already been discussed, the Wudang would come rushing in, ready for battle.

“There’s nothing to be nervous about.”

Baek Cheon spoke softly.

“Don’t forget your training. We won’t lose to anyone. We are disciples of the Great Mount Hua!”

“Yes, Sasuk!”

“Yes, Sahyung.”

The disciples’ each had a determined look in their eyes. The playfulness that was present just a short while ago had faded. Only the cold demeanor and resolve of a swordsman remained.

Baek Cheon now sensed the enemy’s qi as well.

“Get ready!”

Everyone’s eyes were locked onto the main gate.

Reflected in their eyes was the sight of Wudang’s disciples, dressed in black robes, jumping high over the main gate.

Three of them!

‘Take them one by one….’

Suddenly!

“Okay!”

There was an ominous sensation that something crazy was happening from behind before something hazy flew out towards the disciples of Wudang that were crossing the sect’s wall.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

The Wudang disciples were thrown back out at twice the speed they had charged in.

The four disciples of Mount Hua felt their tension deflate, and their qi began to dissipate as if it was running away.

“Huh?”

When he saw their reactions, Chung Myung tilted his head.

“Should I have let them in first?”

“…”

‘You brat! Are you going to do it all yourself!?’

Chapter 128: The Sword of Mount Hua is Strong (3)

“W-what?”

The sajaes who had jumped inside ‘flew’ out?

And they were twice as fast to leave as they were when entering?

Wudang’s disciples caught the sajaes that were thrown back.

“Ack.”

“Ahh… did something hit you?”

Fortunately, it seemed like they weren’t seriously wounded. Considering the speed at which they bounced back, they were strangely uninjured.

“What happened?”

“… I don’t know. I saw something hazy….”

Jin Hyeon’s face hardened.

‘They didn’t even see the attack?’

It sounded like utter nonsense.

One person could say that. Humans make mistakes. But it was impossible for all three of them to be unable to see what had attacked them.

It would only be possible if the attacker’s skill level was several times higher than his sajaes.…

‘… we’re only up against the disciples of Mount Hua and Huayoung Gate.’

Jin Hyeon, who had such thoughts, quickly found a reasonable answer.

“Looks like we stepped into a trap. Though I’m not sure how.”

“You mean it wasn’t an attack?”

“If it had been a proper attack, would it have ended with such little damage? It wouldn’t have been strange if one of them had been cut down.”

“Ah… right, you’re right Sahyung!”

Jin Hyeon bit his lip.

‘Was it really a trap? If not?’

The exact method was unknown, but what became apparent was that the enemies had someone that could utilize some tricks. It seemed that this was the reason they had requested a battle and not a spar.

“They’re playing tricks.”

Jin Hyeon drew his sword and took two steps forward.

“Follow behind me. I don’t know what sort of traps they’re using, so I’ll lead the charge and break through.”

“Yes! Sahyung!”

Jin Hyeon looked at Huayoung Gate’s tightly shut entrance with slightly nervous eyes.

‘What could be behind this? Either way, excessive caution would just play into another trap.’

“Let’s go!”

Without waiting for an answer, Jin Hyeon rushed forward and kicked the gate.

Kwang!

The door shattered and splintered with a crashing roar, scattering shrapnel everywhere.

The dust that had risen gradually subsided, and then there was silence.

‘… where’s the trap?’

Jin Hyeon had gathered his resolve to break in, but nothing happened. He could only see Mount Hua’s disciples standing off in the distance and staring back at him.

“Geez, why did you break the gate? It wasn’t even locked. Ah, kids these days make a mess of everything.”

Chung Myung clicked his tongue.

There were so many reasons that Yoon Jong wanted to scold Chung Myung, but now it was time to deal with the enemy.

Jin Hyeon scanned to the left and then the right before frowning.

“Is this all?”

“What?”

When Chung Myung asked, Jin Hyeon growled.

“Do you intend to deal with all of us with only the few of you? That’s quite bold! I don’t know if that’s confidence or arrogance.”

Chung Myung looked at Yoon Jong with a pouty face.

“What’s he talking about?”

“Well, I’m getting a familiar feeling from him.”

Chung Myung smiled and spoke.

“Don’t you feel like you’re looking at the old Baek Cheon sasuk?”

Baek Cheon, who was suddenly brought into the issue, gnashed his teeth.

“… Don’t.”

“Don’t~.”

“Hey!”

Baek Cheon’s face flushed red.

However, Baek Cheon himself couldn’t deny that Jin Hyeon’s words and actions were similar to his former self.

‘That’s what happens to those who don’t know that there’s another sky above our sky.’

Baek Cheon’s mind was broken after meeting Chung Myung… no, not just literally or metaphorically. Although his head had been beaten, it really did help him to understand reality.

However, no matter how much he’d changed, it was unpleasant to see his shameful past alive and well in front of his eyes.

“…. Let’s just finish this quickly.”

Baek Cheon spoke through a blushing face, and Yoon Jong and Jo Gul turned their heads as they struggled to restrain their laughter.

A look of bewilderment appeared on Jin Hyeon as he watched that scene.

‘What is this? They look relaxed?’

‘Are there other traps?’

Yet, no matter how he scanned the area or searched, he couldn’t feel any qi. What sort of trap could even be used in this place?

And yet, they still greeted him with this attitude?

Jin Hyeon’s face began to heat up.

‘These arrogant bastards!’

Defeating them in a battle of words could help knock them down a peg, but it didn’t seem like it could solve the problem. Jin Hyeon’s mouth opened.

“I don’t know where the hell your confidence comes from. Do you believe that Mount Hua, which has never defeated Wudang in the past, can fight back now?”

Chung Myung laughed.

“Who was never defeated? A hundred years ago, we were much stronger than you.”

Although it was never officially recognized.

“Ha? A hundred years ago?”

Jin Hyeon smiled and laughed.

“Yeah, right. A hundred years ago. The era of the Plum Blossom Sword Saint that you’re so proud of.”

“Huh?”

Chung Myung was a bit shocked.

It felt strange to hear the name ‘Plum Blossom Sword Saint’ coming from this guy’s mouth. That name couldn’t even be heard in Mount Hua, but now it was coming from a disciple of Wudang?

“Did you know that the Plum Blossom Sword Saint you’re so proud of was defeated by the Wudang’s Taiji Sword Emperor?”

“What?”

Baek Cheon was enraged.

“What nonsense are you saying?”

“Hahaha. Nonsense, you say? The two of them once had a spar. To protect the honor of the Plum Blossom Sword Saint, our ancestor hid the result.”

“This…”

“Mount Hua has never been a match for the Wudang sect. It would help you to understand that.”

As Jin Hyeon continued his taunting, the faces of Mount Hua’s disciples flushed red in anger.

It was fine to ignore and look down on them, but disrespecting their ancestors was unforgivable.

The Plum Blossom Sword Saint is the pride of Mount Hua.

“How dare you speak such drivel about our ancestors!”

“You’re crossing the line!”

“He’s not someone your foul mouth can speak of!”

“… I cannot forgive you.”

An unknown sadness encroached upon Chung Myung’s heart when he saw his fellow disciples react like this.

‘They’re protecting me so much! Me!’

‘Hey, you kids! I’m the Plum Blossom Sword Saint!’

‘Ah, oh my, damn it! I can’t even tell them the truth! How tragic!’

But apart from those emotions, Chung Myung didn’t feel particularly angry at Jin Hyeon’s words. He just thought it was a bit absurd.

‘Wow, this is such a distortion of history.’

‘That Taoist bastard demanded a spar with such a determined expression that it seemed like he wouldn’t give up even if he died. It’s a bit annoying to call it a ‘secret spar’, I was just too lazy to fight that weak idiot.’

And what?

Who had beaten whom?

- Your wickedness has gone too far. As a fellow member of a Taoist sect, I will show you the true path of a Taoist. Please do not blame my sword for being merciless; I ask that you reflect on what you have done.

- …t-that… I admit that your power surpasses mine. Knowing that I am lacking, I want to back down. No… I am not trying to walk away; no, wait!—stop hitting me! You’ve already won! How can a Taoist act like this… ah! Ack! No! I am not saying that… ackk!

- Hyung! Spare me!

“He was such a good little brother.”

Although he was older, he referred to Chung Myung respectfully as Hyung.

“Huh?”

“Ah, nothing.”

Chung Myung waved his hand.

After that, whenever Chung Myung stopped by Wudang, he would call out to the Taiji Sword Emperor and have a nice time. They would visit a popular neighborhood where there were a lot of expensive stores. Chung Myung had the pleasure of renting the top floor of the most expensive restaurants and drinking the most expensive alcohol, while the Wudang sect was left to pay the bills.

Whenever Chung Myung thought of the Taiji Sword Emperor’s distressed expression, he felt a little bad before laughing.

No… Now wasn’t the time to reminisce.

“Wow, the story changed this much.”

No one knows the truth, and there is no proof either.

At that time, Jin Hyeon, who misunderstood Chung Myung’s reaction, scoffed at him.

“Even Mount Hua’s most powerful swordsman couldn’t withstand the power of Wudang. Don’t you think you’re too arrogant to try and deal with us now? Your pride in front of Wudang—”

“Hey, shut up and come fight! Come on!”

“…”

Chung Myung sighed heavily.

“You see, it doesn’t matter who won a hundred years ago. Can men from a hundred years ago come and support or cheer for you now? They’re all dead, you bastard! If you like those old men so much, just go join the Wudang—ah, you already are a bastard of Wudang.”

He already is one.

“…. How dare you!”

“Anyway, you old-fashioned people….”

Even though his past had been distorted, Chung Myung didn’t feel angry.

‘What does it matter now? I got defeated by the Heavenly Demon anyway.’

The present is what matters most.

And…

‘That’s what those in power do.’

The Wudang sect would never have dared to say such a thing if Mount Hua was stronger than them. In other words, if the current Mount Hua was overwhelmingly more powerful than the Wudang sect, then even if they claimed that the Plum Blossom Sword Saint was stronger than the Taiji Sword Emperor, there would be no backlash.

Control belongs to those who grasp power, whether it’s history, money, or the right to speak.

This was something that Chung Myung had no complaints about.

‘I’m strong!’

‘It’ll all be mine!’

This problem could be resolved as long as Mount Hua could take down the Wudang sect.

Well, it didn’t really matter if the distorted history was corrected anyway.

The current Chung Myung needed to receive a higher evaluation than the past Plum Blossom Sword Saint.

“You really need to see blood to get your mind strai—”

“Young trainee Wei! Wei!”

Jin Hyeon tried to speak but was interrupted when Chung Myung called for Wei Soheng.

Wei Soheng, who was watching from behind, was utterly puzzled.

“Yes?”

“Did you do everything I asked you to?”

“About the rumors? Y-yes, I spread word to the people in Nanyang.”

“Good. Now then, ugh!”

Chung Myung drew his sword.

The disciples of Wudang flinched as they stepped back.

All of a sudden…

As Chung Myung swung his sword, qi gushed out from the tip.

However, the sword’s slash wasn’t directed at the Wudang disciples. Rather, it headed toward the walls of Huayoung Gate before slicing them open several times.

Crack!

In an instant, the walls collapsed.

“W-what are you doing?”

Wei Lishan’s eyes widened.

‘No, why would that son of a bitch tear down the walls of their own sub-sect?’

“Ah…”

But Wei Lishan soon understood Chung Myung’s intent and went silent.

Around the wall, a stampede of people from Nanyang was rushing to view what was happening.

Having heard that Wudang and Mount Hua would fight at Huayoung Gate, an audience came to watch. Who wouldn’t want to witness this battle?

“I kind of like growing my name.”

Chung Myung chuckled.

Their purpose here wasn’t just to help Huayoung Gate. They needed people to see that Mount Hua could beat down the Wudang sect.

Every small victory they achieved would help raise Mount Hua’s reputation in the future.

“… It’s quite embarrassing.”

Hearing Baek Cheon’s words, Chung Myung smiled.

“If you are going to do it, do it perfectly.”

“Right.”

“Then there’s only one thing left to do.”

Chung Myung looked at the Wudang disciples.

“Sahyung. How many are possible for you?”

“… um… two.”

“I think it’s three for me?”

“Alright, that’s five.”

Chung Myung stroked his chin.

“Yu Sago should take care of four. Baek Cheon sasuk, you can handle him.”

“And you?”

“Do I have to?”

“… forget it.”

‘There are people around, so restrain yourself, please.’

“Then let’s go! Sasuk! Sago! Sahyung!”

“aa…”

“Ack…”

“Phew!”

Mount Hua’s disciples each sighed in various ways as they trudged forward.

“Someone needs to fall today.”

A cold chill flickered in Baek Cheon’s eyes.

“If they’re the disciples of the Wudang Sect, they’ll be more than enough to show the results of your training. Let’s go, guys. Show those bastards the sword of Mount Hua!”

“Yes, Sasuk!”

“Yes, Sahyung!”

Behind them, they heard a quiet voice respond.

“Why do you all react so differently even though I said the same thing?”

‘You should just shut your mouth, brat….’